[
    {
        "question": " 653万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.377263469818494
    },
    {
        "question": " 1722年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1786241655972205
    },
    {
        "question": " 9302年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.68923365642931
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.657800140395275
    },
    {
        "question": " 2998万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.856963311389595
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.73万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.729762030627719
    },
    {
        "question": " 102億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.064175492402775
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.6万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.205912219349476
    },
    {
        "question": " 712時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.630341261993422
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.4時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.886271548445814
    },
    {
        "question": " 3022億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.759600359478023
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.6万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3929415461695025
    },
    {
        "question": " 463億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.887065100118075
    },
    {
        "question": " 175万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.020505825493718
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6369547340889548
    },
    {
        "question": " 935億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.034352160267796
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.19万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2351474365553694
    },
    {
        "question": " 1736万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.461447930170244
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.71兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1739363623834573
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.01兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7632234785656635
    },
    {
        "question": " 921兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.407819131571381
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.9万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7770410082783219
    },
    {
        "question": " 4387msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6421468113067608
    },
    {
        "question": " 3084垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.99031093436416
    },
    {
        "question": " 373兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6351874256547245
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.450242956689482
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.7兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.064920988233652
    },
    {
        "question": " 96兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.982183084461612
    },
    {
        "question": " 117万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.0673631790947855
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.57337528582923
    },
    {
        "question": " 817京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4132813394006005
    },
    {
        "question": " 376京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6384901811519805
    },
    {
        "question": " 5973兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2199232402785483
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.308427055929917
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.87京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9480452951249205
    },
    {
        "question": " 4197万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6229579001162553
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.37229315848789
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.7万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.29845309012318
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.91937690303193
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.94億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.435069696166743
    },
    {
        "question": " 8001万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.283367382354896
    },
    {
        "question": " 986日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.152380653202937
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.5日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.473813270218487
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.83兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.822962661411566
    },
    {
        "question": " 1万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.62169606187031
    },
    {
        "question": " 4436時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.203300819189423
    },
    {
        "question": " 1440万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4378422621132203
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.52兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.820131306963459
    },
    {
        "question": " 213万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.54987517195227
    },
    {
        "question": " 199分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.07611496808491
    },
    {
        "question": " 7701億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.387749215629139
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.6万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8804899346535189
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.58兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.377035252026204
    },
    {
        "question": " 1421万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.374491746733318
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.98秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.99933032921644
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.74京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.074124627989146
    },
    {
        "question": " 246億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.454268924318408
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.5兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.180281853781142
    },
    {
        "question": " 392万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8156826260939918
    },
    {
        "question": " 670億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.826060721397177
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.2万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.635063607684044
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.1msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.691304395243233
    },
    {
        "question": " 3009垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.97964596519514
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.43京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.989209106429292
    },
    {
        "question": " 144京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.603544897936892
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3930773395261966
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.9億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.632106030049782
    },
    {
        "question": " 6547万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.816031578506992
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.8万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.274622369280225
    },
    {
        "question": " 7383垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3694125293349675
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.9垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.674948692658879
    },
    {
        "question": " 2195京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.785158386385666
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5925696972972547
    },
    {
        "question": " 121京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.08253632807388
    },
    {
        "question": " 3754兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.574530663896864
    },
    {
        "question": " 163万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.21309065375044
    },
    {
        "question": " 141年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.71143762263554
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.13万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.652897873301535
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.868625672769308
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.873909368944175
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6331270560030542
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.9日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.73645971762108
    },
    {
        "question": " 5078日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.642213211126634
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.8日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.36451707694713
    },
    {
        "question": " 127万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1610541776484027
    },
    {
        "question": " 29万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.082521943815344
    },
    {
        "question": " 1077時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.810245130107345
    },
    {
        "question": " 5552時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.300768213763113
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.7時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.21610119475804
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.88兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.868000161930604
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.1万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4225786896521964
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.3億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.858748835816433
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.914643545501362
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.46億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3115746472468892
    },
    {
        "question": " 3753万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6379161121841332
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.2億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.277361369513251
    },
    {
        "question": " 2892万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.683031495952866
    },
    {
        "question": " 2766秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.441900976473479
    },
    {
        "question": " 170兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.731369398736862
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.3兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.326370989547944
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.8兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.18247405235137
    },
    {
        "question": " 4801万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.903183016438935
    },
    {
        "question": " 1020億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.008713726742348
    },
    {
        "question": " 843万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.925878861614942
    },
    {
        "question": " 7466京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.374270566873865
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1455600543999789
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.6京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.798518235052459
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2868976308790283
    },
    {
        "question": " 2296万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3609549809892485
    },
    {
        "question": " 2720億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.434561763412876
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.1usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.492153061467744
    },
    {
        "question": " 899垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.454833861021312
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.11垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.388159707188205
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.9兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0656956109757154
    },
    {
        "question": " 940億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1951162623002234
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.1京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.381767439639331
    },
    {
        "question": " 233万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.36670101530974053
    },
    {
        "question": " 1179億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.071604093984213
    },
    {
        "question": " 2207日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.781458073862773
    },
    {
        "question": " 253万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.782548817499632
    },
    {
        "question": " 235万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.529879352898417
    },
    {
        "question": " 104万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0733331879801806
    },
    {
        "question": " 9423時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.593972200540308
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.014323969192584
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.7時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.070745654558585
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.293972868300652
    },
    {
        "question": " 3390万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.371800508602787
    },
    {
        "question": " 2173万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5590057144112635
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.22分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1247538231756637
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.04万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.087004038337984
    },
    {
        "question": " 780兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.393519870940146
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.15億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9745830547549996
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.616210823675372
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.1億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.978148840271424
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.7万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.527574561846482
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.35981494697779
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.5京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.834524192543228
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.81兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.827852925726028
    },
    {
        "question": " 295兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9130333576047995
    },
    {
        "question": " 3351万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7470734958180176
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.8億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.943593563595881
    },
    {
        "question": " 108万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.033466359111738
    },
    {
        "question": " 340msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.531884464586582
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.755881033656209
    },
    {
        "question": " 2979兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.537643101387073
    },
    {
        "question": " 807兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.350482368330827
    },
    {
        "question": " 187兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.493128694796017
    },
    {
        "question": " 313兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.49581862449438
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.34万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.9702533691432145
    },
    {
        "question": " 2547usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.405945078307593
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6891173518106477
    },
    {
        "question": " 2490京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.459746719020261
    },
    {
        "question": " 4949兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1382315396997673
    },
    {
        "question": " 2161兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5565114780204
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.89京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5902800192751405
    },
    {
        "question": " 346億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.538896007165375
    },
    {
        "question": " 674万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.8284074543940116
    },
    {
        "question": " 281年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.010886804284268
    },
    {
        "question": " 2511万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.837484753862932
    },
    {
        "question": " 537万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.110046597529308
    },
    {
        "question": " 359日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.491738887393215
    },
    {
        "question": " 11万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0994157525525838
    },
    {
        "question": " 977億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.609827112579246
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.14万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3952536954399175
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.765289685761357
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.635280506261157
    },
    {
        "question": " 127兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.383437739602076
    },
    {
        "question": " 266億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.265929464980184
    },
    {
        "question": " 486億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.908294448634289
    },
    {
        "question": " 609分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.563109643543512
    },
    {
        "question": " 147分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.9457352153996785
    },
    {
        "question": " 222兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8481906301861155
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.26億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.030133145238249
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.74億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.385317429665584
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.442447516121183
    },
    {
        "question": " 116万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.065021501116318
    },
    {
        "question": " 281兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9493047652002122
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.87億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9002056529542735
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7473784441414697
    },
    {
        "question": " 363億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.78120261601881
    },
    {
        "question": " 379万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5785262698151667
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.6msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.9167615876956745
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.846365217273788
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.65兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4867762169675192
    },
    {
        "question": " 178兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.695148784982255
    },
    {
        "question": " 2433兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.60798888461415
    },
    {
        "question": " 170万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22989934484778374
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.16兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.619270060112463
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.39万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.923885941835675
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.004279823559012463
    },
    {
        "question": " 1736京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.302959782554284
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.8垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.021487576754438
    },
    {
        "question": " 212兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.548376244747259
    },
    {
        "question": " 114兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.057176830986643
    },
    {
        "question": " 7684兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.885607241620999
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.8万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.588845405485425
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.62年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.227296255024882
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.511311627282334
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.94年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.561830317506182
    },
    {
        "question": " 1168億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.505266643616153
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.646289200599792
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.2万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.803906410464236
    },
    {
        "question": " 499万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7555399945436654
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.7億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.298464558006561
    },
    {
        "question": " 422時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.403757041724995
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.4時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.797395148464795
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.5時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.268008684110935
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.3億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.044999662181796
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.4億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.45830379575248
    },
    {
        "question": " 662分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0429060459551986
    },
    {
        "question": " 173万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.015633894782457
    },
    {
        "question": " 1217兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.586347810142322
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.2万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5976600341305804
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.773927751116627
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.69万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.652048966190048
    },
    {
        "question": " 4426秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.645995752023665
    },
    {
        "question": " 5624秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.75007467509062
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.97京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.277223588551617
    },
    {
        "question": " 741億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.933483452526108
    },
    {
        "question": " 495億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.138040284335659
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.1万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.181438289187583
    },
    {
        "question": " 9644億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.984239056441455
    },
    {
        "question": " 2434msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.386388192844471
    },
    {
        "question": " 187兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7732347556109831
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.391866008892165
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.8京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.442820586186748
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.28257599910123
    },
    {
        "question": " 142億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.150888631072769
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.02万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6042809183155338
    },
    {
        "question": " 143usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.15543572332377
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.718e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.488788974384946
    },
    {
        "question": " 6027垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.843611394090162
    },
    {
        "question": " 145京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.606362089336313
    },
    {
        "question": " 8411京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.146716900185085
    },
    {
        "question": " 1671億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2230391953738824
    },
    {
        "question": " 5742億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.7590384358425215
    },
    {
        "question": " 3783万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.577855108945491
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.762856901296292
    },
    {
        "question": " 298億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.911445264417405
    },
    {
        "question": " 747日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.253586588039461
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.2兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.627502164340186
    },
    {
        "question": " 173時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8569129392681563
    },
    {
        "question": " 157万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.973391287212102
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.95319656829322
    },
    {
        "question": " 978万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2699092109430388
    },
    {
        "question": " 444億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.489194441339691
    },
    {
        "question": " 5444万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.957775344480747
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.4分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6556258087818714
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.17兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.121113719627793
    },
    {
        "question": " 764兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.946572161334034
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.560919754748877
    },
    {
        "question": " 1637万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.435865822017934
    },
    {
        "question": " 88秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.944599692469415
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.8秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.76346167207981
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.4兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.049677525124632
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4841109789439646
    },
    {
        "question": " 4811兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.125902147917152
    },
    {
        "question": " 845億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.148633775404939
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.23兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.718641050670588
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.236364405572514
    },
    {
        "question": " 2881msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.459614688752506
    },
    {
        "question": " 826兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.41817803998588
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2157328296908982
    },
    {
        "question": " 5615兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.193030697139
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.53億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.769679766464676
    },
    {
        "question": " 271万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4330211885332269
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.31億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.969010504549538
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.075121796132084
    },
    {
        "question": " 212京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8271787635372616
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.2京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.678556799415741
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.7垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.33952204524452
    },
    {
        "question": " 21京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.544832281735556
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.9京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.868411640077271
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.9兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.953913289890516
    },
    {
        "question": " 436万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.639916696379389
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.826305843110758
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7742633824651186
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.7日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.532993492834284
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.49日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.748441831454871
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.1億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.491042166626688
    },
    {
        "question": " 99万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.615264270423056
    },
    {
        "question": " 120万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.856296781984847
    },
    {
        "question": " 671時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.382717890296707
    },
    {
        "question": " 351億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.824640569074829
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.2万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.583560386133751
    },
    {
        "question": " 870万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.161286301679905
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.85万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.545107406347283
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.5分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.506528009717783
    },
    {
        "question": " 3638万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.062029325980456074
    },
    {
        "question": " 2271万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.419688109997029
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.47兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.316752143338492
    },
    {
        "question": " 461億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.885536143448752
    },
    {
        "question": " 486万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.686559267757477
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.0585603839629965
    },
    {
        "question": " 1041京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.518515549307002
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11173659870681085
    },
    {
        "question": " 4394万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0865926802417147
    },
    {
        "question": " 116万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2866686540855377
    },
    {
        "question": " 7514億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.87584409241845
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4113929160214385
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2213979434218003
    },
    {
        "question": " 581京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.207911412637154
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.57億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9679610320365806
    },
    {
        "question": " 3964億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.598163295330808
    },
    {
        "question": " 1840万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.264773757425447
    },
    {
        "question": " 228万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.357861001761913
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.043e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.519321817276245
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.39京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.593081106776316
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.8垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.299760381708207
    },
    {
        "question": " 8846兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.168576255900492
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.81兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4485525962545625
    },
    {
        "question": " 1485兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.171732015602585
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.6万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.5263422199442864
    },
    {
        "question": " 201年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.866409432679385
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.997663233016083
    },
    {
        "question": " 2255日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7907637388094491
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.766947504812233
    },
    {
        "question": " 2万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.236959569572656
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.6万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4983481025816758
    },
    {
        "question": " 2007万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.922321262578452
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5756256595689697
    },
    {
        "question": " 104万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2960682235594059
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.96856487027423
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.64億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.642722983908928
    },
    {
        "question": " 666万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.601573404032075
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.2分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.083668951790021
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.8兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.338658324677225
    },
    {
        "question": " 57万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8190277284225433
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.04兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.399633635461335
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.74万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7941515276516915
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.78万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.577980987043421
    },
    {
        "question": " 5088秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.706508990420744
    },
    {
        "question": " 4682京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.17162360164
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.7兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.639757272615457
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.664981307115488
    },
    {
        "question": " 1056億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.245476439471489
    },
    {
        "question": " 1095万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.039315566618851
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.5万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.550668542555224
    },
    {
        "question": " 248京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.895692028063207
    },
    {
        "question": " 1679京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.288573265444057
    },
    {
        "question": " 617兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.233997694663798
    },
    {
        "question": " 127億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3264872298959527
    },
    {
        "question": " 975億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.988810123492745
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.39兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.731870062547207
    },
    {
        "question": " 4668usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.669135631233405
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.159e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.565215883164095
    },
    {
        "question": " 182兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3237770619753033
    },
    {
        "question": " 404兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0499646716431608
    },
    {
        "question": " 2134京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.551019634524122
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.09076058054162
    },
    {
        "question": " 316万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.5001397563882126
    },
    {
        "question": " 80万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.902840130303115
    },
    {
        "question": " 6885年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.780425498464908
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.4年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.125311092999156
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.2億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2024020025987525
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.01万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.761219318149956
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.040420451548487
    },
    {
        "question": " 323億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.56705657707198
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.17億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.532011985760025
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.845741481212122
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.491836958204333
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.4億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7004510860570505
    },
    {
        "question": " 1707分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0739973520579218
    },
    {
        "question": " 5322万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9479569366490725
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2753303620667165
    },
    {
        "question": " 102兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5087160426332105
    },
    {
        "question": " 5318億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.789217244915387
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.3万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7065699064639772
    },
    {
        "question": " 3016秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7012137351974699
    },
    {
        "question": " 159秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.201631655857403
    },
    {
        "question": " 105秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.02158933930567
    },
    {
        "question": " 5333億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.228153643454022
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.58兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.617079393561195
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.98億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1405796927118645
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.435641664917434
    },
    {
        "question": " 269万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.429029099966985
    },
    {
        "question": " 876msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.942708507635041
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.669037748580559
    },
    {
        "question": " 3898京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.654374063097235
    },
    {
        "question": " 1328兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.566919015947351
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.4京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.973378350560719
    },
    {
        "question": " 1273万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.104986262618598
    },
    {
        "question": " 3374usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.5281940470280766
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8033765016618033
    },
    {
        "question": " 8463京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.99100121311198
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.459158127956047
    },
    {
        "question": " 4703京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.894259661089166
    },
    {
        "question": " 238京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.376456661247918
    },
    {
        "question": " 1414万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.1504996452373673
    },
    {
        "question": " 723億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.858980632787855
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.017292226722363
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.8年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.015209797794968
    },
    {
        "question": " 1327億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.560474978683542
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.44日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7677157185992576
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.009483799981048
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.82万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8224906939759558
    },
    {
        "question": " 301億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.099028845226538
    },
    {
        "question": " 141時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9282566553888856
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.6万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.195784409812074
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.157983815031583
    },
    {
        "question": " 3697分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4095055978393414
    },
    {
        "question": " 165万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.438104918060731
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.883954545865668
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.1億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2498467238957796
    },
    {
        "question": " 450万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.717031221899391
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.8兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.125089842081097
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.743539938509856
    },
    {
        "question": " 823万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.915647317082467
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.37兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4730228126518297
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.086469477534738
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.04兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.050198149898122
    },
    {
        "question": " 3637万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7826435150647
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.144616478633895
    },
    {
        "question": " 4463msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.649671631269406
    },
    {
        "question": " 7088京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.35173616352084
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.1兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.950740888161787
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.5億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2978870514104748
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.308341200184592
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.19億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.791541879299446
    },
    {
        "question": " 2046億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.310864786437206
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.69万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.567243380809339
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.344e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.139053678166077
    },
    {
        "question": " 1197垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.141638421802007
    },
    {
        "question": " 355兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.99399025910165
    },
    {
        "question": " 2427兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.606831091817812
    },
    {
        "question": " 1725兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.236734543097415
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.4兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.865782959805338
    },
    {
        "question": " 3405nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.5320596806400613
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.1万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.026321330602519
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.34209561496556
    },
    {
        "question": " 427年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.351256051710234
    },
    {
        "question": " 1369万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.574035059664075
    },
    {
        "question": " 634日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.738408766604542
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.292256446350422
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.02万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.466218848909306
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.56万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.301489938950397
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.47億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.819839564247734
    },
    {
        "question": " 5506億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.582501002880038
    },
    {
        "question": " 5872分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9906378390262913
    },
    {
        "question": " 949万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.755429201736769
    },
    {
        "question": " 2978分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.252014138674307
    },
    {
        "question": " 667兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.325148137683483
    },
    {
        "question": " 107億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.092879018870727
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6349109915106499
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.3億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.931666883329961
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.53910356195959
    },
    {
        "question": " 1555億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.255297106661618
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.62兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.379225355565966
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.455240098889338
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.85兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.685485214151463
    },
    {
        "question": " 770msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.886236359611274
    },
    {
        "question": " 3737京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.073744222213674
    },
    {
        "question": " 8196京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.977090215298816
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.56877871930601
    },
    {
        "question": " 120兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2994651681896565
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2642393229883804
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.77億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.442613300450634
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.3万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.66567952773728
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.3京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.019347510013537628
    },
    {
        "question": " 523垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.782244448944516
    },
    {
        "question": " 4588京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.105320152514482
    },
    {
        "question": " 3715億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7917957045489721
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.034006385270246
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.1億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.59188343557874
    },
    {
        "question": " 446億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.649819986210474
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.95年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.340631400356733
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.655308430282443
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.34万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.107784645200624
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.29日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8814847355865725
    },
    {
        "question": " 6949日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.778412174179497
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4454238963751453
    },
    {
        "question": " 508万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.325304990818354
    },
    {
        "question": " 481万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.460582722850098
    },
    {
        "question": " 9769億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.269205231449235
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.3億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.487995812539218
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.8万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.19420913634979
    },
    {
        "question": " 1135分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.833017824388373
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.934866690654001
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.598448084211089
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.45億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7998741228557495
    },
    {
        "question": " 6537万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.259083126451539
    },
    {
        "question": " 190秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5003219506944789
    },
    {
        "question": " 170万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.23028954536112
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.41京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.234686540010776
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.89京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.901991978125166
    },
    {
        "question": " 1769兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.691482346417924
    },
    {
        "question": " 628万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0196597894050483
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1082691474695485
    },
    {
        "question": " 5722msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.757556843635333
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.4msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.822061864931983
    },
    {
        "question": " 2477垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.89504580948706
    },
    {
        "question": " 121兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1447683043092676
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.6億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31650861829716326
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.34兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.859654649623756
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.62億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8211569083120946
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.69兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.938848671907762
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.763e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.747544716328404
    },
    {
        "question": " 3203垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.569035051926164
    },
    {
        "question": " 1799京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.698844659329325
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.72兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7926475938803843
    },
    {
        "question": " 580京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.76315080317004
    },
    {
        "question": " 151兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.179260288194081
    },
    {
        "question": " 8703億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.93967745226436
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.22年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.280124791493378
    },
    {
        "question": " 157年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.137991639361714
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.307205446390025
    },
    {
        "question": " 857億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.37052154376661
    },
    {
        "question": " 108万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.413994836589508
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.3万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.624774307762394
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.400272281502976
    },
    {
        "question": " 1542万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.807908647885791
    },
    {
        "question": " 3702時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.346597599228531
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.72628080745557
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.2兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.924637127087067
    },
    {
        "question": " 208億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1605198978202385
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.53万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.877559391951925
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.8分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.378110366955868
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.782261373773825
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.06億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.767508458712271
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.541114077059132
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.289973099294008
    },
    {
        "question": " 906秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.957075591296244
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.373485941980414
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.7京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.325214859079936
    },
    {
        "question": " 1416兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.214697087814276
    },
    {
        "question": " 184兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.707972945143822
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.638619768859102
    },
    {
        "question": " 1762msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24593385696399905
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.35msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.638665349791745
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.979173382805868
    },
    {
        "question": " 3441京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.600175252982616
    },
    {
        "question": " 214京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.773254937216159
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.52京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.963984443625815
    },
    {
        "question": " 2248兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.351834530687084
    },
    {
        "question": " 8928億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.950774513478281
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.64万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.751006594820914
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.2京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8659960651483445
    },
    {
        "question": " 637兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8673070156153295
    },
    {
        "question": " 613兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2314094630184544
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5080032579353453
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4964727950685575
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.04億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.309310890386497
    },
    {
        "question": " 7223億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.858692507632762
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.1年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.362258210726409
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.9年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.459984245176219
    },
    {
        "question": " 1446万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.597962942604551
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.48日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1915292322096547
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.962800423862873
    },
    {
        "question": " 39億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.648138708858784
    },
    {
        "question": " 2782万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.064200837854407
    },
    {
        "question": " 7546時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.655876057178099
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.407609157659235
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.32兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.363232470634927
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.1万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.109018568409314
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.39万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.308378106772504
    },
    {
        "question": " 313分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.273372248693026
    },
    {
        "question": " 1024億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.511470469882404
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.7億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.809507047957049
    },
    {
        "question": " 2239万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.793662280195935
    },
    {
        "question": " 957万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.202921474197575
    },
    {
        "question": " 5851京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.268416149591634
    },
    {
        "question": " 3051兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.547947339913966
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.3億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.049352020150966
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.12億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.836607726053659
    },
    {
        "question": " 5530万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.742708470542643
    },
    {
        "question": " 863万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.936173720725991
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8493883416790142
    },
    {
        "question": " 649京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.875608060209375
    },
    {
        "question": " 8014億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3475366397401665
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.46億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7607789756827732
    },
    {
        "question": " 1356万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1323611475250228
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.7億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.356798497999717
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.8垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.23210598630074
    },
    {
        "question": " 172垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.300233085053211
    },
    {
        "question": " 4132京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.059861864139245
    },
    {
        "question": " 135京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.353106976867453
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.228678229576425
    },
    {
        "question": " 276万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.44065048309111177
    },
    {
        "question": " 1560億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.193165993751073
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.46年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.211684939042596
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.5万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.80896664320004
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.510922505980279
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.12億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9324845902007
    },
    {
        "question": " 1201万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.459847113798727
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.57万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.037310674949822
    },
    {
        "question": " 69日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.775094574288838
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2939374534339345
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9058178549148805
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.911484593039312
    },
    {
        "question": " 2535兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.683284558075808
    },
    {
        "question": " 2615万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2591905624655055
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.6億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.220297949044022
    },
    {
        "question": " 2701分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.20975242598934
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.15106123218067
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7868524378419051
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.1万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0131610134356395
    },
    {
        "question": " 423億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.069738790299038
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.8億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.540458811499416
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.45万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.538415349521387
    },
    {
        "question": " 239兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8789063147585914
    },
    {
        "question": " 8457兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9907320494125065
    },
    {
        "question": " 20億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.745623488941588
    },
    {
        "question": " 131億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.340597080482437
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0300953552242775
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.7万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.775983756667092
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.3兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.009939031251298136
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.8京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.401001950363693
    },
    {
        "question": " 1046京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.463343444452924
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.550907376528943
    },
    {
        "question": " 1150万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0605829362867958
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.04兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.956319754604513
    },
    {
        "question": " 565usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.752106882934765
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.39京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03171419730612968
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.395726957646892
    },
    {
        "question": " 265京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.866884285966957
    },
    {
        "question": " 686億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05797432337719899
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.386936440779278
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.412136142397946
    },
    {
        "question": " 1744万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.2414384507363865
    },
    {
        "question": " 3791年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5212294846889
    },
    {
        "question": " 5121万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.147035952031506
    },
    {
        "question": " 3521日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.926835580337628
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.15万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.435173059690577
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.345747956166946
    },
    {
        "question": " 48億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.30149102105417
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.88559499146548
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.27時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.277800149553718
    },
    {
        "question": " 126万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.37875458125671946
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.7万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5289622327903896
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.76万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9820230194183917
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.5分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.506687196125696
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.676969530193984
    },
    {
        "question": " 793万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9628593041751363
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.618723690144046
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.41億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.866287586109254
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.021256787976403
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.68京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.325688407117454
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.6兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.893671684326676
    },
    {
        "question": " 7064兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.292768509684858
    },
    {
        "question": " 192万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5055948253883256
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.078869364503136
    },
    {
        "question": " 8843兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4477766323980754
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.53垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.610703407762237
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.773258218008447
    },
    {
        "question": " 3688兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.788676703073506
    },
    {
        "question": " 1094億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.038832765967624
    },
    {
        "question": " 845万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.927053839813033
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.883e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.09033136247847
    },
    {
        "question": " 397兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6623880111726332
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.76兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.33379172136986934
    },
    {
        "question": " 4747億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8982700035471491
    },
    {
        "question": " 301京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.478982726160265
    },
    {
        "question": " 1593万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.2022904980301063
    },
    {
        "question": " 3228nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.5089834222006895
    },
    {
        "question": " 2236年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.91169024459803
    },
    {
        "question": " 8524年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.873166674112309
    },
    {
        "question": " 3534年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.268970726794386
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.51603720788777
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.79日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8254969958312683
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.9兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.77259143338739
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.1億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.495589762207995
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.964683517494019
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.7万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.22556043169704
    },
    {
        "question": " 107万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.310402279341605
    },
    {
        "question": " 9543億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.821351656434452
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.47441331835898
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.38分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7504532341453625
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.28万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.500838622088416
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.3分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.672081882158738
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6673518631787276
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.7億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.049018333398015
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5334755709532224
    },
    {
        "question": " 309億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.712508223330937
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.99464540473779
    },
    {
        "question": " 1715億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.73552072316033
    },
    {
        "question": " 337兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.591117169781966
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.46772537248955
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.28兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.853292077147326
    },
    {
        "question": " 33万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5182940522488906
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.0911683063756836
    },
    {
        "question": " 1475垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.670133151150825
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.39232349853005
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.448671828393938
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.86兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.989457846030483
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.88億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2733220579639104
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.76万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.7600600909476383
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.85京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.26857204131606305
    },
    {
        "question": " 1195垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.1409336416769
    },
    {
        "question": " 203兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7515415174040005
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.2京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.60621800792741
    },
    {
        "question": " 164兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.213660489047964
    },
    {
        "question": " 710万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.8511282531690256
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.09兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.784892101182715
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.86年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.185019586223452
    },
    {
        "question": " 293億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9051689065173045
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.556806244785808
    },
    {
        "question": " 639日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.963933607728807
    },
    {
        "question": " 132日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.057275197272695
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.22万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8513444843889073
    },
    {
        "question": " 806万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.52606040165449
    },
    {
        "question": " 195万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.069091702543718
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.742397686117016
    },
    {
        "question": " 3609万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8367656339053529
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.089925282937599
    },
    {
        "question": " 336分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7478743701786539
    },
    {
        "question": " 8668万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.716077116130977
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.35分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.149354457624247
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5976657554467355
    },
    {
        "question": " 165億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.281808159297556
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.5億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3160291336513
    },
    {
        "question": " 251億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.62086231173189
    },
    {
        "question": " 148万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.170405288424325
    },
    {
        "question": " 598秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.776776302017371
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.8兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.439557617293112
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.3兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.821593741852851
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.36億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3661181280997
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43701442337467644
    },
    {
        "question": " 5050msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.703265876490814
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.8msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.976819927120796
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.1京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.250473276761689
    },
    {
        "question": " 8131兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.973646490085395
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.9京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.341388127928833
    },
    {
        "question": " 2481兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6165313397251575
    },
    {
        "question": " 110万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04295983059904085
    },
    {
        "question": " 222億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.346742950784443
    },
    {
        "question": " 497京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1979119694101823
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.94垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.351436487166039
    },
    {
        "question": " 122垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.5285138834858
    },
    {
        "question": " 300京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.699478650845146
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.172668887869115
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.75億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.6771223348831077
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.085751676557973
    },
    {
        "question": " 999年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.562081299747593
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.76万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.517519640762414
    },
    {
        "question": " 1274万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.542700034289664
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.1万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.004150979920569
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.25日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9541632785564995
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.76万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.887379366839619
    },
    {
        "question": " 216時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9541837149373855
    },
    {
        "question": " 500時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.255697409095369
    },
    {
        "question": " 779億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.171063353440491
    },
    {
        "question": " 393億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.43636979123653
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.5万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.677220052617024
    },
    {
        "question": " 1785億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.752794768124874
    },
    {
        "question": " 1685万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2899828191236296
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.7万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9588985421359517
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.7万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.809504342042831
    },
    {
        "question": " 2217秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.3457587785531455
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.547388953693416
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.15兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.974717069580942
    },
    {
        "question": " 236兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.817336348302355
    },
    {
        "question": " 403億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.827037349364284
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.8万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7546136610601826
    },
    {
        "question": " 978万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.990372789402025
    },
    {
        "question": " 1950垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.79125858182478
    },
    {
        "question": " 1196京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.141155301113773
    },
    {
        "question": " 696京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.286597806811917
    },
    {
        "question": " 28億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6693382614882912
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.9億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4754880402547483
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.183898393606349
    },
    {
        "question": " 630垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.30081643357428
    },
    {
        "question": " 366兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.627553126381174
    },
    {
        "question": " 1246兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.539104990716601
    },
    {
        "question": " 1972京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.516668034882958
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.031886827322726
    },
    {
        "question": " 219兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.341141804724934
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.23万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.6258278431217499
    },
    {
        "question": " 2232年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.91099982268104
    },
    {
        "question": " 2255年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.295602766151147
    },
    {
        "question": " 168年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.945319905683014
    },
    {
        "question": " 131億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.553932146647847
    },
    {
        "question": " 480日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0613702477703715
    },
    {
        "question": " 595万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.932931603437611
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.91億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.82893906337727
    },
    {
        "question": " 7796万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.511693608093211
    },
    {
        "question": " 8509万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.708012358781525
    },
    {
        "question": " 236時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.929648121532111
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.4億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.190074692427425
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8755797107015448
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.2億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.205241995976037
    },
    {
        "question": " 6684万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.603155371083654
    },
    {
        "question": " 5298億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.225278510514626
    },
    {
        "question": " 596兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.838640238999183
    },
    {
        "question": " 164億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.659596704618074
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.38万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7502399106287525
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.47秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7382981116582914
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.24兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8514172725366795
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.3京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.41274606860035
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.92兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4402228782049145
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.2億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.905040370540789
    },
    {
        "question": " 306億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.485292073515595
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.4msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.693477500565305
    },
    {
        "question": " 1261京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6018820903077025
    },
    {
        "question": " 752兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.939834720115989
    },
    {
        "question": " 3844兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0284776718899025
    },
    {
        "question": " 6116億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.008297327771696
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.121823709864848
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.436056164930097
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.2760975375619807
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.211e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.00777869118752
    },
    {
        "question": " 628兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8614439380652505
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.02京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.290249232034428
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.1京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.028905578076729
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.200392525336099
    },
    {
        "question": " 1158兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.063660736298583
    },
    {
        "question": " 318万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.50303079834132
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9050151646897393
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.98年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.844623147519089
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.19年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.002359642869711
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4960201348216018
    },
    {
        "question": " 1713日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.613969634690758
    },
    {
        "question": " 4193日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7808375420425735
    },
    {
        "question": " 976日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.926125644796109
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.21288805037696923
    },
    {
        "question": " 487時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3071021776990133
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.8時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3990847534574042
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.287371630983724
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8976681652229066
    },
    {
        "question": " 411億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.835235000563115
    },
    {
        "question": " 43万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.411408393894887
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.80110189638462
    },
    {
        "question": " 2112万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3882280982820125
    },
    {
        "question": " 248億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.838432102088852
    },
    {
        "question": " 951秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2001851173076972
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.29800654386782
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9128486974997072
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.584761104552477
    },
    {
        "question": " 1210兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.526383420551916
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.5億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.85040600534377
    },
    {
        "question": " 1166msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06658899879077085
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.8msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.641684250228825
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.336162861983139
    },
    {
        "question": " 1023兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.510873515702238
    },
    {
        "question": " 2339京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.432577600669779
    },
    {
        "question": " 107京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.472923655703857
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.4兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.718638079770921
    },
    {
        "question": " 58億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7637916775497016
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.81万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.4481903609280222
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.103651149636287
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6522035534952875
    },
    {
        "question": " 131京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.181524160304404
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.45垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.370742368026665
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.7京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.198409524489346
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.2京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.996680790316937
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.1億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.700050075658753
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.86兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.895193586638664
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5726180693369045
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.96年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.637805189554287
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.8年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.418087475102471
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.768158711478787
    },
    {
        "question": " 203億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7448794445993885
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5073636596092284
    },
    {
        "question": " 1558日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.350839292672036
    },
    {
        "question": " 3776日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.51357542194772
    },
    {
        "question": " 189万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.334571253940191
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.22億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1276169486552075
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.02時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3827974933275495
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.78兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.958392481563404
    },
    {
        "question": " 586万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.609272144827711
    },
    {
        "question": " 142万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.374320674199942
    },
    {
        "question": " 964分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.762431411561123
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.04分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.480481050572883
    },
    {
        "question": " 4695億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.172790957175186
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.35兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.034263981540091
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.2億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0581973077742255
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.7億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.918210244545798
    },
    {
        "question": " 4641秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.666583657486543
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.64京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.92330259326884
    },
    {
        "question": " 425億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.692097766457109
    },
    {
        "question": " 1120億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.492948294573397
    },
    {
        "question": " 38兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.80172232372871
    },
    {
        "question": " 5294億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.723747408134209
    },
    {
        "question": " 5726msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.757873434304012
    },
    {
        "question": " 823兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4166161256090959
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.125976955553543
    },
    {
        "question": " 2004億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7455235860399532
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2487882360431357
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.48兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.976590986543332
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.21兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.716685663773701
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.7usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.783012187904254
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.618464268413389
    },
    {
        "question": " 2177京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.401427770758214
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.71兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.013076238596144707
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.07京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.831882955069227
    },
    {
        "question": " 8443億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.926491170557356
    },
    {
        "question": " 1522億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.182327752043051
    },
    {
        "question": " 374億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.572495444369785
    },
    {
        "question": " 1316万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.6816428753322
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.980154172391498
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.528212831943052
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.46869884329706
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.4日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0997935790512745
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18597172063894996
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.65億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0431137308172564
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7282563754454823
    },
    {
        "question": " 8571万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2124016841500707
    },
    {
        "question": " 106億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.864919181087984
    },
    {
        "question": " 2456万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.612155576805916
    },
    {
        "question": " 2294万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.138778941690429
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.34億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.422562052171431
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.213610807910011
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.451941285507824
    },
    {
        "question": " 1330億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.345598592763084
    },
    {
        "question": " 1764京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.747799897176057
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.3京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.84348023340906
    },
    {
        "question": " 167兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.666036555776566
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.3兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.858738544348451
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.5万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9799105776695987
    },
    {
        "question": " 570万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.755786214869671
    },
    {
        "question": " 381兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0817076585703433
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.74京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.738864107800065
    },
    {
        "question": " 3863億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.030664604866735
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.3京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.769694756496047
    },
    {
        "question": " 1591億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.201724060981299
    },
    {
        "question": " 1137万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.0556046302098325
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.19usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.3402792543886672
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.2垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.126502401819716
    },
    {
        "question": " 4593垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.725635873196012
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.2垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.923162379229856
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.15垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.9333341382433
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.102146967604385
    },
    {
        "question": " 1989万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.2986425868065432
    },
    {
        "question": " 2000億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.301049251090186
    },
    {
        "question": " 1864万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.83284494663582
    },
    {
        "question": " 168年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.945062662772001
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.9億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.275621049840039
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.62日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.130039315103276
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.4日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.01218891859221
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.76万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.734722247264874
    },
    {
        "question": " 644億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.428407522534291
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.09万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.562557530216529
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.93時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.023775328756379
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.634652998020475
    },
    {
        "question": " 1198億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.357847399203207
    },
    {
        "question": " 243億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.22679766361296
    },
    {
        "question": " 4353億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.860665988719596
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.19万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.119052646403496
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.9億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.424905090838224
    },
    {
        "question": " 579兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.826185573134135
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6379144714969152
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.06億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.004085686885365
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.04秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.847270089389716
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.19兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8426139997464663
    },
    {
        "question": " 2612兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.480480525382269
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.5億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8423038795139546
    },
    {
        "question": " 2749万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6609792362780063
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1037696299903887
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.284667314851447
    },
    {
        "question": " 161兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.707366155684277
    },
    {
        "question": " 1061京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.089224138558292
    },
    {
        "question": " 1943京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.732254291656435
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.7京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.64808681079914
    },
    {
        "question": " 299万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47556422488157835
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.8万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.8851277960446553
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.642e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.923100825474227
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.06垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.912416079067522
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.5垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.246802592392697
    },
    {
        "question": " 5523兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.96400112884956
    },
    {
        "question": " 442億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.645594911295808
    },
    {
        "question": " 5952億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.774631061058676
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.08万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.7837344921665044
    },
    {
        "question": " 846年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.489848615880977
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.75万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.517104727287956
    },
    {
        "question": " 4811日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1199715912659503
    },
    {
        "question": " 149万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.553089089418554
    },
    {
        "question": " 413日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.77430491632101
    },
    {
        "question": " 600日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7148881938509355
    },
    {
        "question": " 204万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.36759171385015
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.7万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.504393057695976
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.2時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7136753546571164
    },
    {
        "question": " 5時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.255067821071631
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.1万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1062620802240255
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.02兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.745952063179725
    },
    {
        "question": " 199分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5215231513847651
    },
    {
        "question": " 3410万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.310857451316414
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.7分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.318734548712044
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.5分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.322566622813566
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.32京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.021813283220734
    },
    {
        "question": " 8043万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9689149794008496
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.566207211483098
    },
    {
        "question": " 142秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3755049551792877
    },
    {
        "question": " 14秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.144609264765377
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.8秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.579995728177263
    },
    {
        "question": " 4654京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.169029192491871
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.45京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.711813027302814
    },
    {
        "question": " 3187兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.947103027283527
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.3億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.589563213583086
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.345245928920972
    },
    {
        "question": " 3386msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.529745013023101
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.4msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.4681313825137625
    },
    {
        "question": " 301京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.979887656974835
    },
    {
        "question": " 247京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.456474800709931
    },
    {
        "question": " 64兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.250161230603055
    },
    {
        "question": " 3557兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.772965199162805
    },
    {
        "question": " 120兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.07964789168288
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.164904554400188
    },
    {
        "question": " 1047垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.521288792038874
    },
    {
        "question": " 2824京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.514392832477618
    },
    {
        "question": " 134兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5708682505103588
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.19京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.725676566888658
    },
    {
        "question": " 444兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.647578417432294
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.89兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.689724829609051
    },
    {
        "question": " 4602nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.6629684365358135
    },
    {
        "question": " 9865年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.55637778507732
    },
    {
        "question": " 9054年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.899337452886885
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.41年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.694388624038702
    },
    {
        "question": " 247年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.892293489106935
    },
    {
        "question": " 138万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5779532463196295
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.3日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2994971220403593
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.02837729810656
    },
    {
        "question": " 458億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.718798342727002
    },
    {
        "question": " 1319時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7402057009011795
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.4時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4543307518778468
    },
    {
        "question": " 700時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.401404777027513
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.1億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.137099276951414
    },
    {
        "question": " 2968億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.314119920453654
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.85億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.676064739632356
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.4万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.529654973162522
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.5分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.130359938161981
    },
    {
        "question": " 5379億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.231888695002972
    },
    {
        "question": " 6001億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.841714524689907
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.91兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.135083086294678
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.41309604370926
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.52秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.654935806423938
    },
    {
        "question": " 138京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.640596322696107
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.4京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.858720272426295
    },
    {
        "question": " 566億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.196527338344609
    },
    {
        "question": " 22万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5642018380441371
    },
    {
        "question": " 526万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.720602884596399
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.025600571186355
    },
    {
        "question": " 524兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2208886561694443
    },
    {
        "question": " 953億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.042587435304322074
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.91兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.341940030018886
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.23兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.187190784487639
    },
    {
        "question": " 1140兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.056772908078264
    },
    {
        "question": " 7048万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.84808335553617
    },
    {
        "question": " 1951usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.290311197792776
    },
    {
        "question": " 1181垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.573569727477405
    },
    {
        "question": " 8793京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.007637111181162
    },
    {
        "question": " 4526京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.099416492627764
    },
    {
        "question": " 7400億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0910711140306473
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.6兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.848747474642796
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.2億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.635679136082044
    },
    {
        "question": " 1218万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.085636161597854
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.575830142321218
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.43886142776563
    },
    {
        "question": " 5606万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1863791818219145
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.718570998525745
    },
    {
        "question": " 170日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.388359643524038
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.7日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7472384062682895
    },
    {
        "question": " 5026億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.75876036497939
    },
    {
        "question": " 4032万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.225333536947084
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.37時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.423803228145306
    },
    {
        "question": " 370時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.124909916711442
    },
    {
        "question": " 95兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.257048193429952
    },
    {
        "question": " 4834万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.525990740377558
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.24万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1875819678692183
    },
    {
        "question": " 263万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.198507043487567
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.95685461727788
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.095121452815464
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.703452520723921
    },
    {
        "question": " 731兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.92741832168103
    },
    {
        "question": " 259億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.85764608471803
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.7億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.005198464552365
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.32秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.365273978857882
    },
    {
        "question": " 7426兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.371936249056233
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.33億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9285474025872587
    },
    {
        "question": " 347億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.983662028909193
    },
    {
        "question": " 100兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.223925709309453
    },
    {
        "question": " 66億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.819680893239828
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.2msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.5050642782325614
    },
    {
        "question": " 168垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.725216018844447
    },
    {
        "question": " 4115兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.677858431454084
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.5京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.071985980067378
    },
    {
        "question": " 1143億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2799690232148917
    },
    {
        "question": " 2720億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.434602597070607
    },
    {
        "question": " 6524万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.814542559613225
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.094229946903382
    },
    {
        "question": " 3458垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.040053458050146
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.290828673777589
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.9京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.933555211949308
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.7兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5969081366863547
    },
    {
        "question": " 485兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6860297191154405
    },
    {
        "question": " 5519億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.741895900997073
    },
    {
        "question": " 7683億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.885557238447298
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.633277265701051
    },
    {
        "question": " 1069年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.971616057766945
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.812224609800527
    },
    {
        "question": " 4744万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.11386468173267
    },
    {
        "question": " 1549日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5701631241939475
    },
    {
        "question": " 7344日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.802420985864567
    },
    {
        "question": " 1349万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1875595028455184
    },
    {
        "question": " 109億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.658753427158521
    },
    {
        "question": " 108万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.809749796814102
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.6万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.513534155098977
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.2億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.995575096203551
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.92万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.613890797520845
    },
    {
        "question": " 416万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.841330585423647
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.785857954847312
    },
    {
        "question": " 1814億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.759948509219746
    },
    {
        "question": " 3089万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5532535470729156
    },
    {
        "question": " 805万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3496213347938064
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.5億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.98185565614585
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.16秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.618843023871564
    },
    {
        "question": " 4809京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.183252117844983
    },
    {
        "question": " 917兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.025803177042089
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.781356823295405
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.191457000524055
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.95兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.841884361948747
    },
    {
        "question": " 92msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.963639917815952
    },
    {
        "question": " 310京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.992352791703673
    },
    {
        "question": " 1735兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.302720572405242
    },
    {
        "question": " 3546兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.993394447150795
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.311008313500089
    },
    {
        "question": " 680億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.83235317910646
    },
    {
        "question": " 1435億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.156986100230379
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.396e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8807093962659716
    },
    {
        "question": " 147兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23104096245121442
    },
    {
        "question": " 215京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.775258587995262
    },
    {
        "question": " 689京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.060209629473722
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.071429856823717
    },
    {
        "question": " 3785億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.578107016928517
    },
    {
        "question": " 7304億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.863550648670506
    },
    {
        "question": " 3017年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.041852712608132
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.77年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.441769844268789
    },
    {
        "question": " 5003万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.136959096905052
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.5日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2748659967010854
    },
    {
        "question": " 1656日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.377480301364102
    },
    {
        "question": " 277日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.379252731753474
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.37日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.804069482565751
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.71万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6267461086843062
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.4万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.39322774603804
    },
    {
        "question": " 1828時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.818349527912872
    },
    {
        "question": " 109時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.591824846934252
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.19時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.897511883599963
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.42億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.662414951683517
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.6万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.480963333887388
    },
    {
        "question": " 1466万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.387883275287275
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2755903010888865
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.903452128894616
    },
    {
        "question": " 732兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.365555278756384
    },
    {
        "question": " 256億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.47188639467373
    },
    {
        "question": " 6836億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.278476193724728
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.5万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.183158412736315
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.22秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3464707888194853
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.39京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.232601518131577
    },
    {
        "question": " 4286億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.695585404178444
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.624830642678294
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.2億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.847518662852011
    },
    {
        "question": " 9345億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.970598110532723
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.007760667139846
    },
    {
        "question": " 1msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.00090628822506
    },
    {
        "question": " 2847垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.955561400491831
    },
    {
        "question": " 1843兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.328945219922895
    },
    {
        "question": " 209億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7634611640673683
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.57億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0391534739717356
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.337774887344159
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.5億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.549670018081156
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.7万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.620034484151933
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.569e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.911042750461128
    },
    {
        "question": " 108兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09543107197594103
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.54716922804905
    },
    {
        "question": " 170京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.451835088531665
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.3億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7653593874283338
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.070164068238544
    },
    {
        "question": " 634万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.8023582284138326
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.71万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.377694741497318
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.55万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0373722716613343
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.09万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1092039238897917
    },
    {
        "question": " 7961万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.679144360996517
    },
    {
        "question": " 149時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.728106513331852
    },
    {
        "question": " 117万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.346521694673958
    },
    {
        "question": " 215万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1737484258990287
    },
    {
        "question": " 1391億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.365302363628146
    },
    {
        "question": " 4041分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.384637987296282
    },
    {
        "question": " 26分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.193555269157742
    },
    {
        "question": " 9469億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.477512971490908
    },
    {
        "question": " 5406万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.796350419785364
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.44万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1794317591736436
    },
    {
        "question": " 2714秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6554423120215922
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.839052282680122
    },
    {
        "question": " 670兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.889785664792912
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6759101252009134
    },
    {
        "question": " 431兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.85669370808156
    },
    {
        "question": " 121億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.081442443944505
    },
    {
        "question": " 68msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.832457589625458
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.5兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0867073614104652
    },
    {
        "question": " 2996兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5400100582679634
    },
    {
        "question": " 5708億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.200220098903843
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.347666106130774
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.218240288427017
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.194769994164423
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.19万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.913061644518656
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.616e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.321768774096144
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.6垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.958665890587694
    },
    {
        "question": " 169兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6723485012830985
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.5京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8500216196759975
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.4兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.421766152198538
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.2兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.346814045749714
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.0859663780120528
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.9万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.548802552576674
    },
    {
        "question": " 12年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.020465532999867
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.38万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.079158072983869
    },
    {
        "question": " 227万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.735580001389041
    },
    {
        "question": " 778日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.049587639101319
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.27日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.658119983113913
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.45万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8673213852361428
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.683784113588544
    },
    {
        "question": " 117時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.625758359203772
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.832123790394725
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.2億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0938361844693105
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.68万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6665690849244708
    },
    {
        "question": " 73分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08494580239126748
    },
    {
        "question": " 4904分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.468709204427347
    },
    {
        "question": " 834億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4221713956586077
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.7兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.959674128364389
    },
    {
        "question": " 9179秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.40649069713341257
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.401615558559717
    },
    {
        "question": " 110秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.041168980487797
    },
    {
        "question": " 308兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9897184299098742
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.19768012153067
    },
    {
        "question": " 4883億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.132367515099496
    },
    {
        "question": " 423億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.848523934780837
    },
    {
        "question": " 8470億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.927867190889327
    },
    {
        "question": " 547msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.738270668276546
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.337925810807192
    },
    {
        "question": " 321兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0076948907633643
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.9京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.054367003626009
    },
    {
        "question": " 289億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9040242499619078
    },
    {
        "question": " 7446億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.093760728446368
    },
    {
        "question": " 736兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.866630027350858
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.8兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.763381320915038
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.33usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.366509852460978
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6974827377513537
    },
    {
        "question": " 230京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.424409561916304
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.8京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.227840695213565
    },
    {
        "question": " 1836京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.485766458435254
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.7京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9869309710549485
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.2614800706378055
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.27兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.9172967131518
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.897146858206273
    },
    {
        "question": " 3495日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9811964643087201
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.2日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8151759533954435
    },
    {
        "question": " 869日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.097372865689925
    },
    {
        "question": " 4568日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.596213987523988
    },
    {
        "question": " 713万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.910848976510565
    },
    {
        "question": " 8528時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5506367351536996
    },
    {
        "question": " 259時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9689183495544516
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.1億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.678266601306943
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.25874607603174
    },
    {
        "question": " 376万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.797024266103243
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.85京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.086578615768396
    },
    {
        "question": " 2493億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.460272543691411
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.7兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.875040223696077
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.3億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.157625049498852
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.2119936070486146
    },
    {
        "question": " 886京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.448391904914526
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.7億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4186215108412437
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.9億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.888896240074179
    },
    {
        "question": " 280兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.66951577014908
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.1万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4909869586715763
    },
    {
        "question": " 1885msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.275257335845255
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.9msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.590688543291843
    },
    {
        "question": " 506垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.20556327370458
    },
    {
        "question": " 31兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5542271252039237
    },
    {
        "question": " 136兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.575691752281488
    },
    {
        "question": " 234兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.590184156731866
    },
    {
        "question": " 384兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.584130759693767
    },
    {
        "question": " 141万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.1494529695784577
    },
    {
        "question": " 5883垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.27082679449539
    },
    {
        "question": " 3243垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.574490122346678
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.88011207121932
    },
    {
        "question": " 9344京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.192387527966414
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.4兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.95139955277719
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.1億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.612748944732214
    },
    {
        "question": " 567万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.7535447991844153
    },
    {
        "question": " 4024年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1669772347977165
    },
    {
        "question": " 197億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.732974240692423
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.65日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8030486992538652
    },
    {
        "question": " 299日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.634693083502516
    },
    {
        "question": " 629万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8559213591827137
    },
    {
        "question": " 322億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.127539517290385
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.84万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.362698785733948
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.71038372957284
    },
    {
        "question": " 694億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.12047538138628
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.320766015538739
    },
    {
        "question": " 491億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.91301596498914
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.15分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.39639857905259
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.562899943537579
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.21299689274915
    },
    {
        "question": " 9113万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.403365466959642
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.3億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.730630614840806
    },
    {
        "question": " 5340秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.727520723216097
    },
    {
        "question": " 372京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.072306049393859
    },
    {
        "question": " 627億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8607413617277544
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.24兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.794252308188279
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.2万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.939509265222318
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.91万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5917981015141702
    },
    {
        "question": " 481万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.681726709398626
    },
    {
        "question": " 5628msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.75031882264603
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.84987978825939
    },
    {
        "question": " 1219億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14932882162248085
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.8億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1494227427824124
    },
    {
        "question": " 101兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.22664960073617
    },
    {
        "question": " 2143兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.331001708699228
    },
    {
        "question": " 4803万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.68153871754624
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.5万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.397701498516839
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5166258566354855
    },
    {
        "question": " 448京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.714570928069949
    },
    {
        "question": " 234垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.81308714905979
    },
    {
        "question": " 3056億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.706978082064067
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.3億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5942334364878876
    },
    {
        "question": " 1312億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.11801252731392
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.35兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.970694647289159
    },
    {
        "question": " 1056年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.585900993733256
    },
    {
        "question": " 1635万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6511910748164045
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5259519347966466
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.7日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.888166479732976
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.044455068596405
    },
    {
        "question": " 741万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9271733221456255
    },
    {
        "question": " 2495万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.01695191017913
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.050651329665863
    },
    {
        "question": " 1885億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.554677738502868
    },
    {
        "question": " 189万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1177294135776346
    },
    {
        "question": " 3466億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.76173032395143
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.121776600300125
    },
    {
        "question": " 1059兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.526142646160364
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.8億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.937447859663404
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.82億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.208522651134626
    },
    {
        "question": " 157秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.41845618051576383
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.521626908222721
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.7兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.350416233130372
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.227005929531712
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.9億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1150044381741973
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.55万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09981315815693836
    },
    {
        "question": " 780万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.891912768743271
    },
    {
        "question": " 113msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.051728086224148
    },
    {
        "question": " 229京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.861933762480476
    },
    {
        "question": " 219京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.403222392909891
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5601614525842864
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.12億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8364927799979571
    },
    {
        "question": " 1601億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.204399228275921
    },
    {
        "question": " 2175万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.337411167864244
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.467641806244437
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.2垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.301989730544459
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3388289783156164
    },
    {
        "question": " 5006京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.143216930058078
    },
    {
        "question": " 101兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2255935802218403
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.1兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.232232775775985
    },
    {
        "question": " 368万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.5660712038611482
    },
    {
        "question": " 7234億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.859355835851604
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.05万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.343909556643718
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.00872843152448
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.36万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.077657157616705
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.3日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9155362070453106
    },
    {
        "question": " 8206日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.850625012260926
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.4万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6643614868747725
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.6万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.61813061988838
    },
    {
        "question": " 131時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.672973885185968
    },
    {
        "question": " 7720億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.166960244112236
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.6万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.471082385732055
    },
    {
        "question": " 824億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.137852245127746
    },
    {
        "question": " 141分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9274688266794966
    },
    {
        "question": " 378分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.356192915899113
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.972419698136662
    },
    {
        "question": " 688万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.901251907079513
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.74兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.384968662498034
    },
    {
        "question": " 285万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.676843761342373
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3382836545229964
    },
    {
        "question": " 1810秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.257625379368356
    },
    {
        "question": " 14兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.64770418778315
    },
    {
        "question": " 1490兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.236731599800251
    },
    {
        "question": " 2128兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.771621266747117
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.76兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.797356909732097
    },
    {
        "question": " 149万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1721716383135656
    },
    {
        "question": " 6650msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.822846182219888
    },
    {
        "question": " 931京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.470359701747571
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.7垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.631742160259204
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.2億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.42666192855583485
    },
    {
        "question": " 478億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9009155479346536
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.12億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7092346878299614
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.75万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5735989661721828
    },
    {
        "question": " 19万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.278669506079542
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.929e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.27416481555547
    },
    {
        "question": " 32京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.568002530252554
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.625721440632866
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.6兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6135887630728973
    },
    {
        "question": " 795兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.900120614979652
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.034423330573212
    },
    {
        "question": " 1292万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.111111381072744
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.890915352778853
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.34年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.579978637985841
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.7万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.868268865021795
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.7万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.754565592865362
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0631222899965065
    },
    {
        "question": " 430時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2532034682594961
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.860888394696826
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.22億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7876122370001855
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.49万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3847631085595202
    },
    {
        "question": " 444億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.869616854408296
    },
    {
        "question": " 171分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.012225293646118
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.46億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.039705077438815
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.072998326039475
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.8億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.276420990364566
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.380146653941497
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.8秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.9385816351220155
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.1秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.944947923964467
    },
    {
        "question": " 180京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.75538267234618
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.8億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4582892035024597
    },
    {
        "question": " 919万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.40691491805130875
    },
    {
        "question": " 3004億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.699605776698325
    },
    {
        "question": " 545億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7366368621560335
    },
    {
        "question": " 767兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3860378557155761
    },
    {
        "question": " 2874億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5220048619822093
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.670848647044853
    },
    {
        "question": " 1875億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.49486759702915
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.215391039770174
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.8億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.443850623004341
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.22万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.964847622593124
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.101e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.460299688901221
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.78垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.506975761204949
    },
    {
        "question": " 484兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.12861866267267
    },
    {
        "question": " 213兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5499699160506126
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3289625075892455
    },
    {
        "question": " 2959兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.4711773933696
    },
    {
        "question": " 247万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.3932972857389485
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.91年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.634001820224766
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.55万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9878978953431792
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.6万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.057929524119042
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.6万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.09059664867074
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.98日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.713437937865724
    },
    {
        "question": " 170億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.288547227710404
    },
    {
        "question": " 345時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1574513709439183
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.992875678267248
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.480739886312113
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1374653624090691
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3928564025104055
    },
    {
        "question": " 2664万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.203655698861269
    },
    {
        "question": " 331億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0207864586846664
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.09兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.021887878559598
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.8兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.64328480741376
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.7億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.493181277345673
    },
    {
        "question": " 1758兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.746298412916797
    },
    {
        "question": " 8402億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.987858894666058
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.2億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2840734804121388
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.4兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.70438155489325
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2052560167713922
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.326217817043691
    },
    {
        "question": " 60垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.27921494801817
    },
    {
        "question": " 3946兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.659664799619568
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.3兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.209215805690961
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3594029123465905
    },
    {
        "question": " 5201億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.716100663727971
    },
    {
        "question": " 4211万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.62440995371519
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.2万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.326012940094886
    },
    {
        "question": " 2438京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8881859626563324
    },
    {
        "question": " 3660兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6269913673938163
    },
    {
        "question": " 4454京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.092433432984452
    },
    {
        "question": " 115兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2836272078439377
    },
    {
        "question": " 278億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4437696120938726
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.171937274602376
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.35兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.638706337395853
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.807213537251047
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.48億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.979889833704578
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.1万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.206991757065589
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.372341997053201
    },
    {
        "question": " 9855時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.051177071198484914
    },
    {
        "question": " 910億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.5789751865954
    },
    {
        "question": " 112万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.826537855217507
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.904015133971737
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.687938642744253
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.68万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4080810293152646
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7435578868369834
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.5分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.707729747689066
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.4分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.714562088391444
    },
    {
        "question": " 309億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.990978359577122
    },
    {
        "question": " 125兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.159440960924934
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.26万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.30470740027807
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.2万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.886767214348988
    },
    {
        "question": " 379秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.579003905655341
    },
    {
        "question": " 260秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.415652463807087
    },
    {
        "question": " 937京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.473037701168403
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.6京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.48871195811442
    },
    {
        "question": " 1025兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.454558692975064
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.6億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.784909378385319
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.6万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4705611832502528
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.2203683654916
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.01京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1043460931761047
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.275162443227472
    },
    {
        "question": " 1010億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.448120104905859
    },
    {
        "question": " 4277兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.852996801161973
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.2億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7572831391069696
    },
    {
        "question": " 2155万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.33349571333472
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.56usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.8783629548812817
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.9京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4251069076574918
    },
    {
        "question": " 824兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9792434906261049
    },
    {
        "question": " 32兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9491722269167968
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3500930219292515
    },
    {
        "question": " 662京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.820665683968615
    },
    {
        "question": " 3314万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5203117344114747
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.1億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.3251124395540606
    },
    {
        "question": " 306年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.048687727979406
    },
    {
        "question": " 251年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.897927440451522
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.684464924199789
    },
    {
        "question": " 5052日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.083648119129377
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.11日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.644540627922115
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.405012859641245
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.9時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09514231588819588
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.75万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.607745412793169
    },
    {
        "question": " 192時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8391707532665595
    },
    {
        "question": " 135時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.687366708322308
    },
    {
        "question": " 251万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.679023322640393
    },
    {
        "question": " 157億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.038365659154576
    },
    {
        "question": " 148億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.391533287480454
    },
    {
        "question": " 2582万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.19016610075624
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.3兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.850240718233551
    },
    {
        "question": " 5244万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.783186360965461
    },
    {
        "question": " 2488万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8396358408965003
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.9万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.52136683192119
    },
    {
        "question": " 598京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.278103590530899
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.36兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.930571496197284
    },
    {
        "question": " 3665兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.007810942795656
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.4万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9656573167927018
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.75億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.82910554498505
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.8万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.52876623950117
    },
    {
        "question": " 324京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.011793453556446
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.39京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.705479771734377
    },
    {
        "question": " 9538兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.423148129823834
    },
    {
        "question": " 444兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.869278323140532
    },
    {
        "question": " 3818万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.581883976825873
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.3万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.4809787324703247
    },
    {
        "question": " 5678usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.754179880479406
    },
    {
        "question": " 2335垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.869489966882436
    },
    {
        "question": " 2551兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4702838920410133
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4544529061270834
    },
    {
        "question": " 170京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.452349820814578
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.303756295904212
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.296418206441025
    },
    {
        "question": " 929億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.967962622969468
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.66万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.987472702414561
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.24年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.802049342502462
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.82万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4297449770250203
    },
    {
        "question": " 3456日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6969319927555
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.8億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.531043507954573
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.2万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.434318884904107
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.47時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.516024914937909
    },
    {
        "question": " 52兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.995105366757889
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.85億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.835089816621629
    },
    {
        "question": " 378分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7988651352622678
    },
    {
        "question": " 4429分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.424408728464316
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.92万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.06155282106149
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.11億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.994602036304465
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.9兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.997314480612266
    },
    {
        "question": " 18兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.699242789465757
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2771475913768646
    },
    {
        "question": " 2805秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.447987282168931
    },
    {
        "question": " 102秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.00857668050049
    },
    {
        "question": " 1326億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6238745498970155
    },
    {
        "question": " 1171兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1319477103204925
    },
    {
        "question": " 9663万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4288031149210212
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.99兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.822920313164438
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.59億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.662189600065858
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.222131292784796
    },
    {
        "question": " 1360msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.133470801447835
    },
    {
        "question": " 4899兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.191315246071591
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.48垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.457243741519449
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.605779453367622
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.36445502361378224
    },
    {
        "question": " 960兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.982367586649996
    },
    {
        "question": " 4321usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.6355960887903311
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.91垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.273092197224651
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.18京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.919508437047491
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.747437707550839
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.17垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.935208950368155
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.7億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9899839670595789
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.958075958352491
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.128260202564245
    },
    {
        "question": " 712万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.415056757818236
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.7万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.875388001018374
    },
    {
        "question": " 59年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.491688661066702
    },
    {
        "question": " 1096万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.477354287109126
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.800039420690767
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.011988451564322
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.356254071503304
    },
    {
        "question": " 33億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.576369816692238
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.33万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9876179169299597
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.23時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.066168238098908
    },
    {
        "question": " 439兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.922129978819369
    },
    {
        "question": " 8768分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7845565677728583
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.291489504340712
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.8分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.154905740469769
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.1億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.046665689158591
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.4兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.865474048327794
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.722251764279085
    },
    {
        "question": " 244秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6086702348576112
    },
    {
        "question": " 310秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.491247176077247
    },
    {
        "question": " 641秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.806917032287679
    },
    {
        "question": " 1151億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5623812753192714
    },
    {
        "question": " 7782億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.954592804836433
    },
    {
        "question": " 3534万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9919581416932854
    },
    {
        "question": " 325兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.734152864529403
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2578946675974878
    },
    {
        "question": " 3929兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0954440050376997
    },
    {
        "question": " 1002京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.064258563021768
    },
    {
        "question": " 267億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8708379272088385
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.4京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.965669735624536
    },
    {
        "question": " 856億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.932589899915357
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.009890136665059
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.171816859949878
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.971e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.344510683897731
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.74垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.822197660219179
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.3垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.80580433539383
    },
    {
        "question": " 5893京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.992205667714302
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.4京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.496653396762447
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.03億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.6055629431555563
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.4万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.240487438394403
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.24万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9484544100807089
    },
    {
        "question": " 209万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7001290929391075
    },
    {
        "question": " 4003日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.760713533420091
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.97万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.889314555956373
    },
    {
        "question": " 144万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.214645864650512
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9338724990769602
    },
    {
        "question": " 886時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.725739456875604
    },
    {
        "question": " 8323時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4765778269392875
    },
    {
        "question": " 135時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.686665254835784
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.33時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.924431465184565
    },
    {
        "question": " 4950億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.97399507175346
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8652531597539992
    },
    {
        "question": " 672万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.048993513485204
    },
    {
        "question": " 4636万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.444333270608206
    },
    {
        "question": " 7834億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3951905527268
    },
    {
        "question": " 108万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.095116726291978
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.912538082091123
    },
    {
        "question": " 1648万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.438924188702074
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.8秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.411066793712322
    },
    {
        "question": " 174秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.241536275412562
    },
    {
        "question": " 5835京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.267263562680231
    },
    {
        "question": " 124兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.156736427765265
    },
    {
        "question": " 110億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.486541659904617
    },
    {
        "question": " 1415万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.37254874779812
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.260318473444314
    },
    {
        "question": " 3143msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.4973366020985015
    },
    {
        "question": " 1664京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.722349255479787
    },
    {
        "question": " 2272京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.419875415480327
    },
    {
        "question": " 2738億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8811846430450663
    },
    {
        "question": " 811億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1309237570413693
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.35兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.970671410163316
    },
    {
        "question": " 9936億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.997232968019564
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.2usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.435323069041078
    },
    {
        "question": " 12垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.580107709874826
    },
    {
        "question": " 8647京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.000375640037513
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.4垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.967273589238532
    },
    {
        "question": " 6018兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.001311805365555
    },
    {
        "question": " 114兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0582471691701
    },
    {
        "question": " 2993万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.4760914250743673
    },
    {
        "question": " 5864億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.768163840251205
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.67万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.231597789993437
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.8万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9531394945858533
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.8日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.24213579118278
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.351418189226921
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.7億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.847435215982939
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0156706085194926
    },
    {
        "question": " 126万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.878302107146067
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.54時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.105407485994139
    },
    {
        "question": " 341兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.812473438522641
    },
    {
        "question": " 9466億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.817831646456561
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4373102211880084
    },
    {
        "question": " 556分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.523557865295732
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.7億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8752608538349658
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.1兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.745671742398605
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.546308774227354
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.1万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.200105180612138
    },
    {
        "question": " 5132兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2115187776906025
    },
    {
        "question": " 1242億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1576101151854488
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.07京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.930756323660628
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.7億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.595937526769541
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.328887948235
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.9万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.868456625267555
    },
    {
        "question": " 525垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.22094612721754
    },
    {
        "question": " 119兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.138027562186725
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.610942920962676
    },
    {
        "question": " 122兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.306994441122708
    },
    {
        "question": " 339億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.52980157002607
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.5万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.6949577278667114
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.43京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03665755317852848
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.81垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.512441270190825
    },
    {
        "question": " 8619兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3791488809847667
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.4京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.627043895057675
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.071494072779726
    },
    {
        "question": " 133万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.12373034311454534
    },
    {
        "question": " 2466万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.391965933810741
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6206078073493475
    },
    {
        "question": " 6706年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.768941890597388
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6890617241707195
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.539360406444602
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3597265420887705
    },
    {
        "question": " 282万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5080578177324977
    },
    {
        "question": " 1890万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.896153239479091
    },
    {
        "question": " 2368時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.15246136446473
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.808360389478906
    },
    {
        "question": " 4944兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.97341047069014
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.93億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.435852575279561
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4462479087149154
    },
    {
        "question": " 4775万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.457097384356166
    },
    {
        "question": " 1466億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.667311400558557
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2683523913460855
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.6億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8579960280059264
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.9万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.165902506452424
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.7万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.989755759507924
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.197139924014008
    },
    {
        "question": " 1055億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5242667092053233
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.39133446882863
    },
    {
        "question": " 2257億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.797304887181292
    },
    {
        "question": " 229兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.581450687455005
    },
    {
        "question": " 1134万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.054459770637125
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.517374310316849
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.2兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6991948501586425
    },
    {
        "question": " 1987億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7419796250217423
    },
    {
        "question": " 1438億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3795217577171788
    },
    {
        "question": " 647兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.81082662592553
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.4万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.828686182289095
    },
    {
        "question": " 667usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.823857001945656
    },
    {
        "question": " 3043垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.984523353243285
    },
    {
        "question": " 2599京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.478350058821741
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.37垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.366463528141743
    },
    {
        "question": " 6303京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.021406139216959
    },
    {
        "question": " 571兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.756799541531235
    },
    {
        "question": " 50億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6989040665495256
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.98兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.776651349081014
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.1年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.362364717813486
    },
    {
        "question": " 9447年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.69592548153524
    },
    {
        "question": " 2697億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.868600484700771
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.355884677812462
    },
    {
        "question": " 575億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.817441283851082
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.821650556519704
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.04万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.261656156706215
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.4億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9455514240834866
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.3万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.656891241517857
    },
    {
        "question": " 1811分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.479787738367615
    },
    {
        "question": " 7807分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.670657988579082
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.4兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.831361599203843
    },
    {
        "question": " 430兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.69669561699038
    },
    {
        "question": " 149億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.617287046277096
    },
    {
        "question": " 1777万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.471426110181666
    },
    {
        "question": " 113万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.054786944714282
    },
    {
        "question": " 829京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.419755923036726
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.260128175763007
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.7兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.189504975295348
    },
    {
        "question": " 1032億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.235690719935414
    },
    {
        "question": " 5038万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7022396558503035
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.97万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.599170362244844
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.219807324447314
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7173493170150156
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.4兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6128005131472976
    },
    {
        "question": " 593京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.216752078461814
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.28兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.01962034821266
    },
    {
        "question": " 366万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5633929622012301
    },
    {
        "question": " 570万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.755638790640563
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.9usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.714899278099516
    },
    {
        "question": " 114垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.556609434056126
    },
    {
        "question": " 522京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.780935662895304
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.05兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2919088624676158
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.1京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1415730167875076
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.1京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.463798278068936
    },
    {
        "question": " 4725万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6743637820740964
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.91兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.996069994161594
    },
    {
        "question": " 4680年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.232518176534036
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.11万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.85173588703907
    },
    {
        "question": " 125年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.818190959742606
    },
    {
        "question": " 792億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.336419170795065
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.32日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.015239752213885
    },
    {
        "question": " 366日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.722070749209063
    },
    {
        "question": " 6444万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8666756996080864
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.869994036956592
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.05434614656038
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.86時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.243347812914212
    },
    {
        "question": " 2038億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.588548132903397
    },
    {
        "question": " 2650万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.264943550296438
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.86万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.808345102730885
    },
    {
        "question": " 2863万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.234955535293613
    },
    {
        "question": " 1446分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.938191806364979
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.3兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.019575315992908
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.2万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.40987446420637785
    },
    {
        "question": " 557億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.189717756119491
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4928701727754365
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.2万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.709064816486096
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.51秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.654213253147475
    },
    {
        "question": " 133兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6244645478828064
    },
    {
        "question": " 402億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.667743887175067
    },
    {
        "question": " 5097兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.15099179486877
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.6兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.890607952340027
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.6億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.556393516420261
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.236989861190948
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.72京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.441903002075576
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.99兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5392665458337762
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.3億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20213245181965211
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4057493447886138
    },
    {
        "question": " 9718万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9875895162122792
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.09331700218192
    },
    {
        "question": " 1324usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.121821278025367
    },
    {
        "question": " 1039垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5176418252887895
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3905718040372315
    },
    {
        "question": " 1178兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5148182397193075
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.89兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6833342883467595
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.071218055451215
    },
    {
        "question": " 8562兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.932597200368457
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.12万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.6145283773307229
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.6万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.18111220288621
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.740665473757127
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.29億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.955147031894836
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.85943770816658
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.86日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.393421878854912
    },
    {
        "question": " 115日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.996245180512965
    },
    {
        "question": " 2385億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.434929991480183
    },
    {
        "question": " 403億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.224939833338416
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.69万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.123700353180801
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.79384742039307
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.62億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.161474396127094
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.95万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.793587391264072
    },
    {
        "question": " 5916億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.993875865479197
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.109859899858446
    },
    {
        "question": " 176分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.024421517634938
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.917143263352056
    },
    {
        "question": " 239万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4420726653898075
    },
    {
        "question": " 25兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.842231688245525
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4193988175714907
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.7万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.861355767490917
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.786339445501541
    },
    {
        "question": " 5231兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.782093955643643
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5022186746383888
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.47851197152552
    },
    {
        "question": " 2097億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.321649413376644
    },
    {
        "question": " 155msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.191340438371258
    },
    {
        "question": " 401垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.104117316845816
    },
    {
        "question": " 304兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5459824820463917
    },
    {
        "question": " 532京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.169343044551411
    },
    {
        "question": " 2125億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5492521739221496
    },
    {
        "question": " 114万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.057876709228619205
    },
    {
        "question": " 251万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3999508816185164
    },
    {
        "question": " 959usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.982026970776971
    },
    {
        "question": " 202京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.806393052818328
    },
    {
        "question": " 112垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.110977504171302
    },
    {
        "question": " 598兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2203908948991913
    },
    {
        "question": " 313兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.717134243599489
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.1兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7332520077628715
    },
    {
        "question": " 3042万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.4832087689483353
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.93兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.899054530623912
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.6年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.074901127959728
    },
    {
        "question": " 1162万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.502770481053359
    },
    {
        "question": " 7329万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.245247417595959
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.6日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8447494094868055
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.30085048673379
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.7億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.995713854762407
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.25万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9724985737699394
    },
    {
        "question": " 372万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.349271018689384
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.93時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.397076545633323
    },
    {
        "question": " 899億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2332973448284985
    },
    {
        "question": " 9万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7957131576307117
    },
    {
        "question": " 2096万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.543288224924502
    },
    {
        "question": " 3791分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.35695187802183
    },
    {
        "question": " 2377億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.877257249936148
    },
    {
        "question": " 153兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.247451660133912
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.9億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.105726334934705
    },
    {
        "question": " 6789万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.053640023901108
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.36万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.526842264966963
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.24兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2204203611107642
    },
    {
        "question": " 144兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.221095142729721
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.7兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2808895422399385
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.19兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.725903064456966
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.075151183675828
    },
    {
        "question": " 128msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.107223318409192
    },
    {
        "question": " 765兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.384749829921541
    },
    {
        "question": " 9826京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.055876205372815
    },
    {
        "question": " 2170億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.78022256428092
    },
    {
        "question": " 103億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2366603235561247
    },
    {
        "question": " 674万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8285616154285491
    },
    {
        "question": " 1872usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.2722517273695413
    },
    {
        "question": " 2427usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.38513063858869
    },
    {
        "question": " 219垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.841491963760927
    },
    {
        "question": " 6450兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.873090325661374
    },
    {
        "question": " 3202兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9491343977962003
    },
    {
        "question": " 139兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.365620091642554
    },
    {
        "question": " 604億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7807046172090424
    },
    {
        "question": " 1514兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.180164114544299
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.193311779354474
    },
    {
        "question": " 125万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.65819557196498
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.0280825715815
    },
    {
        "question": " 6775万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.26861563244975
    },
    {
        "question": " 3712万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.949840671151819
    },
    {
        "question": " 7794日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.828269709853524
    },
    {
        "question": " 1602万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2622484578260815
    },
    {
        "question": " 5014万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3199808954854735
    },
    {
        "question": " 1861万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.04787006469957
    },
    {
        "question": " 350万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8229296061594416
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9685122995357085
    },
    {
        "question": " 62万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0143304806330695
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.5分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0214683508193096
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.151223609451332
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.1分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.211330763450876
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.98億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4034612062056573
    },
    {
        "question": " 174億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.304926215152571
    },
    {
        "question": " 149億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.615466382971152
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.37億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1444160264376935
    },
    {
        "question": " 97秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.986649992437094
    },
    {
        "question": " 1956億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7925296945987226
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.83兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.747242744475127
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.2億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0891830039726607
    },
    {
        "question": " 863億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.157833397209908
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.244970054227069
    },
    {
        "question": " 179万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.253463938235871
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.277160504985194
    },
    {
        "question": " 7642京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.384391877193403
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.38兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4402534022580082
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.44京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.091303408843409
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.18兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.843053015982469
    },
    {
        "question": " 220兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.34297714382287
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.6億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.441606098020774
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.36万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.971354289748401
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.881e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.775669247926723
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.450193946718443
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.9兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.114581170263057
    },
    {
        "question": " 4887兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.910922353993545
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.7京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.63048741776998
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.1億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.892857792678072
    },
    {
        "question": " 816万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.9117354586021835
    },
    {
        "question": " 2303年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.924595392608712
    },
    {
        "question": " 111年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.767430103465042
    },
    {
        "question": " 740億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.306647457026127
    },
    {
        "question": " 2073万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.696758023203833
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.21752653859181
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.4時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15581979344984953
    },
    {
        "question": " 113万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.610950430701061
    },
    {
        "question": " 552時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.297857608007703
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.751263340658916
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.090113374072762
    },
    {
        "question": " 155万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.411793343395312
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.21万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.571030075703859
    },
    {
        "question": " 4013分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.381596001234405
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.8039497495265415
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.23兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.127974814379643
    },
    {
        "question": " 316兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.563548068455715
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.74万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2023601562857134
    },
    {
        "question": " 3025万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.70261389512328
    },
    {
        "question": " 613万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.787275412285672
    },
    {
        "question": " 601億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2800876979868461
    },
    {
        "question": " 620兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.856019967213315
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.1億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2702152899516723
    },
    {
        "question": " 747億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0953162877316736
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5726414338939945
    },
    {
        "question": " 262万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.418003345720864
    },
    {
        "question": " 177垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.748814854522857
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.68京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.888217049285557
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.68717732222953
    },
    {
        "question": " 374億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.79452434843079
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.2兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.570571020806608
    },
    {
        "question": " 490万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.689825480951888
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.07usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.486747112408662
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.5京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2897997440860065
    },
    {
        "question": " 6581京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.88180062501778
    },
    {
        "question": " 51京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.150872249003692
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.65京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.889416743051665
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.89京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.897211955729712
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.1兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.532409085883724
    },
    {
        "question": " 4301億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.633541186870646
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.1年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.437790135253055
    },
    {
        "question": " 7058年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.569344338793632
    },
    {
        "question": " 2648日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8606554550346868
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.44万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9172642026095925
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.98461440382282
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.1日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.763274181578703
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.23億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.852322477066796
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.45万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3559271897085763
    },
    {
        "question": " 157万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.973829267641167
    },
    {
        "question": " 3135時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.05254200876659
    },
    {
        "question": " 151時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.735892058443726
    },
    {
        "question": " 8761万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2219199698918524
    },
    {
        "question": " 330万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3599127232860404
    },
    {
        "question": " 136億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.355952781432812
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.005307174988906
    },
    {
        "question": " 111分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.82406955461348
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.003718338494597
    },
    {
        "question": " 750億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9386801157223035
    },
    {
        "question": " 4433秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09040215814705266
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.84億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.675123775844616
    },
    {
        "question": " 6万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.778129849142497
    },
    {
        "question": " 8949億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.452969632966662
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.32億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4292175246565988
    },
    {
        "question": " 373万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.015571410343121483
    },
    {
        "question": " 5549万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9660317852904217
    },
    {
        "question": " 2003万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.30170935035893
    },
    {
        "question": " 3391msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.530364806664204
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.87msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.588258901325476
    },
    {
        "question": " 251京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.900024472730368
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.8兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.733294344540369
    },
    {
        "question": " 113兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.497660681867686
    },
    {
        "question": " 6524兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.036369073801634
    },
    {
        "question": " 2958億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.470958564760959
    },
    {
        "question": " 1901usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.27907297602014824
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.8usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.553670265282078
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.067e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.529524442547685
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.47垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.714120586453105
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.41兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.36873826376005225
    },
    {
        "question": " 2576京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.632749473348662
    },
    {
        "question": " 7425億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8706747056067385
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.068906236108125
    },
    {
        "question": " 1164億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.065773746441577
    },
    {
        "question": " 109年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.600880470098511
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.9年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.339034202642661
    },
    {
        "question": " 266年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.145385787883821
    },
    {
        "question": " 1983日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7349630205433644
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.02億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.984778133719082
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3265765012407975
    },
    {
        "question": " 1306日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.052332604503457
    },
    {
        "question": " 106億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.084414508600966
    },
    {
        "question": " 699万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.46420823823458
    },
    {
        "question": " 256時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.187185734938112
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.693988434276509
    },
    {
        "question": " 114時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.611374652843782
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.74億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.267890051798666
    },
    {
        "question": " 1636万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.055413578462437
    },
    {
        "question": " 917億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.18402223772764
    },
    {
        "question": " 1299分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.891920274450933
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.912154724200827
    },
    {
        "question": " 3039億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9839089430630104
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.073768815677358
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.1兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.80682896321744
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4758173500322775
    },
    {
        "question": " 359秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.5555595486286755
    },
    {
        "question": " 103秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.014155511035138
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.6京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.433607416253104
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.48京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.937204401415357
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.660967014910128
    },
    {
        "question": " 7997万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.124776813080674
    },
    {
        "question": " 284万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4529487975622275
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.23msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.50901849989261
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.9兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3459279748826316
    },
    {
        "question": " 303兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.544407207003565
    },
    {
        "question": " 2756兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.883934670423882
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.22京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.015585671698593
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.01181117365528
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.03億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.955827899679692
    },
    {
        "question": " 4935京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1944955619223823
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.316557991642782
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.7兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8539074173147332
    },
    {
        "question": " 2237京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.571476918379018
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0738511138355005
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.6億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.9220546234847022
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.25億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.720342225744636
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.120066100528523
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.91万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.892209659444152
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.8億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.925901208344168
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6165054499450204
    },
    {
        "question": " 3兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.534199151259728
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9831297614897165
    },
    {
        "question": " 354万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.327285054374396
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.1万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.97243497900828
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.45時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.292367587267118
    },
    {
        "question": " 138万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4185391070468403
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1057675344536495
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.46万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7609242347020535
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.24分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.288455442170585
    },
    {
        "question": " 624億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2965172523764985
    },
    {
        "question": " 1832億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.326539836965239
    },
    {
        "question": " 316万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.943679187596099
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.1秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.21811153943724793
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.04秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6062956274437665
    },
    {
        "question": " 3969億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0998425611423857
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.83京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.647139060094325
    },
    {
        "question": " 148億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.612896814656156
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.4億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.044093743606707
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.2万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.401585073534739
    },
    {
        "question": " 3991msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.601084015742973
    },
    {
        "question": " 6415msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.80719220955018
    },
    {
        "question": " 300京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.978024310971105
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.423713611425363
    },
    {
        "question": " 575兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.20368819708247
    },
    {
        "question": " 17億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.452576650199161
    },
    {
        "question": " 5473億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.738233239787377
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.95兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.694705073125077
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.56万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.409052028462587
    },
    {
        "question": " 227京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8566278493516697
    },
    {
        "question": " 1364垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.198284690696456
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.7垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.205126269407726
    },
    {
        "question": " 332兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.742337588226703
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.25兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5116959577842732
    },
    {
        "question": " 2945兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.469052622693003
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.2075410084685756
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.36万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.533772554438056
    },
    {
        "question": " 528年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.664824719411202
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.7億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.00600866835821
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.7日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.313178588745902
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.222014445389189
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.215706054843661
    },
    {
        "question": " 167億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.843077744591856
    },
    {
        "question": " 4162兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.89868942655333
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.08兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.691601502380724
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.5分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16898188740949838
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.8分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6154530793883346
    },
    {
        "question": " 216億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8361962038706237
    },
    {
        "question": " 230億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4248991954094
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.4万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9670456263108715
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.83億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.673965298311923
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.89秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.838024800533592
    },
    {
        "question": " 167兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.72366384370327
    },
    {
        "question": " 5977兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.83998352652313
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.5億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1018902952011462
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.7兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.762795135283833
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0346804556430986
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.6msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.966746180240217
    },
    {
        "question": " 4584兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1624756715300784
    },
    {
        "question": " 352兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.610324735024916
    },
    {
        "question": " 330京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.96273655912666
    },
    {
        "question": " 736兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0889728075863845
    },
    {
        "question": " 9012万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.954814337312648
    },
    {
        "question": " 2472usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.39305025186693987
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.7万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.922850217167756
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.91京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.45085920583659345
    },
    {
        "question": " 60垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.84168461365362
    },
    {
        "question": " 1986京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.74172659643578
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.241746310551235
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.24兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3507749138218457
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.78億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.576997573630928
    },
    {
        "question": " 3576億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.553449179512098
    },
    {
        "question": " 463年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.227611907475919
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.4万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.744810503679771
    },
    {
        "question": " 9362日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4090643627558475
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.5万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.332260543013315
    },
    {
        "question": " 783日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.830058644350163
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3430748994970212
    },
    {
        "question": " 150時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.797106336727843
    },
    {
        "question": " 2013時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.860250936598523
    },
    {
        "question": " 116兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.344367828442396
    },
    {
        "question": " 3879万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.430390067210443
    },
    {
        "question": " 140万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.367113829197658
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.19万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.569905127422029
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.869956750863512
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.809118568160725
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.02億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5439605056882884
    },
    {
        "question": " 261万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.859768125361357
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.372798352010758
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.267214704089718
    },
    {
        "question": " 244秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.386931527105931
    },
    {
        "question": " 103京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.512335949439062
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.07億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0208973980828084
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.7兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.27446669969484
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.77万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.21181067302164625
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.5万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5372560098808106
    },
    {
        "question": " 465msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.667007866360303
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.770084369421549
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.077875554188234
    },
    {
        "question": " 113兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.497645210185301
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.7京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.990775547856444
    },
    {
        "question": " 6787億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.831647601365955
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.16億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.961894723192355
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.6京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4286463722026022
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.5京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.034190543217341
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.1兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8073240502224899
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.06兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9261591835101288
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.121322133671261
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.953053683229493
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.06万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.4850937508425521
    },
    {
        "question": " 15万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.738961068989524
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.52万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.756613712175257
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.09年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.45719753316088
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.59億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.185378472324308
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.37日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.686240174355727
    },
    {
        "question": " 2724日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.37177043504121
    },
    {
        "question": " 932億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.026992340976018
    },
    {
        "question": " 1964億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.912983399462409
    },
    {
        "question": " 7557万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.656483372295927
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.652289157030821
    },
    {
        "question": " 76時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.437310530307382
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.4億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.19003280879336
    },
    {
        "question": " 11兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.881985596699938
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.9億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.902372807138173
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.47万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.171167294262587
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.754802574643813
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.1万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.027597470303131
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.1億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.806797946488919
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.36億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8611262032627875
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.2411923065089008
    },
    {
        "question": " 120京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.579565954768837
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.076732343847674
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.9億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9986704468866865
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.9億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.15575852757843
    },
    {
        "question": " 8607億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.934872453952051
    },
    {
        "question": " 2499兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8989981222852303
    },
    {
        "question": " 2245億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4148129258222333
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.5京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.19599486765725
    },
    {
        "question": " 415億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8399385285347787
    },
    {
        "question": " 4195万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6227529902700788
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.434521299037423
    },
    {
        "question": " 7632usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.882623898543971
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.43京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30931410439555385
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.2京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.781037860161045
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.3垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.408991026660058
    },
    {
        "question": " 5726兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9796821571511245
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.5京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.585317542750204
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.3兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.368007656554263
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.019532324772255
    },
    {
        "question": " 142年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.713835785609891
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.7万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.317533489341294
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.67年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3899699154124425
    },
    {
        "question": " 599億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.215418984673544
    },
    {
        "question": " 335万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.905638609801437
    },
    {
        "question": " 845億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.984302960570207
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.643019218076774
    },
    {
        "question": " 3331時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.300690450711041
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.52時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9575547670647717
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.53時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.535365649229586
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.64兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.839890006895944
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.3億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.838514269806261
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4727460468174796
    },
    {
        "question": " 360万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.334358375610012
    },
    {
        "question": " 568兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.255186512808672
    },
    {
        "question": " 2777万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5070329006170144
    },
    {
        "question": " 664万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.266100369571665
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.97万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9981783436716625
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.102682083893953
    },
    {
        "question": " 499兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.199161676829128
    },
    {
        "question": " 491億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7543642128703203
    },
    {
        "question": " 956兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.424280730719717
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.1万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8851316515236207
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.08兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.70547253307131
    },
    {
        "question": " 112万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.049288791778306
    },
    {
        "question": " 2531msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.403245840889564
    },
    {
        "question": " 128垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.607900390377718
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.18京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.976082238231056
    },
    {
        "question": " 516兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1561086425551075
    },
    {
        "question": " 487億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.909651928689337
    },
    {
        "question": " 516万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7126386487224723
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.6万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.8607192483533304
    },
    {
        "question": " 1usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.000818610405421
    },
    {
        "question": " 541京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2346894788613336
    },
    {
        "question": " 2680兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4915786356494398
    },
    {
        "question": " 69兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2824464457518658
    },
    {
        "question": " 291京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.68613132070023
    },
    {
        "question": " 1573兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.196757644020099
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.5兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.398560813166427
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.3億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.955723119826525
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.1億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.854907848534822
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.1万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.439973324598121
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.78億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.047921284386709
    },
    {
        "question": " 469億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.291040510049697
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.88時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3673913487233156
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.752674886957367
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.5兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8865499529671625
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.65兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.725094001618643
    },
    {
        "question": " 1190万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.297512158543492
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.848033118048297
    },
    {
        "question": " 4208万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12530879807370443
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.74兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8227392410256025
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.5万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.155137750482271
    },
    {
        "question": " 734秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0872909638430672
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.0275274911192085
    },
    {
        "question": " 4473億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.151769295349826
    },
    {
        "question": " 164億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2771775784293915
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.87億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3395580317579023
    },
    {
        "question": " 4133億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.838073434206309
    },
    {
        "question": " 4855msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.686151621897414
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.84msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.584436484263792
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.17京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.214952624904328
    },
    {
        "question": " 3163億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5635899393343535
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.7兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.405876306085572
    },
    {
        "question": " 146億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.385138650175047
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.6兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.456600792456749
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.75億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.439874541840823
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.153000609636215
    },
    {
        "question": " 496垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.196671019756169
    },
    {
        "question": " 388京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.652608339913709
    },
    {
        "question": " 191兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7247223355948815
    },
    {
        "question": " 611億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.008097124772702413
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3851191308693975
    },
    {
        "question": " 1061億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.025694364265795
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.19万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.714869966840925
    },
    {
        "question": " 2344年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.932316544901663
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.1年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.645587366529311
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.67万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.00217080079815
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3933626319207555
    },
    {
        "question": " 139日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.300233557576016
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.096364240051335
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.8万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0020856640158893
    },
    {
        "question": " 488万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.308584517868492
    },
    {
        "question": " 10万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.778952884803221
    },
    {
        "question": " 3161時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.056177419849376
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.427384828593293
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9618159249094793
    },
    {
        "question": " 959万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.203819062678175
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.1分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.141019649419281
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.71兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.071110227311713
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.8億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.673879600287122
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.5万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3956632300416714
    },
    {
        "question": " 995秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2198709220249149
    },
    {
        "question": " 6055秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.782140307563587
    },
    {
        "question": " 1892秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.277013969117307
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.9兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.991048437115408
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.52兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.993779005723962
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.9億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.873438361484233
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.5兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.610195323701571
    },
    {
        "question": " 5157msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7124139060869805
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.339601573929604
    },
    {
        "question": " 311msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.492526071013021
    },
    {
        "question": " 838垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.424463657576338
    },
    {
        "question": " 8364京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.985896558938242
    },
    {
        "question": " 548京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.182680859576731
    },
    {
        "question": " 56京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.970166594777535
    },
    {
        "question": " 374兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.572930430864835
    },
    {
        "question": " 1532億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.185239256157066
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.052853892407895
    },
    {
        "question": " 3047京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.985141299883126
    },
    {
        "question": " 437京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.704185957289056
    },
    {
        "question": " 4678京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.113741180082492
    },
    {
        "question": " 439京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.864301201688367
    },
    {
        "question": " 522兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.718085111192429
    },
    {
        "question": " 391兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.59197432892422
    },
    {
        "question": " 41億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.612297507295697
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.58年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.223010423866822
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.31万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.462894892604517
    },
    {
        "question": " 2340年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.089895529038655
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.72年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.486348759361395
    },
    {
        "question": " 1819万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.697590431933866
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.06日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0847181719106986
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1771704290591063
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.61万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.919055675379365
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.1億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.649814253957505
    },
    {
        "question": " 269時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.049986709464985
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.7万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.437846593891903
    },
    {
        "question": " 1555兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.470988705978106
    },
    {
        "question": " 1850億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.108736026798955
    },
    {
        "question": " 404億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.828559943868203
    },
    {
        "question": " 672分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.605228246381818
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.899980313364267
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.829811434241256
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1710800424580039
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.4億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.027770547429094
    },
    {
        "question": " 243億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.607955027588396
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.44秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.537044120466857
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.468447927755992
    },
    {
        "question": " 661京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.3216676146343
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.7兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.616314779434852
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.5億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2397649703864415
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.28533248255845
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.27万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7973540790000886
    },
    {
        "question": " 689msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.838240559186788
    },
    {
        "question": " 1571msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.196224507386892
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.9京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.278958629298868
    },
    {
        "question": " 931兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0325633749595635
    },
    {
        "question": " 453兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.099820748266016
    },
    {
        "question": " 7930万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12113895061054869
    },
    {
        "question": " 2033億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.308144890124561
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.106051895594401
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.31e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.470143659050578
    },
    {
        "question": " 997垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.062193650503128
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.6京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.029844404575541
    },
    {
        "question": " 110京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.261385985626198
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.3兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.348224064097083
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.3兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.594207711069357
    },
    {
        "question": " 887億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.948097021701872
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.8年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.249225905045814
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.15年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.997168758155734
    },
    {
        "question": " 4097万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.050195805210985
    },
    {
        "question": " 354万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.707547427960016
    },
    {
        "question": " 8781億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.001031862102915
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.4時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.32243496052054565
    },
    {
        "question": " 2128万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.10602717940026
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.761700180637058
    },
    {
        "question": " 164万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49341082639162037
    },
    {
        "question": " 8318分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7616790858894118
    },
    {
        "question": " 151万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.402259902539363
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.5分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.232367921629404
    },
    {
        "question": " 148億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.671199937850688
    },
    {
        "question": " 421億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.687604135555395
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.1億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.950692195801713
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.9億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.902063157942704
    },
    {
        "question": " 121秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.084090377875507
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.105519029123679
    },
    {
        "question": " 110京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.543808621690732
    },
    {
        "question": " 263億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.484150392857385
    },
    {
        "question": " 5804億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.207399779902211
    },
    {
        "question": " 4657万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8899102789348663
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.172473767607326
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.1006044289204535
    },
    {
        "question": " 652msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.814371833780562
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.729939905899906
    },
    {
        "question": " 495京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.757889964285201
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.83京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.209194069046595
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.4京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.62596186065001
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.005747224444848
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.5億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.835663464816469
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.9京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4449837303586488
    },
    {
        "question": " 528兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7862579208662102
    },
    {
        "question": " 3240兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9542032270764818
    },
    {
        "question": " 143京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.376277244508714
    },
    {
        "question": " 3429兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.535189384558603
    },
    {
        "question": " 286億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.455806060634767
    },
    {
        "question": " 5807万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.763926426821337
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.980049114453186
    },
    {
        "question": " 191年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.778910703192734
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.823864707994355
    },
    {
        "question": " 882万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.325528721211953
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.31万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9581078735437085
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.096003285893602
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.8日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.465314893732723
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.542066429641642
    },
    {
        "question": " 262万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.03814575519777
    },
    {
        "question": " 21時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1013176743977877
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.693228227079338
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.77億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.109894324659206
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.4億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.713494095568971
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.1億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.097528841397622
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.808873986808377
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.77分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.456318936032925
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.7兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.053625018558827
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.37億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9863181968291492
    },
    {
        "question": " 2540万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.848608936015868
    },
    {
        "question": " 7685秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1074965121796243
    },
    {
        "question": " 1679秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.22493367429958
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.49京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.240879090778977
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.162619651354375
    },
    {
        "question": " 9123兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.403817164911231
    },
    {
        "question": " 6553万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0383174525707366
    },
    {
        "question": " 910万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9589341138844003
    },
    {
        "question": " 320垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.005803271630759
    },
    {
        "question": " 888億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.011678292117429656
    },
    {
        "question": " 196京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.735514942106951
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.8億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1450189498072794
    },
    {
        "question": " 568万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7543908169854974
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.1922496510082592
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.233605160468498
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.731e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.739516006821788
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2076071718978207
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4626752408010948
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.28兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0199859398513595
    },
    {
        "question": " 7895兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.897346887464558
    },
    {
        "question": " 223万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.34805946608494565
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.1972585851512516
    },
    {
        "question": " 6186年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3536840431461385
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.47億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.24827242653752
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4622340935835465
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5716231251261945
    },
    {
        "question": " 4196万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.68029728811198
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.4時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1302590032653539
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.5万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.276417196682775
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.3万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22515226443958647
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.871139072477757
    },
    {
        "question": " 27億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6524655862375015
    },
    {
        "question": " 109分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.813972004307435
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.28分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.696342303448057
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.8兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.482484973277234
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.8万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0217533342673901
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.691555842976829
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.348829447360141
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.6秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.629799067748634
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.697601346411819
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.370182847877693
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.28兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.959657522945847
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.92億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5054630782341825
    },
    {
        "question": " 1096億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.039805025407157
    },
    {
        "question": " 30万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.476581388502558
    },
    {
        "question": " 117msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.06797870399979
    },
    {
        "question": " 114垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.55948323038579
    },
    {
        "question": " 388京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.652551062646471
    },
    {
        "question": " 2303兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.806049076335783
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.87兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.679929376988974
    },
    {
        "question": " 3561兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.551533867331253
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.65万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.8229389462242473
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5608965161639912
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.2京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.813557746097697
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.28兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3619813399180005
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.48251771166756
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.234172200013583
    },
    {
        "question": " 699万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.8441862521414467
    },
    {
        "question": " 1311万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.117504715267066
    },
    {
        "question": " 7554年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.440474800293404
    },
    {
        "question": " 5388年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.452100484416913
    },
    {
        "question": " 500億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.136648434527283
    },
    {
        "question": " 864万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.31679325824635
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.183642566810445
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.041035704549951
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.10513479809596
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.416555907272938
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.811231589345523
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.613950196482294
    },
    {
        "question": " 1039億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.295837580264896
    },
    {
        "question": " 6453分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6514047997007977
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4921907235531195
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.52万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3246001012852435
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.05万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.559654420840753
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.679267683085236
    },
    {
        "question": " 6024億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8433783534740815
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.7万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.267918136554764
    },
    {
        "question": " 137万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.358352832119953
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.02秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7006219187541034
    },
    {
        "question": " 5807京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.26511837373468
    },
    {
        "question": " 115兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.125764397984451
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8306780175513415
    },
    {
        "question": " 193兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.508505437402107
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.4万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.795518941341053
    },
    {
        "question": " 2163兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.836216865189142
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.69兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.049977173227999
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.01京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.14342894520242
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.28京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.083724997333949
    },
    {
        "question": " 5080兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.705871912392569
    },
    {
        "question": " 8330usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.9206329607802011
    },
    {
        "question": " 743usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.870794194056636
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.802e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.333856637084676
    },
    {
        "question": " 1209垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.1458347187573
    },
    {
        "question": " 508京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.149846795014735
    },
    {
        "question": " 118兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2941936033763977
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.100676687158691
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.2791129142210265
    },
    {
        "question": " 2068億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.315635137560843
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.8万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.920764304185409
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.84年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7089637136906335
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.449756739853198
    },
    {
        "question": " 553万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.180552270156163
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.410125279966064
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.637596058378001
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.3日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6715993261414965
    },
    {
        "question": " 80日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.839720346644645
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.7兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.95908459635091
    },
    {
        "question": " 197億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.914166135352568
    },
    {
        "question": " 4000万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.380256082671162
    },
    {
        "question": " 281時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.004631863895048
    },
    {
        "question": " 125万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.37461262241041515
    },
    {
        "question": " 169億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.070458301898261
    },
    {
        "question": " 2265分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5768813902802659
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.747291632511548
    },
    {
        "question": " 510万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.770869194183764
    },
    {
        "question": " 587億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2125993481471635
    },
    {
        "question": " 3641万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.783014674665441
    },
    {
        "question": " 192兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.785625933362282
    },
    {
        "question": " 17京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.292719413205255
    },
    {
        "question": " 181兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.701848617571825
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.690709523838182
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.68万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.565407574296377
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.011751397655692
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.647662320455716
    },
    {
        "question": " 149兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.237157681619647
    },
    {
        "question": " 1910兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.724699527050557
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.1億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9383494386491817
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.95億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.997970144866061
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.050492305743499
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.25979484092451
    },
    {
        "question": " 4702垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.173467462250279
    },
    {
        "question": " 3643垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.624914710237165
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.65京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.32761217397863
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.16垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.934113160292119
    },
    {
        "question": " 286兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.455817061897576
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.7兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.783125442568078
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.327562358993956
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.9万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.204750551193456
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.933374432303872
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5863075040339742
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.519811465220434
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.93日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.531202147789044
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.314471065334116
    },
    {
        "question": " 552時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.361481204017011
    },
    {
        "question": " 153万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.962254277444632
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.1兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.712659131115851
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.4万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1504689252982354
    },
    {
        "question": " 5万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9207542232949244
    },
    {
        "question": " 961億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4839639466907335
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.354557194944922
    },
    {
        "question": " 137万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5807535845132348
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.04万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5318531813627354
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.307637481674616
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.28兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.36360646320838
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.42京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.933823589648025
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.6億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1564346722528533
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.8兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.495275595375519
    },
    {
        "question": " 4339万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.637381270192774
    },
    {
        "question": " 119京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.574956344564214
    },
    {
        "question": " 113兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1183590686872
    },
    {
        "question": " 1547京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.633319890448467
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.1兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.802633699771822
    },
    {
        "question": " 602億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.779448619198901
    },
    {
        "question": " 367万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.564819668010921
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.8垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.299264676923388
    },
    {
        "question": " 237垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.439148986530988
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.664493871693889
    },
    {
        "question": " 4039億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.828168892767317
    },
    {
        "question": " 52京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.71593378226911
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.2245658961997306
    },
    {
        "question": " 5572nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.7460426773617468
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.26万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.191556301788515
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.55年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.270590723714225
    },
    {
        "question": " 126億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5390142649411995
    },
    {
        "question": " 1060万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.40542054209646
    },
    {
        "question": " 846日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.08596521098595
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.18902948629855
    },
    {
        "question": " 2632万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.040031176719408
    },
    {
        "question": " 310時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.269129446279142
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.42時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.2013994899705
    },
    {
        "question": " 9133億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.239983251237579
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.7万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.753764894092142
    },
    {
        "question": " 9711分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2090990506296038
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.92万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.550743798583659
    },
    {
        "question": " 819分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.691285380906035
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.3分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.38353711029388
    },
    {
        "question": " 7455兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.373634164118243
    },
    {
        "question": " 4932億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.756511481067112
    },
    {
        "question": " 1770万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.691607279835327
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.2万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.978911508188646
    },
    {
        "question": " 106万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.027192062881836
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.8兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.858249927676557
    },
    {
        "question": " 437兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.703952527598048
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.471394819841225
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.314139359077371
    },
    {
        "question": " 101万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0045118801093063
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.2277700439717565
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.5msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.332466631044006
    },
    {
        "question": " 1679兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7262801355916235
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.4兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8696835816329282
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.2億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4359356728257091
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.53兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.625502685008223
    },
    {
        "question": " 922兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.964496984833296
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.0372891690169572
    },
    {
        "question": " 2388usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.378018178982535
    },
    {
        "question": " 2268垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.856828185141729
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3131375007842854
    },
    {
        "question": " 3990京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.044682397558184
    },
    {
        "question": " 6351億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0246711347311666
    },
    {
        "question": " 166京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.218988721369287
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.84億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.4538127675019075
    },
    {
        "question": " 26億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.415139890906229
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.7年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.93668909721971
    },
    {
        "question": " 1349日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5677714114766175
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.8日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5796246844723547
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.952959514514075
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.2億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.78311150463315
    },
    {
        "question": " 1549万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.809765986544463
    },
    {
        "question": " 413時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.393915603945232
    },
    {
        "question": " 4422時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.201896847114764
    },
    {
        "question": " 568時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.310695241721055
    },
    {
        "question": " 4094兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.891501696757208
    },
    {
        "question": " 24万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.221013520203068
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.9億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.102100832661574
    },
    {
        "question": " 4635分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4442321463559775
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.06億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4077208670636931
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.1兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.296611220624978
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.1億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.876643026268738
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.3億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.036550978059557
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.18512000574572
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.55京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.159546639975809
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.4京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.56006109459816
    },
    {
        "question": " 2209万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.787859803301385
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.317919518094392
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.214068287131994
    },
    {
        "question": " 1406兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6491707959338342
    },
    {
        "question": " 451京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.718104413651469
    },
    {
        "question": " 439兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.086625990483937
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.9億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1801966309167566
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.6億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.41463077484134
    },
    {
        "question": " 1785万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.251723452158497
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.56万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.932487940569618
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.8京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.319152881396759
    },
    {
        "question": " 5522垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.805627551627921
    },
    {
        "question": " 193京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.729230755750333
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.562832675879589
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.2860550825705
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.35兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.970936829398799
    },
    {
        "question": " 140億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.146937634261726
    },
    {
        "question": " 1818年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.821863258929669
    },
    {
        "question": " 203年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.028471261718021
    },
    {
        "question": " 1926万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.722419511042584
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3225986786991735
    },
    {
        "question": " 1434日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.093140624470136
    },
    {
        "question": " 62万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8495930186917742
    },
    {
        "question": " 663億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.441433656200138
    },
    {
        "question": " 6570万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.595686036470543
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.5億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.151441717460037
    },
    {
        "question": " 1581万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.040528691514904
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.641696623592016
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.117240859406775
    },
    {
        "question": " 3365億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.028231189264262
    },
    {
        "question": " 8445万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9901163733794123
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7046087004263666
    },
    {
        "question": " 731万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0855064449084955
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.25万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.966125009416313
    },
    {
        "question": " 419京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.123800740256431
    },
    {
        "question": " 736億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.930472429813605
    },
    {
        "question": " 7130兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.296787401025515
    },
    {
        "question": " 868億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.160347844755995
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.65万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.752321212217881
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.4万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.405235370694015
    },
    {
        "question": " 328msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.515766053322638
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.7垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.06605282042237
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.9兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.361264570324094
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.6億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3164891553784033
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.5億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8402670259169929
    },
    {
        "question": " 957億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.981025182197959
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.83億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.451965992003914
    },
    {
        "question": " 403万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.605287027794631
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.1垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.294479656774778
    },
    {
        "question": " 5180兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.777829808798822
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5666597419677815
    },
    {
        "question": " 29兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6837121540536812
    },
    {
        "question": " 7203億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8575221124872607
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.0236452367757307
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.76億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.942316753672493
    },
    {
        "question": " 220年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.904547116711855
    },
    {
        "question": " 21年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.265300104283303
    },
    {
        "question": " 826年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.637591816705275
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6470853321412147
    },
    {
        "question": " 1443日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5394855771580485
    },
    {
        "question": " 5694日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.691908623156026
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.03万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.538684257008144
    },
    {
        "question": " 5752時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.379655057573773
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.002672525890771
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.657455583329812
    },
    {
        "question": " 381万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8607581433599332
    },
    {
        "question": " 611万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6276692965231327
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.7億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.893498882267909
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.76分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.353103483950907
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.4分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.327738489819398
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8267029119801661
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.8万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7519615625386378
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5426693328996794
    },
    {
        "question": " 9969秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2204931027288097
    },
    {
        "question": " 2212秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.344690844379121
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.2秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.558946251447377
    },
    {
        "question": " 4834兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.185530111950072
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.6京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.563579575125239
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.33億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9665503262004513
    },
    {
        "question": " 6251万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0177872006612807
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.14兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.711185152013211
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.0325552695703886
    },
    {
        "question": " 71京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.352723064100505
    },
    {
        "question": " 1114京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.11023053018092
    },
    {
        "question": " 4041億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0501413436694813
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.6京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.761542579375881
    },
    {
        "question": " 3881億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.588898150495101
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.78万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.4442185069541957
    },
    {
        "question": " 1096usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.039701928989433
    },
    {
        "question": " 2031垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.808953619569953
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.534907041980751
    },
    {
        "question": " 510兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1515935531081176
    },
    {
        "question": " 5625兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.971956157709192
    },
    {
        "question": " 1228億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0892100688920587
    },
    {
        "question": " 46億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6627750007074686
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.0155535794623836
    },
    {
        "question": " 57万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.317891596487623
    },
    {
        "question": " 3897年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.533178117254515
    },
    {
        "question": " 10年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.500116160479966
    },
    {
        "question": " 502万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.138586602283968
    },
    {
        "question": " 173日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.618986578983959
    },
    {
        "question": " 42日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.781354483134743
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.7万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.50473551645616
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.7万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8113165909530948
    },
    {
        "question": " 17億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8511888011744215
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1154935830004318
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.1万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.210493838250255
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.75488657091917
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.5兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.04618725917856
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.7億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.753684529772732
    },
    {
        "question": " 1909億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.50257190068797
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.974529641907373
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.83002012448151
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.5万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5618361292092089
    },
    {
        "question": " 383億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.026665407665776
    },
    {
        "question": " 616万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.011140700420783
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.4秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.647723599951562
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.426977033399178
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.18兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3574549971342873
    },
    {
        "question": " 229兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.423521826179358
    },
    {
        "question": " 498万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14055582334638883
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.548823608325341
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.03億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8469014300537845
    },
    {
        "question": " 2765msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.441671648135996
    },
    {
        "question": " 4919京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.19305639707436
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.7京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.79358922095587
    },
    {
        "question": " 205京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.755089994065898
    },
    {
        "question": " 8877兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.17013709737353
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.34億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.523442299463029
    },
    {
        "question": " 130万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.1127751037221927
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.6usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.67761121918075
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.4垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9699239607793535
    },
    {
        "question": " 243兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4494428265656414
    },
    {
        "question": " 7794兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3354617303444147
    },
    {
        "question": " 8763兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.164490163939246
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.62兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9355049494382244
    },
    {
        "question": " 12億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.0792954214510857
    },
    {
        "question": " 7566万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.878844190968101
    },
    {
        "question": " 2244年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.913345903983352
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.780300037639266
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.082121516333185
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.84億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.272853881290564
    },
    {
        "question": " 143日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5347923332843068
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.31日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.736591911410988
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.4万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7333480698323145
    },
    {
        "question": " 408億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.230309719791153
    },
    {
        "question": " 776万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.667884425138187
    },
    {
        "question": " 268万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.98392224586825
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.889061312460947
    },
    {
        "question": " 180兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.535143914874354
    },
    {
        "question": " 169万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0688451649391935
    },
    {
        "question": " 262億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.63957362832687
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.28分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7458313136525114
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.87分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.772590721678493
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.22京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.847841407248001
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.095260006678969
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.677414195589268
    },
    {
        "question": " 577万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9832509303413675
    },
    {
        "question": " 1499秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.175684213995654
    },
    {
        "question": " 6299秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.79926106131256
    },
    {
        "question": " 722兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.359718975794338
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1895560968812158
    },
    {
        "question": " 1749兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.68647977905322
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.87万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.058511614635852194
    },
    {
        "question": " 1006万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.002490021128489
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.26万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.721238230990605
    },
    {
        "question": " 2348兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8718572264601374
    },
    {
        "question": " 2508京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.462909148328631
    },
    {
        "question": " 498兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.140704722590446
    },
    {
        "question": " 296兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.692530107960346
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.212481056799346
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.66億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.823235670623998
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.35京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.026235410322215102
    },
    {
        "question": " 3991京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.664577502139253
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.47360442810238
    },
    {
        "question": " 2994兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.698084968264217
    },
    {
        "question": " 462兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.664915507200156
    },
    {
        "question": " 1596万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.2031031996780073
    },
    {
        "question": " 1311nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.11748096478362835
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.79年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.388457153658075
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.77年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.259767631066458
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.6万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4201434528539076
    },
    {
        "question": " 772日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.268029785004909
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3404828018549142
    },
    {
        "question": " 4723時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.29400601740523
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.919350079523179
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.9時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.407142453041381
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.1億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1989176674760555
    },
    {
        "question": " 1535分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.02776621167087656
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3494511615282985
    },
    {
        "question": " 328分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.294664419271579
    },
    {
        "question": " 4782億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.180848129104559
    },
    {
        "question": " 6029億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8437728672323095
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.77265587078768
    },
    {
        "question": " 9785万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.212399538575371
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.4兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3233570173947657
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.100009727360039
    },
    {
        "question": " 536億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.173128805343984
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.379079879983488
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.47836334069544
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.8万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.427557493920085
    },
    {
        "question": " 61京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.286728891545319
    },
    {
        "question": " 3384京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.592898388655666
    },
    {
        "question": " 1726兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.680711558006744
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.289622740444271
    },
    {
        "question": " 409万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.611388490180369
    },
    {
        "question": " 452億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.655225142105032
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.04万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.309837721379914
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.12京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2881560674710082
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.7垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3125409849696545
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.1京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.39844211723336
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.6京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.773013708915063
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.271648798397253
    },
    {
        "question": " 7286億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.8624896927932575
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.05兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.956616563487538
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.82189982222004
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.25兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.789112675293959
    },
    {
        "question": " 566万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.132783957125591
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.385378005898252
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.088106045786688
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9103606820083785
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.921588276084839
    },
    {
        "question": " 1040時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.573533189305953
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.415013965247299
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.965916687572087
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.91億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.814322108958709
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.853256036858636
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.1分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.564140141083012
    },
    {
        "question": " 2647億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9240054373390967
    },
    {
        "question": " 755億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.941676317787686
    },
    {
        "question": " 2887億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.904113718784669
    },
    {
        "question": " 4696万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.893587578558091
    },
    {
        "question": " 493秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.692816463275757
    },
    {
        "question": " 2772京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.944005574122148
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.090419737614827
    },
    {
        "question": " 821億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.357845201330168
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.1万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0736014892627166
    },
    {
        "question": " 1659億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.219923478334817
    },
    {
        "question": " 3057msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.485282346540185
    },
    {
        "question": " 1451msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.161539728663419
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7649021517564685
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.98兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7609249022075812
    },
    {
        "question": " 3168兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.944475705896966
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.13億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.182176833345061
    },
    {
        "question": " 2605兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.415752639770242
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.3074772604231955
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.46usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.6493866340196157
    },
    {
        "question": " 155京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6919099264603166
    },
    {
        "question": " 236兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43692923473592216
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.63131109476317
    },
    {
        "question": " 393兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.815847158932316
    },
    {
        "question": " 129兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.111287855858006
    },
    {
        "question": " 334兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.524198402740815
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.0743920980758705
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0586021265710865
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.713542110123345
    },
    {
        "question": " 156億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6303850251098195
    },
    {
        "question": " 175万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6226828583867645
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.4日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9647230547853773
    },
    {
        "question": " 37日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.504565285858598
    },
    {
        "question": " 300万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5343931356161518
    },
    {
        "question": " 171億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.851985997154074
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.920348598032797
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.8時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.950952071047183
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.42時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.530548002131324
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.11億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.604028140606159
    },
    {
        "question": " 590万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.612831428507034
    },
    {
        "question": " 117分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2908622805733241
    },
    {
        "question": " 991分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.774102913879038
    },
    {
        "question": " 288分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.238151290848732
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.930010666662576
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.7兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.110624683927835
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.91億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.656204508862446
    },
    {
        "question": " 137万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5789032655646196
    },
    {
        "question": " 287億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.67964099155151
    },
    {
        "question": " 538万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.73078633033753
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.1秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.826636035825631
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.67兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0657503405070523
    },
    {
        "question": " 219兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.403552653774874
    },
    {
        "question": " 1939億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.731362259020352
    },
    {
        "question": " 6709億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0485058526425615
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.8億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.962761178888799
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.0713047628505645
    },
    {
        "question": " 141msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.150372787849932
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.6兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.027827422506311317
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.8京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.604729921043228
    },
    {
        "question": " 1337京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.56994470566568
    },
    {
        "question": " 1603兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4266692050893095
    },
    {
        "question": " 4700億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6721161684271575
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.16億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.619401565971661
    },
    {
        "question": " 327万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.513996705212616
    },
    {
        "question": " 3700京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0693571858863145
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.9京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7349114712585507
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.01垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.222897422490366
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.43兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0300219666990205
    },
    {
        "question": " 6641億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8222653447589616
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.24兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.350011860455772
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.173981180607494
    },
    {
        "question": " 96年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.544419461066028
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.62万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.501396667174875
    },
    {
        "question": " 663年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.54201599379216
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.602975419837074
    },
    {
        "question": " 148万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.551888963012413
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.1日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.066961932956991
    },
    {
        "question": " 4474億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.708217433660788
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.5時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6086337658290542
    },
    {
        "question": " 2369時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.15274660782906
    },
    {
        "question": " 4912時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.24757471897595
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.7時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.509202754286594
    },
    {
        "question": " 4846万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.964707404218512
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.7億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.251459508575401
    },
    {
        "question": " 127分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3254508467850936
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.994170102921794
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.05分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.626075695839132
    },
    {
        "question": " 130分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.890530127575829
    },
    {
        "question": " 118億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5746748505823467
    },
    {
        "question": " 357億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.61657933822056
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.34249103138224
    },
    {
        "question": " 4319億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.857197916353337
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.53京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.377858684992433
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.312085731368552
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.4億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7947551012939065
    },
    {
        "question": " 106億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.245979188946368
    },
    {
        "question": " 595億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7742841312496385
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.47万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.810590388568487
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.9兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14396025933181678
    },
    {
        "question": " 7510億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9391665738300414
    },
    {
        "question": " 4499億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.096810373673507
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.39億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8640341628558645
    },
    {
        "question": " 260億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.414318224392025
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.2億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.615416959866146
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.517180670152437
    },
    {
        "question": " 760兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9443444143886737
    },
    {
        "question": " 217兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7800287666889636
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.42京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.756201781232692
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1884872085088034
    },
    {
        "question": " 9389億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.972629489130705
    },
    {
        "question": " 2811nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.44883062490204795
    },
    {
        "question": " 5501年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3027624920085845
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.2万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.489084906658672
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.892780688056938
    },
    {
        "question": " 861日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.37248343089585356
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.22億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.887679125128146
    },
    {
        "question": " 2659億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.48221828718998
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.860533719709406
    },
    {
        "question": " 1796時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.032555032226257
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.55時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.48823350909615
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.506398213621727
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9290291354929403
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.5億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.907693478438928
    },
    {
        "question": " 722万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.63642346020215
    },
    {
        "question": " 212分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.104887215874246
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.3分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.273453018810402
    },
    {
        "question": " 8562兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.433795456882615
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.191571344496237
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.9万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.96133330356146
    },
    {
        "question": " 2055万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.53461416483001
    },
    {
        "question": " 223万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.347770108254545
    },
    {
        "question": " 712秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.85231049140806
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.73393450725182
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.66兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.488095432767706
    },
    {
        "question": " 468兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.11392690440046
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.5万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1489496550287281
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.64万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5615013775192865
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.92msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.282761832930024
    },
    {
        "question": " 1348兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.630786034018149
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.4兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8695865794359368
    },
    {
        "question": " 209兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.763759946403217
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.53832177013216
    },
    {
        "question": " 225兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.352364535801781
    },
    {
        "question": " 8827億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.945795575309084
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.4usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.7105496709317505
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.5垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.43315447161485
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.84垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.748660535844425
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.44京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.36989685251768
    },
    {
        "question": " 160京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.426125034799158
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.9億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4752616963004219
    },
    {
        "question": " 349億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.543152766614181
    },
    {
        "question": " 1150nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.06075736563776579
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.61年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.545127307024072
    },
    {
        "question": " 2795年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.388805531491311
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.68年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.252999329118161
    },
    {
        "question": " 1885日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.713078440011996
    },
    {
        "question": " 106万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.182312424768352
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.4億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.701260344256779
    },
    {
        "question": " 378時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1967541933392467
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.3万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.349934098843148
    },
    {
        "question": " 2249時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.908300421543218
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.351054695876989
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.2万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.810959676529566
    },
    {
        "question": " 1746分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4637706726091315
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8383073020244756
    },
    {
        "question": " 1805万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.320045444656259
    },
    {
        "question": " 332億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.964467932133637
    },
    {
        "question": " 7923秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.120765213658765
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.2088907026529756
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.25秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.719754767269014
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.2京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.281137780795749
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.89兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5238122448032305
    },
    {
        "question": " 215兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.776921570773472
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.349836670225399
    },
    {
        "question": " 136万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.132406124778677
    },
    {
        "question": " 261兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9185174649852546
    },
    {
        "question": " 3382億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5926996109383498
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.739864980365508
    },
    {
        "question": " 3342億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7458025560569363
    },
    {
        "question": " 101兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.006020833597681
    },
    {
        "question": " 3418億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.533757945533084
    },
    {
        "question": " 17usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.231187449520918
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.17垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.001649975444284
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.3京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.559007579299788
    },
    {
        "question": " 282兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8944828945047787
    },
    {
        "question": " 4189億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8439939813018305
    },
    {
        "question": " 513京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.710074218914592
    },
    {
        "question": " 2838万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.4530162224799126
    },
    {
        "question": " 152万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.1830892775415123
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.8万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.760730598688868
    },
    {
        "question": " 730年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8059726482687015
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.36億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.359708187385648
    },
    {
        "question": " 2813万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.82943571410662
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.247023659744055
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.09万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.643408544617923
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.326477549395506
    },
    {
        "question": " 137時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7555649733101732
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.8時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5828415288900595
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.2時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.114622227192104
    },
    {
        "question": " 3270兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.793886909539026
    },
    {
        "question": " 6749億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.67086029626339
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.4億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.148253641914708
    },
    {
        "question": " 1402万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.924824348674962
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.7兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.02821642556145
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.8万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8399723630651001
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.8万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.113525038866
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.5万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7840921123506774
    },
    {
        "question": " 843万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.925780386192148
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7320090972233215
    },
    {
        "question": " 21兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.385104819139761
    },
    {
        "question": " 375億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.01816786561989
    },
    {
        "question": " 157億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.418339313261055
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.81兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.448894603916845
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.1万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.234184452413327
    },
    {
        "question": " 205兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8137945587191542
    },
    {
        "question": " 943京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.03797884707471
    },
    {
        "question": " 166億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6648898553293914
    },
    {
        "question": " 9285兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.189636572084972
    },
    {
        "question": " 1732兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.23851378392985
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.4万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5319250122133532
    },
    {
        "question": " 1896usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.27781034776381
    },
    {
        "question": " 53垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.225410478935815
    },
    {
        "question": " 6430垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.871716672928839
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.2京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.325783134325004
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.6京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.004541274463207
    },
    {
        "question": " 1110億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0452787096604643
    },
    {
        "question": " 748億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.873949081923524
    },
    {
        "question": " 3548万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.549969551500648
    },
    {
        "question": " 90年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.516435243061076
    },
    {
        "question": " 234年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.311941050799006
    },
    {
        "question": " 204年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.80879693732188
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.2万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.308226860847615
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.09日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.642929106700517
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3110885539431374
    },
    {
        "question": " 658億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.437874164535305
    },
    {
        "question": " 1634万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.991402773560875
    },
    {
        "question": " 11万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.598686446147045
    },
    {
        "question": " 11時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.598205703892763
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7375039859082095
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.2万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2433907765581895
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.2万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8151423478856907
    },
    {
        "question": " 203万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.085971233827689
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.84分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.544450752218047
    },
    {
        "question": " 136分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.910642065739705
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.681518304928568
    },
    {
        "question": " 261兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.480176525622616
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.69億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.329402074680607
    },
    {
        "question": " 123万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.312024249033141
    },
    {
        "question": " 287秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.458175405723875
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.776734481408578
    },
    {
        "question": " 522億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.78142575577926
    },
    {
        "question": " 1040万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.46076717440059034
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.4億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.660357851575538
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2754720541988283
    },
    {
        "question": " 254万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.404430024132953
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.76垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.075884061661211
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.8兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0624558663794286
    },
    {
        "question": " 1366京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.579033658793746
    },
    {
        "question": " 29兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.683638394266489
    },
    {
        "question": " 8229億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.915351869560572
    },
    {
        "question": " 6877万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.837381083646158
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.284730889988062
    },
    {
        "question": " 193垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7868875741200965
    },
    {
        "question": " 515京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.775430765019327
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.46兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.37129583435858926
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.29京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.020529800510227
    },
    {
        "question": " 2500兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.397973642779643
    },
    {
        "question": " 9405兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.973364182279777
    },
    {
        "question": " 362億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.559257727700967
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.3年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9472861324618114
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.901922144160006
    },
    {
        "question": " 2570万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.847553703645367
    },
    {
        "question": " 366日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.944022756651001
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.32日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.524225968809489
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.98万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6578001860150862
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.9億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.397109509921926
    },
    {
        "question": " 1653時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.996356019692322
    },
    {
        "question": " 4165時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.175863411764042
    },
    {
        "question": " 344万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8164392215473737
    },
    {
        "question": " 754万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7192554140150524
    },
    {
        "question": " 1975万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.517371750546874
    },
    {
        "question": " 3253分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.290457994127946
    },
    {
        "question": " 6609分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.598259778859527
    },
    {
        "question": " 1526億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6847522869458613
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4765470593387375
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.61億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3251491512186035
    },
    {
        "question": " 2184秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5610636022350632
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.155323586481657
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.92垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.966729185933099
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.5億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.533112948570663
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.45億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9815157831189145
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.9億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7124092217868405
    },
    {
        "question": " 9969億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.998639760778998
    },
    {
        "question": " 844万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.926132638652545
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.07460162921879
    },
    {
        "question": " 9419京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.037495829183857
    },
    {
        "question": " 9086兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.402065043392878
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.353297420157806
    },
    {
        "question": " 243万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3860627226805491
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.53兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.931174993493233
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.51usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.8757999695812084
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.4垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.905999719532152
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1858618667015817
    },
    {
        "question": " 395京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.040819456083268
    },
    {
        "question": " 298兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6963673282935625
    },
    {
        "question": " 2806兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.448106261758683
    },
    {
        "question": " 405万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.6069513081910416
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.19万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.9635410910479778
    },
    {
        "question": " 179万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.815767216964485
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.4万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.801967894448044
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.27万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.952803267195502
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.58億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.934343166460827
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.9万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.15792948709938
    },
    {
        "question": " 875万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9993992314171782
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.92万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3114569153808104
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.955431636750969
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.65万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.493505046437647
    },
    {
        "question": " 1582時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.755473474663303
    },
    {
        "question": " 130万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3947781181245469
    },
    {
        "question": " 8861分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7891400197023424
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.88億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8108070611140334
    },
    {
        "question": " 2465兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8929363002605655
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3294044356677106
    },
    {
        "question": " 1130億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.49671429439343
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.83億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.906116323159271
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.171600470254342
    },
    {
        "question": " 2505秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.398884881081397
    },
    {
        "question": " 167京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.722644885266955
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.11億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3878279364245063
    },
    {
        "question": " 9024兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.399098863622697
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.65億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.973519796077741
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.267643827412607
    },
    {
        "question": " 212msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.326394034410205
    },
    {
        "question": " 158msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.198602761965743
    },
    {
        "question": " 329兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0185969656006366
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.5兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9469757582561296
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.46904895580486
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.4京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.552160324850167
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.7兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.650509088923954
    },
    {
        "question": " 736万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.8669206444675375
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.8usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.660642801776809
    },
    {
        "question": " 1931垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.787025239248684
    },
    {
        "question": " 1161垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.128239862891123
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5094406614623885
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.34兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.143061529786481
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.062303192787269
    },
    {
        "question": " 381兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.580466295805909
    },
    {
        "question": " 1638億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.21426877859166
    },
    {
        "question": " 148万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.732535189330413
    },
    {
        "question": " 2665年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.368207038620241
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.52年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.375320090283381
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.496386216626775
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5954094506258816
    },
    {
        "question": " 1123日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.208896584014628
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.66兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.941805883064362
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6435421940016104
    },
    {
        "question": " 1778時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.028152748050966
    },
    {
        "question": " 346時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.094780172762509
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.738304833994622
    },
    {
        "question": " 8938億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.230584842858215
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1531569975802924
    },
    {
        "question": " 509億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.928610796387883
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.2分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5355962619372883
    },
    {
        "question": " 1953兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.791897667625122
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.37億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8675233612124704
    },
    {
        "question": " 710億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2949886887626345
    },
    {
        "question": " 2898億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.683956624985836
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.622977348647615
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.28京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.421085223759428
    },
    {
        "question": " 2118億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.769608545655652
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5201425827232615
    },
    {
        "question": " 2421億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.383925201404521
    },
    {
        "question": " 4488msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.65206319616969
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.625428979212697
    },
    {
        "question": " 4129億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6793783550062293
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5708545902467437
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.22億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0803346904421018
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.79億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.94398938213704
    },
    {
        "question": " 2340万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.369132137807902
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.31万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.519957492964707
    },
    {
        "question": " 188京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7764477617521213
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3209573094793323
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.9京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.411510282888923
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.02京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.922175575363556
    },
    {
        "question": " 200兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.300929076169513
    },
    {
        "question": " 1186万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.074020314550993
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.2億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.945283978619211
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.7年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.126491443484319
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.996974589230529
    },
    {
        "question": " 1380万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.577730571364907
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.544066783822208
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3669606745296745
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.322088550999773
    },
    {
        "question": " 297万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.530441853237418
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.4億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.393440990230328
    },
    {
        "question": " 297時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.250199877185167
    },
    {
        "question": " 335時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.081790441596691
    },
    {
        "question": " 346万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8187924303388872
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0546468939462073
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.3万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6411787562553255
    },
    {
        "question": " 1927分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.063044401214944
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.91万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.37032618644899
    },
    {
        "question": " 9055兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.45811149288207
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.8兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.642980739013076
    },
    {
        "question": " 17億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.67520497257902
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.7億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.708601878446353
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.3万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.646742686066528
    },
    {
        "question": " 3808秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.580679711683162
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.022096220846011
    },
    {
        "question": " 3547兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.05103528678008
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.8億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9488670180560386
    },
    {
        "question": " 982万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43597690237436537
    },
    {
        "question": " 1467万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3882361089922446
    },
    {
        "question": " 235万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.370490172569668
    },
    {
        "question": " 3033msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.48180363409148
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.921512953188027
    },
    {
        "question": " 899京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.017020796410218
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.600470437973071
    },
    {
        "question": " 3938億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8171436360179314
    },
    {
        "question": " 98億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9911871732400925
    },
    {
        "question": " 2919usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.4651613803138077
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.536e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.687562837568159
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.180133625257866
    },
    {
        "question": " 6209京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.236748570624178
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.6兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.206913887326209
    },
    {
        "question": " 352億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5470383278041933
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.3307034279753385
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.281615492851722
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.728919500045652
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.28万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.177814196793136
    },
    {
        "question": " 3300日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.455004446666772
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.9日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.675720594810613
    },
    {
        "question": " 598万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8344942428612905
    },
    {
        "question": " 3398万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.15102696051655
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.9時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.390011130316565
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.953162399975925
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.71億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.84892231376894
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.77億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.784500668661289
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.1万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.114769131660557
    },
    {
        "question": " 300分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.255534654194417
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.5兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.407074368665708
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.166982949144057
    },
    {
        "question": " 500億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.142581539386824
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.2万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5265603586468863
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.5京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.118857954778916
    },
    {
        "question": " 439億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.705701604726255
    },
    {
        "question": " 1869億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.715338910024465
    },
    {
        "question": " 6851万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0576117017340376
    },
    {
        "question": " 353億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.547381182232594
    },
    {
        "question": " 2346msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.370411416340216
    },
    {
        "question": " 195垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.791031959423968
    },
    {
        "question": " 935億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03417318600784536
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.22兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.789716006170111
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.7兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.89420656049255
    },
    {
        "question": " 1236億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.091921460017995
    },
    {
        "question": " 593億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.773397253057276
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.532e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.904631979897036
    },
    {
        "question": " 8375垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.986481669172514
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.6京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.943330823228042
    },
    {
        "question": " 779億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11322632502837382
    },
    {
        "question": " 208京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.317883969968328
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.85億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.6860157542130523
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.277695335965792
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.2万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9085965719775055
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.097087909595935
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.78億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.881526779526971
    },
    {
        "question": " 111日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.425411546517826
    },
    {
        "question": " 1150日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.21889773552461
    },
    {
        "question": " 110日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.979368641759853
    },
    {
        "question": " 102億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.067236678804938
    },
    {
        "question": " 173億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.858319941873901
    },
    {
        "question": " 832万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.698238456698045
    },
    {
        "question": " 102時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.56551231989562
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.592994960095472
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.28億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1412579782598793
    },
    {
        "question": " 399万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.442490857421748
    },
    {
        "question": " 3606億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.77887697204866
    },
    {
        "question": " 1736分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.01760846573486
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.79825645584155
    },
    {
        "question": " 3257兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.013997247192043
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.4万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3045459419743535
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.658630002170981
    },
    {
        "question": " 2231秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.570390459663138
    },
    {
        "question": " 123万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.091231400630942
    },
    {
        "question": " 384秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.584352243221344
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.681714785572138
    },
    {
        "question": " 747億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9365521310428178
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.561605621172911
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4123990106914572
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.182185040503243
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6831142305567255
    },
    {
        "question": " 36兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.620342107090845
    },
    {
        "question": " 567億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1973154649581108
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.92兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.814830407252172
    },
    {
        "question": " 108万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03251951536437425
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.1210025287094
    },
    {
        "question": " 163万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.212512240773451
    },
    {
        "question": " 5149垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.212931661689539
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.9京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7617816352765643
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.3垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.00316706084038
    },
    {
        "question": " 419京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.843892317087513
    },
    {
        "question": " 3187兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.503432309622971
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.360410427152129
    },
    {
        "question": " 1000nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.00021530054387097763
    },
    {
        "question": " 1151万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.498872288366954
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.19日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2933795233688925
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.98万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.838735443676644
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.1万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7661606219349502
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.32億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.539893411336682
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.396150521608861
    },
    {
        "question": " 820万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1929274751241192
    },
    {
        "question": " 147万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.010366405671314
    },
    {
        "question": " 4349分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8602236512171777
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.5分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4451766802721373
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.805641554712318
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.842226794047072
    },
    {
        "question": " 410億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.11380290117238
    },
    {
        "question": " 1730億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.301475689190768
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.47億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9836321761650115
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.58億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7758991270596916
    },
    {
        "question": " 368万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.565589412384245
    },
    {
        "question": " 406京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.109803248341525
    },
    {
        "question": " 117億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1308125120040255
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.87京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.901018852873435
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.61兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.103070583884374
    },
    {
        "question": " 5912万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.771764881263371
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.9msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.590159515908234
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.338213616533972
    },
    {
        "question": " 343京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.036938981120022
    },
    {
        "question": " 9966京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.06200071770964
    },
    {
        "question": " 2652億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.867351452379571
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.85京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.807635689394665
    },
    {
        "question": " 9612万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9827971899668873
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.28兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.51600839357587
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.1usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.324079799605684
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.7京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1516803642930062
    },
    {
        "question": " 35京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6080539561077707
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.3兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9393398092021388
    },
    {
        "question": " 1354兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.35349105770624
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.44京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.735391226051299
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.24億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.6275345313585907
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.43兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.97462730807216
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.99万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.03798150089336
    },
    {
        "question": " 1787年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.972882724020137
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.33億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.407654776063444
    },
    {
        "question": " 3841日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.964639201925014
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.07万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.786192630747143
    },
    {
        "question": " 225億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.410132534175686
    },
    {
        "question": " 1830億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.882281175877392
    },
    {
        "question": " 309兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.76867804832788
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.07万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4517597500304025
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.89億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.81211637756123
    },
    {
        "question": " 5387分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5095103539291035
    },
    {
        "question": " 9989分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.777690528805286
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.9939169806827515
    },
    {
        "question": " 6795兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.33338913229176
    },
    {
        "question": " 47億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.735591515576964
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.8万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9464251866206483
    },
    {
        "question": " 150億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.397788513387315
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.11万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.324926130021168
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.9兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9143916633464375
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.095539752101473
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5749484598695704
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.9万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5999702708453125
    },
    {
        "question": " 2129msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3282497014910857
    },
    {
        "question": " 359msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.555261456524487
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.4兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.417297156465235
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.7兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.723055044051855
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.601148389531068
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.72億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1093548843149703
    },
    {
        "question": " 269万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43044397876043194
    },
    {
        "question": " 8751万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.94204171138035
    },
    {
        "question": " 550京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.241520204297794
    },
    {
        "question": " 176垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.308050341110683
    },
    {
        "question": " 8415兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.368777877673035
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.7京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.891460555929219
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.22京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.914906817564517
    },
    {
        "question": " 8300万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.919095806390878
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.51億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.5448399742276795
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.41年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3688417585503716
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.3年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.861505019581259
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.936801957654904
    },
    {
        "question": " 30万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.915397473931618
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.2兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.86515936749186
    },
    {
        "question": " 124時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7118656741882534
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.227724218958835
    },
    {
        "question": " 187万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.828562857109016
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.713474518824604
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.03兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.884876490259176
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3207216811076683
    },
    {
        "question": " 2178万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.559972481997094
    },
    {
        "question": " 762分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.660030801899982
    },
    {
        "question": " 300億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9788152491718343
    },
    {
        "question": " 506兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.767573839296356
    },
    {
        "question": " 3100億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.935003008876551
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.8億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.750730080216784
    },
    {
        "question": " 357万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.552060372791711
    },
    {
        "question": " 1331億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6252273329618641
    },
    {
        "question": " 1469兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.230638965759612
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.781095670673674
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.95億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.996411023694094
    },
    {
        "question": " 7693万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.886120831516586
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.1057800927629806
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.701154253391466
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.92京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.346094355713272
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.541782345288318
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.49889250259636
    },
    {
        "question": " 4528兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.655940837317441
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.54万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5489040280773858
    },
    {
        "question": " 160万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.204547609340292
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.61京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3828636273508701
    },
    {
        "question": " 136垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.197810944559235
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.22京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.302250889429323
    },
    {
        "question": " 525兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.942180208356426
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.457174389379151
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.267736134139533
    },
    {
        "question": " 651万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.813358111507914
    },
    {
        "question": " 932年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.531881576436466
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.32万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.743350845079219
    },
    {
        "question": " 288年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.958615988136788
    },
    {
        "question": " 1001万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4380092962371345
    },
    {
        "question": " 4890日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.069543615412457
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.69日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9837781982008913
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.347917100513676
    },
    {
        "question": " 1037億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.635649643832082
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.9万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7173413344638835
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.4時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.467164142299161
    },
    {
        "question": " 138万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.42003683438552764
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.2億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8155362916798214
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.594931445171959
    },
    {
        "question": " 156万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.970449184564687
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.2分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.103661504051525
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.167906378258326
    },
    {
        "question": " 3930兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.095559794271894
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.47億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8017467970909866
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.62兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.264292489815729
    },
    {
        "question": " 130秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3346379521295151
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.9万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.868795516408497
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.33704118410102
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.5兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.296897929786825
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.222026140552227
    },
    {
        "question": " 540兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.176179704529748
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.8億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.710270414401769
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.73兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.828283111501007
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.96msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.842421759466903
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.003953480634231
    },
    {
        "question": " 1915京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.783269598910286
    },
    {
        "question": " 907兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.021319596214359
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.6億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.34466227303556085
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.52億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6231530886256664
    },
    {
        "question": " 3673億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.564996817669802
    },
    {
        "question": " 293億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.466416336408441
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.883e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.776015259044877
    },
    {
        "question": " 32京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5685412021571947
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6609227800022932
    },
    {
        "question": " 2888兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.682386369783018
    },
    {
        "question": " 254京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.404207632554016
    },
    {
        "question": " 18兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.254951259241981
    },
    {
        "question": " 2313nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.36409367406658677
    },
    {
        "question": " 3147年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.440336552726993
    },
    {
        "question": " 121億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.519533779544851
    },
    {
        "question": " 347日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9201885518444546
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.23万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6670413134915965
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.3億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.898210139126983
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.8億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.977413106831125
    },
    {
        "question": " 2665万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.203901526531807
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.614924937884716
    },
    {
        "question": " 4992万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9776285095063006
    },
    {
        "question": " 3128万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.336950071139095
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.456842771235135
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.3万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.46236720683743
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.928208535518745
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.15億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.212941528555771
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.81兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.51168135265733
    },
    {
        "question": " 8139億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.3542550540576
    },
    {
        "question": " 5828秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9873519874367451
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.3万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.772739986302275
    },
    {
        "question": " 148兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6711492254452374
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.1兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.707932878529622
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.3兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.895793330053715
    },
    {
        "question": " 1211万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.304815967370666
    },
    {
        "question": " 3817msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.58171873706099
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.910001685847705
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.529827822231995
    },
    {
        "question": " 23京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.425969560853053
    },
    {
        "question": " 2519億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8449036683968012
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.23京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.84834524998184
    },
    {
        "question": " 3444兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.537065644834914
    },
    {
        "question": " 1137億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.05572838343531
    },
    {
        "question": " 1022usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.009418871150683
    },
    {
        "question": " 1993京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8006521109875804
    },
    {
        "question": " 5668兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.816962260139976
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.9京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.086093595797038
    },
    {
        "question": " 6431億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0301084527422666
    },
    {
        "question": " 3157億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4993255417538096
    },
    {
        "question": " 531億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.725075691505066
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.1806102462939905
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.9万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.459522747341136
    },
    {
        "question": " 626年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.739268318456778
    },
    {
        "question": " 1237日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5299007872363315
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.2億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.844171661221922
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.993755796437639
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.8時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.237240883280527
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.397928121937559
    },
    {
        "question": " 563億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.591999681863201
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.9億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.667978891487324
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.1分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4695703722128393
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.842239214531533
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.58分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.332209267457975
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.2京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.96590942500188
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.310106524586601
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.5万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0296940482080017
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.416890903709139
    },
    {
        "question": " 711億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3532964705323838
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.58兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.724780547634998
    },
    {
        "question": " 5288億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.166955483396985
    },
    {
        "question": " 226億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.576477199801855
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.077070266783297
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.213489169686306
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.478496656923035
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.1京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.124994625557891
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.2垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.568778735681418
    },
    {
        "question": " 3431京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.97910883449778
    },
    {
        "question": " 1438億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.379573186704569
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.3億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.968331405245955
    },
    {
        "question": " 5737万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.7587148815355595
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.7京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4878964100979366
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.79垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0075337870986045
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.8京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.641880616217039
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.2京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.815543209051987
    },
    {
        "question": " 4357兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.639163672013342
    },
    {
        "question": " 5016億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.700350048307198
    },
    {
        "question": " 144億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.156925970525211
    },
    {
        "question": " 136万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.697170241715321
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.39年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.320959675557644
    },
    {
        "question": " 1万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.720981794811944
    },
    {
        "question": " 27億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.869164425401497
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.03万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.160715491424301
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.76日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7329772556948857
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.970296978913131
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.7億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.305347430011649
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.34億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.485634797789498
    },
    {
        "question": " 167時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.000788931747808
    },
    {
        "question": " 1848万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.545996303643049
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.909026843272267
    },
    {
        "question": " 6468分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.032591644651599
    },
    {
        "question": " 520万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.49410625254761
    },
    {
        "question": " 118億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5735939178658707
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.8億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.684721904995407
    },
    {
        "question": " 1840万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.708592849006107
    },
    {
        "question": " 450万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8751669248036
    },
    {
        "question": " 1138秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.056066043750272
    },
    {
        "question": " 550兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.241459733926822
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.83京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.515276505202035
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.614269058142522
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.4億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.898041402252201
    },
    {
        "question": " 1184万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.073306741974774
    },
    {
        "question": " 807msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.9070897333650585
    },
    {
        "question": " 297msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.47252165367938
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.6京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.187840068594172
    },
    {
        "question": " 3165億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5639119429158523
    },
    {
        "question": " 247京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.836160384500152
    },
    {
        "question": " 1068億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2505262602642504
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3438910691457293
    },
    {
        "question": " 7551usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.8779789959525897
    },
    {
        "question": " 9940usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.997396348680619
    },
    {
        "question": " 853京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4322145662228403
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.435855440397834
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.57286825824922
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.1京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.021727144207318
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.7億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7610374599989145
    },
    {
        "question": " 478兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.679627010997086
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.52億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.8764957656496115
    },
    {
        "question": " 329年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0793066139356515
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.095052720064146
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.97年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3192023522401986
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.557041517203714
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.9万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0284096983109112
    },
    {
        "question": " 449日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.03251508108335
    },
    {
        "question": " 629日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.956737135834793
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.99万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9017338412943243
    },
    {
        "question": " 6981万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.463735285832711
    },
    {
        "question": " 630万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.577650386721595
    },
    {
        "question": " 338兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.808851817874015
    },
    {
        "question": " 1298億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.955037455873142
    },
    {
        "question": " 6839万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.056849210186133
    },
    {
        "question": " 2831万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.230133527043943
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.938644923154206
    },
    {
        "question": " 8243億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.417288300478191
    },
    {
        "question": " 5635万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8143786639784443
    },
    {
        "question": " 310万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9348617983009917
    },
    {
        "question": " 1457億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.38518423790638
    },
    {
        "question": " 721万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.857690133191026
    },
    {
        "question": " 199兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7998728665322323
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.4兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.701206916365478
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.2億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.33671789405538
    },
    {
        "question": " 2514億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.62228417115951
    },
    {
        "question": " 1748msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2424243684998828
    },
    {
        "question": " 192msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.284245055085382
    },
    {
        "question": " 1738msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.23994983975882
    },
    {
        "question": " 491兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1919454287095732
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.29753530166167
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.1京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.806817226808742
    },
    {
        "question": " 353兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.770169931129917
    },
    {
        "question": " 690万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8390631291616291
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.1億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.433150802756138
    },
    {
        "question": " 5789京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2637808584518235
    },
    {
        "question": " 5995兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8412858035863033
    },
    {
        "question": " 2928兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.910215856864544
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.6京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.808960789582413
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.8億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3757057211948778
    },
    {
        "question": " 3156億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.499070634233099
    },
    {
        "question": " 735億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.86634511039363
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8603876825282737
    },
    {
        "question": " 1199年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.799562446397557
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.7年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.47533655029908
    },
    {
        "question": " 77万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3244579856296963
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.396698108106584
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.9日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.921296679973156
    },
    {
        "question": " 478億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.737303667099273
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.64800234711874
    },
    {
        "question": " 3232時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.065816286663019
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.2時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.2725993152879
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.4億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.101366890923323
    },
    {
        "question": " 276億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.28233813333944
    },
    {
        "question": " 215億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.554052740515894
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.1億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3078604365585487
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13678566292263272
    },
    {
        "question": " 1113億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.490066451404141
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4764472671909243
    },
    {
        "question": " 227秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.356912872940233
    },
    {
        "question": " 140兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6479462661602002
    },
    {
        "question": " 2084億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.382406750820862
    },
    {
        "question": " 6972億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.287058756399045
    },
    {
        "question": " 130兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.334222646081434
    },
    {
        "question": " 2578億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.411338504961261
    },
    {
        "question": " 145京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.661647409502981
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.9京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.753123601669703
    },
    {
        "question": " 16兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6469975144848688
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.5京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.74641116594108
    },
    {
        "question": " 8310万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9195829460506841
    },
    {
        "question": " 3069万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.486931615936194
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.88垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.495773995680389
    },
    {
        "question": " 4803垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.74500604551207
    },
    {
        "question": " 8757京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.386035300855004
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.4京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.173184807494195
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.41京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.869819465297212
    },
    {
        "question": " 969億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.986428256545045
    },
    {
        "question": " 1930nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.2856196485244633
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6556419552502035
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.52年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.376097367773551
    },
    {
        "question": " 1392億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.581458436420553
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.398834440025719
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.58万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.490222791507467
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.214814607201034
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.5万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9524927974889845
    },
    {
        "question": " 259万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.19199609381329
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.9万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.93526265326241
    },
    {
        "question": " 291億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.74358010786549
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.01億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6204716424546985
    },
    {
        "question": " 1952億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.512277400242649
    },
    {
        "question": " 7026分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.624869831353145
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.9分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.56243475387492
    },
    {
        "question": " 748億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3750847426513686
    },
    {
        "question": " 2776万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5069595987601465
    },
    {
        "question": " 731万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3075347422127868
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.376510946715026
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.6京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.276224783358078
    },
    {
        "question": " 338兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.592194533161965
    },
    {
        "question": " 1308万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5604195802363998
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3247241742794653
    },
    {
        "question": " 6239億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.795146599491705
    },
    {
        "question": " 284万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.45287997298326
    },
    {
        "question": " 3396msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.53101773690188
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.948821168106658
    },
    {
        "question": " 68兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.895870995780465
    },
    {
        "question": " 2438億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8306867252298764
    },
    {
        "question": " 9890万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2170272772787618
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.038481509266723
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.1204788638446326
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.4万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.702334181552878
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.405e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.64887553548183
    },
    {
        "question": " 261垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.48006213623034
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.71垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.117174692146833
    },
    {
        "question": " 3165京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.722173252614068
    },
    {
        "question": " 108京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.033218495589804
    },
    {
        "question": " 6632万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.8216164782559874
    },
    {
        "question": " 140万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.146567390819701
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.7年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2121779980543215
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.01633827242478
    },
    {
        "question": " 677日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.26851322719918747
    },
    {
        "question": " 11日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4220966109063626
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.995013803862674
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.8万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7717374904015815
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.6万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.586401410205655
    },
    {
        "question": " 146時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.942891345971067
    },
    {
        "question": " 116万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.621307626569441
    },
    {
        "question": " 1597時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.759540913302077
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.441914023861283
    },
    {
        "question": " 369万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4088383077808526
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.2万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.89590124109351
    },
    {
        "question": " 481分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.459872209478096
    },
    {
        "question": " 322億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0087417202798417
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.7兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.011419244871536
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.24兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.30366735014696
    },
    {
        "question": " 856億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.154237673611796
    },
    {
        "question": " 1216秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.084811940524036
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.767034202882196
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.087720584553438
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8573377156488835
    },
    {
        "question": " 6140億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.010003386400506
    },
    {
        "question": " 363万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5604279518644177
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.573432622320986
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.09垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.459625072460232
    },
    {
        "question": " 1888京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.339518439870423
    },
    {
        "question": " 1285億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.552591811030808
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.8兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5987318972962115
    },
    {
        "question": " 5704兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.756185932542028
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.2億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.3045201630984105
    },
    {
        "question": " 929京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4692721829723743
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.082587147827569
    },
    {
        "question": " 9048兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4002650487828587
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.478057606976677
    },
    {
        "question": " 9395億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9728968444348816
    },
    {
        "question": " 1053万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.0225337726464956
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.01万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.77878181808107
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.338095824417836
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.7年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.510740115718695
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.9億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.834678210916603
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.239941708289908
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.364094536504017
    },
    {
        "question": " 996億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.618011543161728
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.32時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.504305289590172
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.56万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.434746676329098
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.78億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9589479987633647
    },
    {
        "question": " 454億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.498625201420655
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.2分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.008476498339512473
    },
    {
        "question": " 1746兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.743174819803771
    },
    {
        "question": " 284億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.51751791768647
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8822503303471094
    },
    {
        "question": " 932億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.191302405568893
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.9秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.698314029457737
    },
    {
        "question": " 2159億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8353581262584764
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.4兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.024376188756434
    },
    {
        "question": " 7248億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.303944204950125
    },
    {
        "question": " 1058億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2461619565885576
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.33兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.920574000317071
    },
    {
        "question": " 50msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.699067350312944
    },
    {
        "question": " 364兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0619069580001184
    },
    {
        "question": " 608兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8474901518856486
    },
    {
        "question": " 521億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1603216401432714
    },
    {
        "question": " 394億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.817510183300349
    },
    {
        "question": " 581万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7639574546286454
    },
    {
        "question": " 181億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.258579014662153
    },
    {
        "question": " 1426usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.154196727068996
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.9京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2637602782834967
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3014478927868165
    },
    {
        "question": " 145兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6051736521639026
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.2垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.845325175056804
    },
    {
        "question": " 7210兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.857936002525971
    },
    {
        "question": " 582兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.764843135089555
    },
    {
        "question": " 4732億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.67504106871819
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.934179041989618
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.75年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.159650840082328
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.5年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.90582544379688
    },
    {
        "question": " 1271億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.541740984318182
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.648918305175416
    },
    {
        "question": " 1303万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.172539371010984
    },
    {
        "question": " 152万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.802619452903716
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.49万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.368747615304725
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.607714925357393
    },
    {
        "question": " 224億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.192068836603742
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.39億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.027317376269958
    },
    {
        "question": " 1084分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.813178621881517
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.2分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.654539650934773
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.35兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.140088296804763
    },
    {
        "question": " 1345億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.192166414533156
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6241233091918195
    },
    {
        "question": " 5907億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.993199039158437
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.22秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7174581971161103
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.71秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.756571354955858
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.61京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.484059065983606
    },
    {
        "question": " 6740億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8921460991331736
    },
    {
        "question": " 286億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9004723574627653
    },
    {
        "question": " 5011万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9217628369652737
    },
    {
        "question": " 261億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.416946846060077
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.97msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.293701566505764
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.617003833811649
    },
    {
        "question": " 6325京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.864529115813873
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.632472237615761
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.45兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.148931304762875
    },
    {
        "question": " 648兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.8113528439441
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.9万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.9186358902843237
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.3京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4370806565066818
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.43垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.710284696092506
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.2垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.296197273189325
    },
    {
        "question": " 4939京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.915512601414388
    },
    {
        "question": " 5453兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.736598736627703
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.96兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.695793248305634
    },
    {
        "question": " 1638nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.21434166409725397
    },
    {
        "question": " 165年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.159137025934045
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.3億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.308848951499627
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.575182502128765
    },
    {
        "question": " 536万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.88742479098433
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.5億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.36881392194509
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.8億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.030991812839934
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.7時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1887499317381875
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4143253557109476
    },
    {
        "question": " 993万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.838494375521231
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3058138424985097
    },
    {
        "question": " 2963分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.249885355983647
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.16京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.463239396077489
    },
    {
        "question": " 5753億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.82338803926565
    },
    {
        "question": " 4342秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08140142836545183
    },
    {
        "question": " 2789秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6672612952361032
    },
    {
        "question": " 629兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.299721521228344
    },
    {
        "question": " 175兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.306718805673103
    },
    {
        "question": " 5738兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.20246925329106
    },
    {
        "question": " 234億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.591123538233729
    },
    {
        "question": " 2462万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.391269779365085
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.48msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.393852477794191
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.693857912840409
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1518105695557495
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.6億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10305964759601216
    },
    {
        "question": " 3362兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.748471165990248
    },
    {
        "question": " 5281億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.72275280574622
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.07億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.783536664444602
    },
    {
        "question": " 1126京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5526723305449006
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.7垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.991588171259377
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.621890054657339
    },
    {
        "question": " 1783億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47288460537802335
    },
    {
        "question": " 1439億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.158056788854499
    },
    {
        "question": " 946万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.9759408216378151
    },
    {
        "question": " 2658億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.424569114545108
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.679084308952868
    },
    {
        "question": " 1万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.72266034310444
    },
    {
        "question": " 380万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.017068447702089
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.6万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.101584983763613
    },
    {
        "question": " 5958日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.933486521969822
    },
    {
        "question": " 249日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.333398771827136
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.074961843352427
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.4時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15653830126924673
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.909820947753467
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.404762110209725
    },
    {
        "question": " 6602万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.661305731196013
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.11億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.546426612487744
    },
    {
        "question": " 2959分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.24926152464157
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.7分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.700905329878953
    },
    {
        "question": " 277億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.943667857652491
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.8兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.552312287613494
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.92兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.28407239353614
    },
    {
        "question": " 2156秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5554493948125647
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.51秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7413706390623034
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.44秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.808781024846445
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.690667102504135
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.290681431396763
    },
    {
        "question": " 3099億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.934926181491241
    },
    {
        "question": " 5643億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.973396708777496
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.038556615021032
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.91msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.771854532036422
    },
    {
        "question": " 1154京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.563252118380024
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.5兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.92378526267275
    },
    {
        "question": " 850億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3728927725321927
    },
    {
        "question": " 1598億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4254213034225165
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.82兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.581609589024805
    },
    {
        "question": " 4212usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.6244503273437274
    },
    {
        "question": " 1730垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.739302203744844
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1370945714240044
    },
    {
        "question": " 310京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.935061915570852
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.471990409340023
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.08兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.95786184825499
    },
    {
        "question": " 125億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.097409110178604
    },
    {
        "question": " 2730nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.4362269608836855
    },
    {
        "question": " 2363万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.935673625365252
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.5年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.731022239128634
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.848084322295951
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.5年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.983703948120686
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.8万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3554866054336285
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.38日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0220652692623773
    },
    {
        "question": " 299日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.634068577598697
    },
    {
        "question": " 118万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1307154804824027
    },
    {
        "question": " 864万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.55649339401639
    },
    {
        "question": " 245時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.94586579286594
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.32億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6451253338615577
    },
    {
        "question": " 881万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7865537483905856
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.365270358328163
    },
    {
        "question": " 141万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.928712148748806
    },
    {
        "question": " 13分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.893383873058814
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.81203520739497
    },
    {
        "question": " 622億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.857138095933142
    },
    {
        "question": " 3595万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9994148858143963
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.28万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.57974173028644
    },
    {
        "question": " 175万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.242858833944243
    },
    {
        "question": " 5033億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2029847315771036
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.122132071238875
    },
    {
        "question": " 8331兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.364420682169374
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.624059630008333
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2630816564778058
    },
    {
        "question": " 2902垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.963935004529409
    },
    {
        "question": " 988京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.058115752096931
    },
    {
        "question": " 1201京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.523406649711074
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.8兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.649852394655587
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.73億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.571820146796866
    },
    {
        "question": " 2047usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.3110586030001117
    },
    {
        "question": " 9920京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4976994214578996
    },
    {
        "question": " 1555垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.255310809870972
    },
    {
        "question": " 2663京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.86902326144419
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.1京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.604558409043545
    },
    {
        "question": " 1039億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.016580071705003
    },
    {
        "question": " 172万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.23444744617753366
    },
    {
        "question": " 7247万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.860143575642831
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.08年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.20921959339422
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.2年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.14463422006957
    },
    {
        "question": " 1244日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5323995899079836
    },
    {
        "question": " 2505万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.779011435012448
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.9日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.381984069361502
    },
    {
        "question": " 843万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.983512683629507
    },
    {
        "question": " 582万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.384625423090932
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.590805770286973
    },
    {
        "question": " 108万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31245720218671336
    },
    {
        "question": " 6676分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.666191439545124
    },
    {
        "question": " 156分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4152920707120411
    },
    {
        "question": " 6038分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.559058547954729
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.043122981040521
    },
    {
        "question": " 3118兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.995102008310685
    },
    {
        "question": " 406万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6719529505916497
    },
    {
        "question": " 3139億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.940434986024176
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.293758186325996
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.014094893513299
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.5秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.511525665048222
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.2京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.094904147519124
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.37兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.703868858633253
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.87億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9009780785253128
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.2万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6057567431611066
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.9万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9997173674973787
    },
    {
        "question": " 279万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.445423730555323
    },
    {
        "question": " 357msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.552712439853202
    },
    {
        "question": " 465垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.168192163116034
    },
    {
        "question": " 420兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.686255227933964
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.7京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.053118471308869
    },
    {
        "question": " 7741兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.110638304601919
    },
    {
        "question": " 956万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9805264414926806
    },
    {
        "question": " 6818usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.833626510719121
    },
    {
        "question": " 1482usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.170769411082735
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5643481944979944
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.8京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9546123853670387
    },
    {
        "question": " 11兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.48357822541066575
    },
    {
        "question": " 117兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.29166502861286
    },
    {
        "question": " 9452兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.975525574472003
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.74億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.9415655523083375
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.7万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.5768386637748963
    },
    {
        "question": " 561万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.310946700104806
    },
    {
        "question": " 949日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.41480019610802055
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.77日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.822628987643422
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.64万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.142642876531166
    },
    {
        "question": " 6065万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8403319171756523
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.47億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.49338368813355
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2149626137601874
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.840011351639459
    },
    {
        "question": " 1656時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.775229616554967
    },
    {
        "question": " 695万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1213049844314071
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.985307141487315
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.19万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5623325527042207
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.76分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.767472798680053
    },
    {
        "question": " 250億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8992626364280474
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.118600022801549
    },
    {
        "question": " 876万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3859774445593613
    },
    {
        "question": " 8400万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1461154374781435
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.224304341301411
    },
    {
        "question": " 675億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3307721372842698
    },
    {
        "question": " 2641億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4852552752586883
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.33兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1700427230345305
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23273617081564502
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3151199524556807
    },
    {
        "question": " 2271msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.35612669241436
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.64垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.92262862665088
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1531256431961445
    },
    {
        "question": " 1773兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.69244951948278
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.19兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.013767306377456
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.71兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.569047255009211
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.13億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.7103195886061755
    },
    {
        "question": " 643usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.808220906876191
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.119e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.549951875197358
    },
    {
        "question": " 2017兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3681986108837108
    },
    {
        "question": " 8179兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3563942051263176
    },
    {
        "question": " 1291京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.332699095786475
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.4億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4379474557912766
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.09億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.3206873522917215
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.3072648754850036
    },
    {
        "question": " 24万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.942090439765922
    },
    {
        "question": " 4313億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.072464066576254
    },
    {
        "question": " 7203日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.237737955791534
    },
    {
        "question": " 5160日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8710207998133574
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.64万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.602907098356692
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.220701010599871
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.23万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3382250225972876
    },
    {
        "question": " 202時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.083825544242964
    },
    {
        "question": " 333時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.079042603516766
    },
    {
        "question": " 2206時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.89987208761825
    },
    {
        "question": " 925万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2457115356189752
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.8万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2859665954849184
    },
    {
        "question": " 8367分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.14442544746014
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.8分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.508931964797888
    },
    {
        "question": " 7020万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3475242765555542
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.8万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7149101614553599
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7079465039331698
    },
    {
        "question": " 749万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.096598443955424
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.308355359602555
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.870766818836513
    },
    {
        "question": " 3081億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5522424707699796
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.1億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.229712537715087
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.7兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.159793598779245
    },
    {
        "question": " 1411億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.149380308409807
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.88msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.273028543138656
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.9垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.018642824329746
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.325987875307037
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.5京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.36012869869237
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.39319557854378906
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.32億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.864413735087835
    },
    {
        "question": " 1202usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.07993221276036744
    },
    {
        "question": " 428万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.631098700683696
    },
    {
        "question": " 590垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.271712241687303
    },
    {
        "question": " 2519京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.464712180834618
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.54京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3749059325663895
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.56垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.630219982416241
    },
    {
        "question": " 3477兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.541171492164507
    },
    {
        "question": " 1820億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.2600173985163785
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.39万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.3783627880631955
    },
    {
        "question": " 8079年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.469642173725313
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.3万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.29106462347605
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.5年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.282698232922252
    },
    {
        "question": " 117億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.506583415216178
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.668048780016432
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1771601663588935
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.343434858797568
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.82億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3031152184366634
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.53万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.654677324493342
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.638769009890003
    },
    {
        "question": " 42時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.179139166286172
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3684645466947374
    },
    {
        "question": " 202万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1471453111798664
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.69万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.651515256263556
    },
    {
        "question": " 1135分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8332897188159
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.085598694752507
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.5分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.090444062647896
    },
    {
        "question": " 1603兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.706190087553892
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.354012408755893
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.91億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.906984676985181
    },
    {
        "question": " 9741秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2104699752222903
    },
    {
        "question": " 733秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.86510857501679
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.85兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9565895911770403
    },
    {
        "question": " 241兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.445090431739683
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.785620026356256
    },
    {
        "question": " 1602億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.426505839935608
    },
    {
        "question": " 125万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.098137349533827
    },
    {
        "question": " 274msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.437720242548465
    },
    {
        "question": " 294msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.468662068257755
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.64垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.922319460365554
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.43京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.598372156533062
    },
    {
        "question": " 3618億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.002191902274734
    },
    {
        "question": " 156兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.415711003948525
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.32億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8005139180581384
    },
    {
        "question": " 759万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.880242585664979
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.8usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.824595141034434
    },
    {
        "question": " 2131京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8296827090713697
    },
    {
        "question": " 7625兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9457629159697953
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.3京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.828644801079727
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.250133259912567
    },
    {
        "question": " 5755億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7600416726013464
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.89兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.689627992583866
    },
    {
        "question": " 799万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.9024149831959476
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.112676172757959
    },
    {
        "question": " 2395年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.100001868601574
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.4億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3742155308966995
    },
    {
        "question": " 107万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.411365413117771
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.5万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0351466174023949
    },
    {
        "question": " 2551万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.026566414551624
    },
    {
        "question": " 3663時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.342025970521668
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.940477960528316
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.2兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.697283402021031
    },
    {
        "question": " 211万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.166638588552515
    },
    {
        "question": " 63億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.020873159662692
    },
    {
        "question": " 6672分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.602408426166892
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.77京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.179327324929577
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.200966324442792
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.55兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.375527522885085
    },
    {
        "question": " 1389億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.364601566844259
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.046811840925996
    },
    {
        "question": " 501億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2010640005264519
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18684510958762224
    },
    {
        "question": " 379億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.022091596430487
    },
    {
        "question": " 128億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.327552329740409
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.2万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6256575598989116
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.121075318954937
    },
    {
        "question": " 4166msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.619735565742548
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.44京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.888667017939622
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.138418108918805
    },
    {
        "question": " 294京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.911323326717405
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.88兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.059217363340116
    },
    {
        "question": " 8181兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.91279154509361
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.226391101286358
    },
    {
        "question": " 8711垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.441268758691534
    },
    {
        "question": " 511京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.772113077237874
    },
    {
        "question": " 4820京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.126789739973075
    },
    {
        "question": " 131京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.33817872966095
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.201305683398721
    },
    {
        "question": " 6426億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.80795022046047
    },
    {
        "question": " 1677億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.224612316029772
    },
    {
        "question": " 509万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.268740680823505
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.4万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.820138474900883
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.41億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.81930694342156
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.952806179711847
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.9日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.397706225265892
    },
    {
        "question": " 8274億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.975221173646723
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.098074777427556
    },
    {
        "question": " 6883万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.615920625519998
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.02万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.862631563151018
    },
    {
        "question": " 1920億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.562742069134346
    },
    {
        "question": " 2374万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.217040863071899
    },
    {
        "question": " 1550万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.412104256992031
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.8分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2215236971866035
    },
    {
        "question": " 1402分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.924856233173619
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.26分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.499237833345422
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.3兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.023116709765627
    },
    {
        "question": " 208万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.381521942256243
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6680116581617055
    },
    {
        "question": " 169秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4503828518145414
    },
    {
        "question": " 4350兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.139668643158944
    },
    {
        "question": " 167億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.286641894706005
    },
    {
        "question": " 8588兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.377574982156233
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.354307358730463
    },
    {
        "question": " 2410万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.382014010704913
    },
    {
        "question": " 253msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.403912692559113
    },
    {
        "question": " 142兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6525659441793952
    },
    {
        "question": " 3061億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5493155732109534
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.17兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9443195160500646
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.8億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.090180358123982
    },
    {
        "question": " 572兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.757271304920849
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.0717185689189512
    },
    {
        "question": " 103usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.01420902559798
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.71京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07020014992925261
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.82垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.008934243323379
    },
    {
        "question": " 994兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.440904765340788
    },
    {
        "question": " 9750京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.210856696994771
    },
    {
        "question": " 2454兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.389895903361556
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.1319157747862425
    },
    {
        "question": " 101億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.004260255080825
    },
    {
        "question": " 2634万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.982892913788454
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.133965080820766
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6643985263225591
    },
    {
        "question": " 774万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.269074995889117
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.185710167270542
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.98日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.536226612978835
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.11億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.550775250309581
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.2万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.501905060452305
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.8時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2526170864943893
    },
    {
        "question": " 89万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22860703401833438
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.19万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6331195095361484
    },
    {
        "question": " 113万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.276173029730348
    },
    {
        "question": " 209億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8220006003202047
    },
    {
        "question": " 103万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0755444270837822
    },
    {
        "question": " 6983秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2877434222585784
    },
    {
        "question": " 1228秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3111907295612468
    },
    {
        "question": " 1029京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.513482653712652
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.8兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.663369260654751
    },
    {
        "question": " 137兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.580407691370537
    },
    {
        "question": " 163億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.43469931663542
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.94兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.693783094662985
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.43万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.646737567416741
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6095813813981925
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0848740745264625
    },
    {
        "question": " 205億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7559399400395084
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.1京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.63845409813126
    },
    {
        "question": " 2011兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.303337205064528
    },
    {
        "question": " 101億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.0027615066617
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.175e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.838632906355677
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.1京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.870123224063687
    },
    {
        "question": " 1633兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6567401182625128
    },
    {
        "question": " 3504京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.76636483348163
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.61京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.664093948217849
    },
    {
        "question": " 102億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.0076092872081395
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.106398930384902
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.18万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3533516300575865
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.036284822033947
    },
    {
        "question": " 3119万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.931664866865496
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.518502647438382
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.21138822974501537
    },
    {
        "question": " 2798時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0665773541619314
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.4万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.362906045858524
    },
    {
        "question": " 236万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.929160127295232
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.38兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.920492867873493
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.882833678486021
    },
    {
        "question": " 2105分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5450118979612626
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.16分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.491182243777849
    },
    {
        "question": " 8858分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.725483368950655
    },
    {
        "question": " 306兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.986533527459518
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.285697865454691
    },
    {
        "question": " 20万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7450260692015096
    },
    {
        "question": " 112秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2715063422672759
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.9秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.378072446641568
    },
    {
        "question": " 711京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.353311858674799
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.122879962868653
    },
    {
        "question": " 7251兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.304121921482958
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.9億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.634768230269662
    },
    {
        "question": " 235億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.37032952359689
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.126225797775072
    },
    {
        "question": " 506京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.205451428105627
    },
    {
        "question": " 1222億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1507025328828282
    },
    {
        "question": " 5527兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.186179940077955
    },
    {
        "question": " 2962億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.693450489853942
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.142773702956732
    },
    {
        "question": " 1550億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.190450596389725
    },
    {
        "question": " 521垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.218308247060682
    },
    {
        "question": " 818兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9764417381626278
    },
    {
        "question": " 330兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9621096818937145
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.3兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.948657486934657
    },
    {
        "question": " 6826億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8341832953748436
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.206477396980967
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.07400832932867
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.89万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.631406175130632
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.81年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.665436641497494
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5676226334217103
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.1日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9497519452279954
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.6万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.975189377272274
    },
    {
        "question": " 386日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.523510441540625
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.5万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7695244797426024
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.6万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4807817037572475
    },
    {
        "question": " 443時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.424386536353165
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.7万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.479124055022236
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.5億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9737525920412997
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.37万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7094012140792825
    },
    {
        "question": " 20万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5237949378635625
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.84万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.231275332592077
    },
    {
        "question": " 592億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.273212057811107
    },
    {
        "question": " 312億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.558186813141147
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.878559141180117
    },
    {
        "question": " 430秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8556227644520698
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.4843251494623084
    },
    {
        "question": " 2554億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9085039275196838
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.477146082770139
    },
    {
        "question": " 417万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06372618909009531
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.4万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1531482272666138
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.064974215937853
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.212018437971636
    },
    {
        "question": " 2412msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.382373247634964
    },
    {
        "question": " 719垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.358004139854902
    },
    {
        "question": " 1021億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07256147225820908
    },
    {
        "question": " 5693億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.199023304269595
    },
    {
        "question": " 4714兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.895263303379984
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.5兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.406999667225925
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.348691735296828
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.53usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.5473372097542946
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.939752936832554
    },
    {
        "question": " 1195兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1410095791740804
    },
    {
        "question": " 144兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.600924146505709
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.261704357754416
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.5億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6482239589364991
    },
    {
        "question": " 2441億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.387547016762072
    },
    {
        "question": " 230億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.361683270576997
    },
    {
        "question": " 590年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.71337599014281
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.7年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.319219124506828
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.03億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.918645710292694
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.8日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.921668710057731
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.236630356822848
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.9億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.081536087232402
    },
    {
        "question": " 2158万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.112201828547743
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.819175770057277
    },
    {
        "question": " 1548兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.469161308906004
    },
    {
        "question": " 1055万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.864997127591261
    },
    {
        "question": " 1823億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.482637854130939
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.4分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1826886854052896
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.919957462072087
    },
    {
        "question": " 1209億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.583657674891608
    },
    {
        "question": " 767億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.948226919009593
    },
    {
        "question": " 6263秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24050975745270597
    },
    {
        "question": " 158万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.420397773992349
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.2秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.920007583145532
    },
    {
        "question": " 192秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.284249845371004
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.52兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3772677640317665
    },
    {
        "question": " 5858兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.831230850596013
    },
    {
        "question": " 2382億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.820600234854977
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.6万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7734053642592276
    },
    {
        "question": " 101億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.004401083358825
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.34msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.637550191808442
    },
    {
        "question": " 6319msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.800665307508433
    },
    {
        "question": " 4867兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1884961807499783
    },
    {
        "question": " 6299億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8627636389091042
    },
    {
        "question": " 2053億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7561113264271044
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.8兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5984376899324015
    },
    {
        "question": " 38億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5797037911394747
    },
    {
        "question": " 108億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.031506770027342
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.41150867305678
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.11垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.114773316940562
    },
    {
        "question": " 626京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.860245483089569
    },
    {
        "question": " 286垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.90028485459537
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.39京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.194324418019965
    },
    {
        "question": " 4714億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6734111876934543
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.8億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.9021883437119262
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.8億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.928160868204499
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.2年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.443970929373208
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.33万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.465224196931292
    },
    {
        "question": " 223年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.846616560313176
    },
    {
        "question": " 2551億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.844459695220174
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.1万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.309885890920419
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.4日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.603411169262752
    },
    {
        "question": " 1423万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2107349440509947
    },
    {
        "question": " 845万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.54642664073118
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0044697409209062
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.7万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.228123868818205
    },
    {
        "question": " 660万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.098815141242837
    },
    {
        "question": " 6915分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6814224832469595
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3515459415792375
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.73万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.536212770851428
    },
    {
        "question": " 668兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.326232352308181
    },
    {
        "question": " 1639億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.278201967530672
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.5億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.279127344742013
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.7億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.494661019104689
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.3万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.996841817834264
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.92秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.950248762641827
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.564513485977893
    },
    {
        "question": " 1091億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1012518623524334
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.96億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.041397871005397
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.32646645996266
    },
    {
        "question": " 292億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.465707392360358
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.082978728583976
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5568457454541793
    },
    {
        "question": " 1206億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14498801070984224
    },
    {
        "question": " 200億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7451152605441425
    },
    {
        "question": " 7910万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12000223234847507
    },
    {
        "question": " 6110万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7860461021079521
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.53万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6559959820391035
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.17万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.50135548369058
    },
    {
        "question": " 181京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7577897691251554
    },
    {
        "question": " 260京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.479117151752979
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.05垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.225476194442454
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.71京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.894569322110258
    },
    {
        "question": " 3563兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.551851418698869
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.42兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.92518505087075
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.4万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.616938360923533
    },
    {
        "question": " 1952年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.85279097428093
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.8年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.75410678103181
    },
    {
        "question": " 6388年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.526017351772248
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.97兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.732676289750056
    },
    {
        "question": " 255万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.786616032704464
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.300624500129093
    },
    {
        "question": " 233万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4242958053274943
    },
    {
        "question": " 585時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.387026484403563
    },
    {
        "question": " 5078時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.262014982871382
    },
    {
        "question": " 380時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.136628090035625
    },
    {
        "question": " 2077万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5968619976938059
    },
    {
        "question": " 8736分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7829525981860896
    },
    {
        "question": " 645億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.031268144226768
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.81万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.460469877492079
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.83京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.084955181234767
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.2億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.543058193147398
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.51兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.98894938334349
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.9秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10188559474275105
    },
    {
        "question": " 5675秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.7539595203780936
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.37秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.867680334579516
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.74兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3901019445193117
    },
    {
        "question": " 325兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.575378356932395
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.557944816908888
    },
    {
        "question": " 419万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8437375881204943
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.9万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7845048578648
    },
    {
        "question": " 610msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.785614587253009
    },
    {
        "question": " 2976msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.47370149043617
    },
    {
        "question": " 367垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.065856910432856
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3765146215383617
    },
    {
        "question": " 7932億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3430941002939476
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.393529290918055
    },
    {
        "question": " 101万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0033744637167665292
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.033394289597125
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7687924863821038
    },
    {
        "question": " 304京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.546826511771259
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.6垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.22652507696111
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2745031477744706
    },
    {
        "question": " 585兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.767349635995227
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.1兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.592331588154574
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.15597312973832
    },
    {
        "question": " 5万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2616375391396275
    },
    {
        "question": " 1433年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0986436427818775
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.9年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.002505236675333
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.846216262225976
    },
    {
        "question": " 4263日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.009940468768967
    },
    {
        "question": " 4361日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.797937986894677
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.7日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.608612062109419
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.1万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9658614621832784
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.836251155674587
    },
    {
        "question": " 262時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.195860825510744
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.8時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.262495384630951
    },
    {
        "question": " 431万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9139023958992709
    },
    {
        "question": " 2065分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15655692154761036
    },
    {
        "question": " 947億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.198014442608748
    },
    {
        "question": " 288分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.237360423712082
    },
    {
        "question": " 172分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.01251412650079
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.31京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.22657364536576
    },
    {
        "question": " 712億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.915965809485245
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.76億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.273603009470297
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.6億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.64676608705256
    },
    {
        "question": " 1369秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.13631969968287
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.2124083348391865
    },
    {
        "question": " 9898兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.496761358458652
    },
    {
        "question": " 1592兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2653401936223325
    },
    {
        "question": " 728兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.305656842605213
    },
    {
        "question": " 334兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.74541597445299
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.66億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.985194123641038
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.4万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.647151275709847
    },
    {
        "question": " 1310msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.117161976309601
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7299901894558274
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3342301408432915
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.1京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.936591061974502
    },
    {
        "question": " 317兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.723330872370984
    },
    {
        "question": " 979万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9909914252825602
    },
    {
        "question": " 112万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.0498195364196867
    },
    {
        "question": " 1576usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.19743087589443
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.4垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.406311916308628
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1896004105407014
    },
    {
        "question": " 128垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.550044736955856
    },
    {
        "question": " 1184兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.29522653666333
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.9兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.689501655110943
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.140409505723787
    },
    {
        "question": " 628億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.798262721778953
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9318703781815882
    },
    {
        "question": " 264年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.36392813015077
    },
    {
        "question": " 1636日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6513590096022037
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.392126510291031
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.3日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.637759870099982
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.14兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.845948238279354
    },
    {
        "question": " 6163時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.409558764262536
    },
    {
        "question": " 3466万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.317917682802989
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.01万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.401788734424848
    },
    {
        "question": " 150時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.733092927868126
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.736884127531656
    },
    {
        "question": " 559億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.026995049500268
    },
    {
        "question": " 818万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.754255555900008
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.71万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7908335285356936
    },
    {
        "question": " 6079万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.561979468283972
    },
    {
        "question": " 8455分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.705273169047453
    },
    {
        "question": " 120億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.579449096987111
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1792444291932354
    },
    {
        "question": " 5664秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19682930035757384
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.5万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9075069232810855
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.03万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.481497383694777
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.3秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.349275553639645
    },
    {
        "question": " 105兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5235849094569662
    },
    {
        "question": " 396兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.661293972230251
    },
    {
        "question": " 233兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.811939520256296
    },
    {
        "question": " 3092億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.712152832264817
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.1億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.612501215058943
    },
    {
        "question": " 64万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.806145318681601
    },
    {
        "question": " 387京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0894279758860055
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.78垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.508150718370086
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.3兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.245109707499926
    },
    {
        "question": " 18兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.477998194164517
    },
    {
        "question": " 2662億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.425183547021806
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.23兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.626151084930974
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7872070206879984
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.584082502100986
    },
    {
        "question": " 178京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.693168289669259
    },
    {
        "question": " 4844兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.907097537233556
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.9京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.378666984011096
    },
    {
        "question": " 1323万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.121529356315979
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.4億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.657191481778632
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.64年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.384169672559585
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.5年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8721447004409
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.771520319941067
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.452300273790275
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.716051540991794
    },
    {
        "question": " 869日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.097527437430169
    },
    {
        "question": " 1667億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.279465505789196
    },
    {
        "question": " 2102万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.942535170878449
    },
    {
        "question": " 3252時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.290333301539098
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.75時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.315798460742492
    },
    {
        "question": " 2103時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.879149617880527
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.7億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.929689682258275
    },
    {
        "question": " 5321分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5676420384556979
    },
    {
        "question": " 3040億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.704693887299252
    },
    {
        "question": " 6596分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.597435570511839
    },
    {
        "question": " 6632兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.322815863865527
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1193525891373659
    },
    {
        "question": " 511万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1519897590371437
    },
    {
        "question": " 2365秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5957420778604403
    },
    {
        "question": " 30万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.477320412020003
    },
    {
        "question": " 1466兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.66724966583754
    },
    {
        "question": " 8300兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.982566630792649
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.912435624665616
    },
    {
        "question": " 2869億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.679592091119449
    },
    {
        "question": " 2895万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.461656803647337
    },
    {
        "question": " 6041京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.28233510921706
    },
    {
        "question": " 1956億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3549792255843953
    },
    {
        "question": " 136億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5779730752402334
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.7京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.789959188744191
    },
    {
        "question": " 1916兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.282327275155158
    },
    {
        "question": " 160億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.203050941578604
    },
    {
        "question": " 2755垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.941294279894683
    },
    {
        "question": " 6995垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.908306452834546
    },
    {
        "question": " 4269京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.07397612531936
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.05京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.178611389608106
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.278849591902675
    },
    {
        "question": " 287万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.45783975293422485
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.448618829396079
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.740684776636194
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.23年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.230004607101492
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.4億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9206205530006315
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.5万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.924393104417012
    },
    {
        "question": " 308日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6467225998079495
    },
    {
        "question": " 101億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.063317201102215
    },
    {
        "question": " 148億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.79150178713515
    },
    {
        "question": " 3410時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0890414604876595
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.762237397472386
    },
    {
        "question": " 472兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.953127369335402
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.81万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6747153623869726
    },
    {
        "question": " 2979分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6959066991896754
    },
    {
        "question": " 521分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.494589714787257
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.15京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.11940477014646
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.3万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0470584710613007
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.675131689689287
    },
    {
        "question": " 833秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.142308775787505
    },
    {
        "question": " 920万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.963712643868028
    },
    {
        "question": " 9730京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.48932804118962
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.7億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.73546890287153
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8939864629931713
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.16万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13343627541139713
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.389871981951184
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.5msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.351304595467841
    },
    {
        "question": " 116msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.063936994953423
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.06京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.987058989189916
    },
    {
        "question": " 2822億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.513995874031038
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.870507865862297
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.21億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8459795503468615
    },
    {
        "question": " 168兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.226384448035052
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.205928620622785
    },
    {
        "question": " 522usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.717427324905979
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.022e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.510765007446556
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0967852509882974
    },
    {
        "question": " 2328京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8107305912146545
    },
    {
        "question": " 479兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.902179956725357
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.7京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.855649427362675
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.3180098436247505
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.210141588534256
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.34993361146605
    },
    {
        "question": " 359年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.27535305722478
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.9万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1692092631874367
    },
    {
        "question": " 38万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.960135495974575
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.31万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.022342778842402
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.5日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.639597592327815
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0661175014309967
    },
    {
        "question": " 63万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.419366995979007
    },
    {
        "question": " 4533万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.43448820713567
    },
    {
        "question": " 1503億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.456304287487796
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.2万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3752316633895845
    },
    {
        "question": " 1275億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.327474722585563
    },
    {
        "question": " 366万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.34123596280105
    },
    {
        "question": " 174億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.740774906117114
    },
    {
        "question": " 1224万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.151300577659198
    },
    {
        "question": " 373億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.015210430256278
    },
    {
        "question": " 127秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3253223728168986
    },
    {
        "question": " 215万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.333242942976206
    },
    {
        "question": " 342億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03468474309197611
    },
    {
        "question": " 407兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.673435471447672
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6306029141397371
    },
    {
        "question": " 239万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6008556559351172
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.312805866645212
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.088282325663309
    },
    {
        "question": " 1491垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.67469117673283
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.2京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4291172125229314
    },
    {
        "question": " 193兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.730132309031696
    },
    {
        "question": " 28京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.668788582590759
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.25億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.62839703893384
    },
    {
        "question": " 3513億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.545672920450238
    },
    {
        "question": " 32万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.505372960076235
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.7京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1216214682689185
    },
    {
        "question": " 6327京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.864684577077112
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.535455480159857
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.54京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.626378731985744
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.1億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.38234092657162044
    },
    {
        "question": " 270兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.431983972408208
    },
    {
        "question": " 1178億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.071264662056478
    },
    {
        "question": " 169万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.78894639330375
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.9年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.44614145415634
    },
    {
        "question": " 110年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.763332771551388
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.5年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.334520968062415
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.87万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0253477041025727
    },
    {
        "question": " 6021日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9380192194613555
    },
    {
        "question": " 95日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.914429144771507
    },
    {
        "question": " 143万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2115438670317156
    },
    {
        "question": " 3467万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.159743941136328
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.004484861754438
    },
    {
        "question": " 592時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3289777151560305
    },
    {
        "question": " 3375万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8076278512969313
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.42兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.375475079264614
    },
    {
        "question": " 162万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.431754830995639
    },
    {
        "question": " 3869分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.365778835754238
    },
    {
        "question": " 996分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.77633875631318
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7556472980454325
    },
    {
        "question": " 176億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.309725577626932
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.4万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3951378673971746
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.5億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.942259224068829
    },
    {
        "question": " 946秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.975886632272912
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.598987081109455
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.22秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.624881714136372
    },
    {
        "question": " 476億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17872383363299327
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.1億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.621461456516986
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.6兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.943459055438074
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.76兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.051911290930883
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.222526414449373
    },
    {
        "question": " 183万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.261356780647395
    },
    {
        "question": " 308msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.489044166119502
    },
    {
        "question": " 1546兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6905297752544834
    },
    {
        "question": " 626京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.859801253510143
    },
    {
        "question": " 2518兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.844780044067552
    },
    {
        "question": " 8134万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1321431139407203
    },
    {
        "question": " 5351兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.72839494844547
    },
    {
        "question": " 4759usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.6774729470415786
    },
    {
        "question": " 486京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.188220040564591
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.2兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04193150218510744
    },
    {
        "question": " 689兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2816691833023803
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.76兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8995664379318278
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.4京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.808795000231749
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.39兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.530098551555494
    },
    {
        "question": " 2500億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.397950251557551
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.7年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.212872092614673
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.903959412762367
    },
    {
        "question": " 510万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.145384231172776
    },
    {
        "question": " 3605万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.937145569872646
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.89万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.0552458546028
    },
    {
        "question": " 536日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.665604003610552
    },
    {
        "question": " 8762万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.00011508910315
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.6万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.227834998211892
    },
    {
        "question": " 639万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.58366602345159
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.821175878669557
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.974676198104191
    },
    {
        "question": " 966兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.264515103603204
    },
    {
        "question": " 1689億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.06933740475593
    },
    {
        "question": " 3920万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.815178818620451
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0026260609039523
    },
    {
        "question": " 65分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.591080924698823
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.923400248028312
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.532029039633267
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.5万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5178154640389987
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.38兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.17419868976302
    },
    {
        "question": " 575億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.981424632569261
    },
    {
        "question": " 1072秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.03002058932126
    },
    {
        "question": " 5577京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.247605343766388
    },
    {
        "question": " 214億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.393020308185415
    },
    {
        "question": " 184兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.709086944555049
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.44000121207144804
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.223330997071046
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.2msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.909504850584164
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.43京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.309349528175518
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.05京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.766641681843891
    },
    {
        "question": " 187京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.715461658736608
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.1京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.856701893995494
    },
    {
        "question": " 17億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2302022573080045
    },
    {
        "question": " 1898万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.278381043660957
    },
    {
        "question": " 2626usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.41935664631161
    },
    {
        "question": " 201垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.803586402163502
    },
    {
        "question": " 190兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.34204640588590407
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.547065505868827
    },
    {
        "question": " 158兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.421635978802983
    },
    {
        "question": " 830京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.918955753314119
    },
    {
        "question": " 427兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.630249963208076
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.93億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.4672996220821135
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.628512268374951
    },
    {
        "question": " 6586年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.761132637214271
    },
    {
        "question": " 7239年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.580312353311303
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.42億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3082744430524675
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.05856274586776
    },
    {
        "question": " 435万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6964514230715397
    },
    {
        "question": " 554万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3632374316981295
    },
    {
        "question": " 478時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.457550426941955
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.790112569596895
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.68兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.949914739092713
    },
    {
        "question": " 123万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.932242999093565
    },
    {
        "question": " 2430億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.607410672174426
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8911495893402286
    },
    {
        "question": " 1908分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.058743014415358
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.505219039495266
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5213601201090956
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.6万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.915702474501667
    },
    {
        "question": " 1802億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.477683943696608
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.266740563943782
    },
    {
        "question": " 4355京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.140161539319605
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.9億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6960548939845888
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4750795903897107
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.389582241276486
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.7億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.928088731886898
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.2117574295837192
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.2msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.4646573801721985
    },
    {
        "question": " 203兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8091093393970017
    },
    {
        "question": " 534兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.790962081597727
    },
    {
        "question": " 513兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.154138612681244
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.493215016898617
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.426893362120289
    },
    {
        "question": " 1076万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.031976600009621
    },
    {
        "question": " 476usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.677185136086942
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.388e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.36970764587266
    },
    {
        "question": " 266垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.487829370631927
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.48京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0945051556975445
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.8京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.212324758298654
    },
    {
        "question": " 203兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.308311885770758
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.021422472138256
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.41兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.38213693191922
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.67年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.25238103812447
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.3万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.188446850344784
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.449708227967794
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.59万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.491151701384236
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.294956672237323
    },
    {
        "question": " 366億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.183754822263205
    },
    {
        "question": " 96万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7604334128290775
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.4時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.194193414492334
    },
    {
        "question": " 1497億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.454551643582693
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1446507753592146
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.4億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.973342319140735
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.862251701103691
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.4億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8313382237936582
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.88万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05836216706222919
    },
    {
        "question": " 3868万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.031181396824665
    },
    {
        "question": " 491億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.912812120826931
    },
    {
        "question": " 5378秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.730632875364513
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6511470499555045
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.02兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.909798899808026
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.53兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.846160037319059
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.54万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03764190394354383
    },
    {
        "question": " 7087億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.850474544063005
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.7msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.660184204535179
    },
    {
        "question": " 1949兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7910009104835123
    },
    {
        "question": " 5376億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7939274700869337
    },
    {
        "question": " 161兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.651732707694958
    },
    {
        "question": " 3780億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7993782964212217
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.13221638855157
    },
    {
        "question": " 2264万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.354807043805488
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.5usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.332586076529355
    },
    {
        "question": " 8608京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.436091193745703
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.1京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.344156049750792
    },
    {
        "question": " 3955京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.040858858969004
    },
    {
        "question": " 2846京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.676145326248024
    },
    {
        "question": " 7738億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8886074460373576
    },
    {
        "question": " 359兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.554599888444313
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.0887319488616787
    },
    {
        "question": " 1170万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.630355653716917
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.096188669697985
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.48兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.831788303445473
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.6万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.162520583975996
    },
    {
        "question": " 137日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.29515853115733
    },
    {
        "question": " 401日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.540020940525512
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.35億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.696222095462176
    },
    {
        "question": " 2284万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.978495806879448
    },
    {
        "question": " 181時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.813976327077518
    },
    {
        "question": " 1357兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.411907190024081
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.54兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.773017175362517
    },
    {
        "question": " 520万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9374617581464095
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.7万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.188897768895826
    },
    {
        "question": " 6014兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.28035143569198
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.5兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.024907417452638
    },
    {
        "question": " 376万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.019099763869295
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7790541960782322
    },
    {
        "question": " 292秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.465237692235691
    },
    {
        "question": " 1154兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.563390389723292
    },
    {
        "question": " 111兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.108747345558444
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.26京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.957043181398797
    },
    {
        "question": " 88億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.166545169138339
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.72兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.570914979862323
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.6msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.712310421374759
    },
    {
        "question": " 116兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5650751453000258
    },
    {
        "question": " 274京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.501597289996975
    },
    {
        "question": " 165兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.661914172076283
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.447479756151242
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.86兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.686846613066113
    },
    {
        "question": " 130億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.1155086716883265
    },
    {
        "question": " 2141垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.831856322578941
    },
    {
        "question": " 236垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.43658854269593
    },
    {
        "question": " 53京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.168337025483304
    },
    {
        "question": " 7423京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.092448321685962
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.2億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9203377600536622
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.03億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.701352116844399
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.385549887897241
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.758607147591615
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.82758683993702
    },
    {
        "question": " 3208万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.886479200110152
    },
    {
        "question": " 670日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.98474493666571
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.5万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6760692957195333
    },
    {
        "question": " 214億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.950844752940714
    },
    {
        "question": " 691時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.617775652800615
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.4時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.213580950098074
    },
    {
        "question": " 726万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1404882658153026
    },
    {
        "question": " 1780億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.092083654583277
    },
    {
        "question": " 512万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.931308101356563
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8196639220187127
    },
    {
        "question": " 4739分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.453839957964902
    },
    {
        "question": " 32兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.006828577461364
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.1億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8424847444303065
    },
    {
        "question": " 2596億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.85800258881479
    },
    {
        "question": " 2003秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5234231299350531
    },
    {
        "question": " 4520秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.655161722250803
    },
    {
        "question": " 7124秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.852748717178093
    },
    {
        "question": " 912億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4610334252072923
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.1億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.644993448428299
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.4億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.753887724087618
    },
    {
        "question": " 704億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.069284090063175
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.77億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.89034249372064
    },
    {
        "question": " 447msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.650717423387915
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.4京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.494030013407463
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5002422945357874
    },
    {
        "question": " 353兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.991037574995826
    },
    {
        "question": " 1926兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.506526265586391
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.2兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.465318479551518
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.87億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.836654433492262
    },
    {
        "question": " 405万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.607811723119248
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.7京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1213317650154908
    },
    {
        "question": " 365兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6257382119591226
    },
    {
        "question": " 140京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.589493672374363
    },
    {
        "question": " 2504億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.620437511811972
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.4京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.535962454936652
    },
    {
        "question": " 3730億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.571758585377778
    },
    {
        "question": " 4764nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.6779685691622828
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.882192881780032
    },
    {
        "question": " 392万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0307285568885245
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8308496796239493
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.35日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.665102501921591
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.16484217896513
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.82011612337788
    },
    {
        "question": " 433万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.41492698927538
    },
    {
        "question": " 376万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8542797124029311
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.96億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.536874707711216
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.2億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.84486558501051
    },
    {
        "question": " 797万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.679422797220754
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.2分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.535317392165277
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.5分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.463489931417502
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.60878227488773
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.8億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.337394913511367
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5749123077285812
    },
    {
        "question": " 3563万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.773721022168996
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.2289869332571115
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6352169573260023
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.82京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.64560318751591
    },
    {
        "question": " 1048億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.464253996217311
    },
    {
        "question": " 7320億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.086388634907084
    },
    {
        "question": " 109億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.039165110817497
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.674741326075816
    },
    {
        "question": " 2010msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.303240427370683
    },
    {
        "question": " 775京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3907553040626075
    },
    {
        "question": " 15兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2397025416443817
    },
    {
        "question": " 238京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.82030836484507
    },
    {
        "question": " 1076兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2537282843439135
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.289476748351125
    },
    {
        "question": " 364万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.5609718258098755
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.5万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.398037974655507
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.8京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0668566148531344
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3058309028722923
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.59京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.190963107278112
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.13垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.717337365410721
    },
    {
        "question": " 2490兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.396254918952233
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.5億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.946864107127386
    },
    {
        "question": " 2786nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.44499085693972984
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.49年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1045633463151647
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.156936956087256
    },
    {
        "question": " 6454年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.530487283939616
    },
    {
        "question": " 283億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8899999589488035
    },
    {
        "question": " 60万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.158513369728444
    },
    {
        "question": " 2438日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.545320073851546
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.4日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.563442078378112
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.6万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7201893222632549
    },
    {
        "question": " 732時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4845257387952104
    },
    {
        "question": " 419万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.40016029682025
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.44万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.365447936573851
    },
    {
        "question": " 4029億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.884582104439815
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.9万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1614087293876816
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.37100505559564
    },
    {
        "question": " 6892分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.616500548977264
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.4億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.267712965402333
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.436323147385308
    },
    {
        "question": " 246億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.834570974479357
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.2億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.080244054461135
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.41秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.382276885870006
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.1669540553226625
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.549536864191344
    },
    {
        "question": " 147億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.230145754759109
    },
    {
        "question": " 7492億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.318297232601404
    },
    {
        "question": " 218億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.559796418498454
    },
    {
        "question": " 1740億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.240439984483569
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.214138284367062
    },
    {
        "question": " 1449msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.161076151153187
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.51京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4313352140874622
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.76兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.006135190933386
    },
    {
        "question": " 3790兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.022346731572773
    },
    {
        "question": " 2609億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.638305258411351
    },
    {
        "question": " 3390兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.530177245611549
    },
    {
        "question": " 169万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.227902127999821
    },
    {
        "question": " 2539usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.4047437365459
    },
    {
        "question": " 2093京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.82207011704936
    },
    {
        "question": " 7570垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.942574403084842
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.1垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.936466324532521
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.8京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.666272328690441
    },
    {
        "question": " 627京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.797208508161908
    },
    {
        "question": " 208億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.318911456789046
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.115572414503524
    },
    {
        "question": " 1088万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.598974199541535
    },
    {
        "question": " 129年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.053217174078567
    },
    {
        "question": " 7026億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.28441039035047
    },
    {
        "question": " 1524日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.563160538211443
    },
    {
        "question": " 1189日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.011690629134803
    },
    {
        "question": " 330万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5760620827402683
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.629549506426631
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.9時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.262855252034586
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.42時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.481524458792256
    },
    {
        "question": " 66億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.098572739358422
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.26889896101596
    },
    {
        "question": " 9340万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.192173878389104
    },
    {
        "question": " 515万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.490229996974314
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.35分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.303835319161076
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.808009677282076
    },
    {
        "question": " 6027億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.843583949360703
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.4兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.824375181964507
    },
    {
        "question": " 2848億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.67633991472068
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.2秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.925376198444901
    },
    {
        "question": " 617秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.790455092488465
    },
    {
        "question": " 1911兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.782349343515271
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.374312536127677
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.85633114451086
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.669514132466123
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1430830483556653
    },
    {
        "question": " 4444京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.149012289228106
    },
    {
        "question": " 591兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8350050279339287
    },
    {
        "question": " 3379兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.97251487781949
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.52京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.200535301178439
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.025789391866292
    },
    {
        "question": " 786億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.895436023731738
    },
    {
        "question": " 30万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.476653110264063
    },
    {
        "question": " 703垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.348428547173025
    },
    {
        "question": " 148京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.232721401082826
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.739947908738566
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.36京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.950650051614498
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.37京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.922692776746464
    },
    {
        "question": " 1873兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.27254412157616
    },
    {
        "question": " 1344億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.128379047597145
    },
    {
        "question": " 342年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.096928801432164
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.8年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.195861154045167
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.2億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.803597293280379
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.2日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.21416086803872
    },
    {
        "question": " 235万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.529111708842539
    },
    {
        "question": " 952日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9150301766613795
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.532284273962817
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.99億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.095541233551898
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.46時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3169788544871492
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.807979985856152
    },
    {
        "question": " 184億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.544869225908473
    },
    {
        "question": " 5333分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5685895871773261
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4978478665046735
    },
    {
        "question": " 3048分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.262116223103284
    },
    {
        "question": " 2450分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.167291376727178
    },
    {
        "question": " 3305億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.020368572128304
    },
    {
        "question": " 375億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.637902088580484
    },
    {
        "question": " 4153秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06210804475832332
    },
    {
        "question": " 27億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.653134075706827
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.82万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.834075674133583
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.5兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.343139327982123
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.43京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.038146077542923
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.8兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.085382462618219
    },
    {
        "question": " 1863万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4920592035309
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.37335971832306
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.8msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.9385088834859845
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.7兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3380622292914437
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.3兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7194502034700383
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6085324727583714
    },
    {
        "question": " 9541万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2014334160024578
    },
    {
        "question": " 836億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.922079568709642
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.1554262294953277
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.27usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.5143792668433917
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.81垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0815616375357315
    },
    {
        "question": " 115垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.122661718974907
    },
    {
        "question": " 1153兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5053456616215564
    },
    {
        "question": " 244京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.609285278799337
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.148887639665306
    },
    {
        "question": " 3463億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.53946011280958
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.7万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.8372075654961604
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.24万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.912435369158275
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.6年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6019017088140135
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.784954480462925
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.11年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.991650824634191
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.684047068027592
    },
    {
        "question": " 577日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.141200194015566
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.5日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.135902312486449
    },
    {
        "question": " 733日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.801308138187779
    },
    {
        "question": " 321万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.563382757465371
    },
    {
        "question": " 4162万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.23913996727325
    },
    {
        "question": " 1739時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.018500031160004
    },
    {
        "question": " 115万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.618188073482383
    },
    {
        "question": " 460時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.218971073505665
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.496238982310281
    },
    {
        "question": " 4793万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.522256112438878
    },
    {
        "question": " 1546万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.41095701991508
    },
    {
        "question": " 691分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.617452702417729
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.02分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.082858835220603
    },
    {
        "question": " 3703万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06979100495520085
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.32万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.033052297093706384
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.714093098001763
    },
    {
        "question": " 5195秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9373958725053764
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.2278784911958636
    },
    {
        "question": " 1933秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.286169085316446
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.808954794326202
    },
    {
        "question": " 2942兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.532189423182113
    },
    {
        "question": " 370億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.01186358971326
    },
    {
        "question": " 5465万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.959470753694381
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.95万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7746564160671752
    },
    {
        "question": " 2068msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.315458366021947
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.188411836505311
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.47京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4775864293536243
    },
    {
        "question": " 142京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.217266644459373
    },
    {
        "question": " 100億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4436892519961577
    },
    {
        "question": " 1866兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.492829474320919
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3021929752983703
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.6万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.5870206999694223
    },
    {
        "question": " 104usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.015925363781387
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.352e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.422982261210137
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.68垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6295173346590754
    },
    {
        "question": " 4488京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.095731383794285
    },
    {
        "question": " 8923兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.172378824294998
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.3兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.559842559702819
    },
    {
        "question": " 783億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.89392194344128
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.82兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.58258919043054
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.8万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.531282050618701
    },
    {
        "question": " 4463年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.370250520999326
    },
    {
        "question": " 1140万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.494486871200315
    },
    {
        "question": " 9399万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.353294945917172
    },
    {
        "question": " 130日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.050134496756529
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.72億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.73177792609745
    },
    {
        "question": " 1645億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.835924721870999
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.4万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.216648111669846
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.4万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.30789522735924
    },
    {
        "question": " 4640兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.945835012000284
    },
    {
        "question": " 7874億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.737845974154375
    },
    {
        "question": " 6731分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.04990017928099
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9031859404939855
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.39分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.510034706132165
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.4兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.384468969139824
    },
    {
        "question": " 240兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.443506921512054
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5812118492882257
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.2万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8371864132505995
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.1万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.624272611136686
    },
    {
        "question": " 731秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.86370075877398
    },
    {
        "question": " 522兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.218632713059215
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.093074702387566
    },
    {
        "question": " 31兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.935598815814638
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.618469154582135
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4382274282386875
    },
    {
        "question": " 138msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.13875151601597
    },
    {
        "question": " 637京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.305385165221887
    },
    {
        "question": " 5032兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.765207174307914
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.7億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1575156717082371
    },
    {
        "question": " 352兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.768484601886802
    },
    {
        "question": " 181万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2574944853818828
    },
    {
        "question": " 130億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.114832687190066
    },
    {
        "question": " 3082usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.4887865530824325
    },
    {
        "question": " 726垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.362402322033477
    },
    {
        "question": " 6701京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.889608396823842
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.532195944649086
    },
    {
        "question": " 102京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.229199594736002
    },
    {
        "question": " 1068兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.028502319098237
    },
    {
        "question": " 445億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.648743294943608
    },
    {
        "question": " 4921nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.6920719067907677
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.76年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.620448812017805
    },
    {
        "question": " 889日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3867985149879072
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.986444172388037
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.5日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.342296577302315
    },
    {
        "question": " 164万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.271450346764788
    },
    {
        "question": " 125時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7161288644202657
    },
    {
        "question": " 1254万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.876430910602513
    },
    {
        "question": " 2633兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.699855352248584
    },
    {
        "question": " 3237分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.35183877076988224
    },
    {
        "question": " 3863億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.808789692500891
    },
    {
        "question": " 138分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9173059970731194
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.6分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.67885416391453
    },
    {
        "question": " 1688億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7285021742442104
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.87兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9594903856317565
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.5万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2795899407966305
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.247346685574727
    },
    {
        "question": " 663万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.821596465001821
    },
    {
        "question": " 4394億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.144055638449052
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.46億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.45375499507775086
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.99兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.443427950437183
    },
    {
        "question": " 67万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0482006251238118
    },
    {
        "question": " 959億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.982003941360022
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.7万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.640490004247978
    },
    {
        "question": " 444垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.14832553555526
    },
    {
        "question": " 4576京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.723987209945896
    },
    {
        "question": " 5542兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.187385023371786
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.648279626311149
    },
    {
        "question": " 1027億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.011764865094057
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.51兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.65379690203046
    },
    {
        "question": " 293万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.466387958751909
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.52京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2433590924369211
    },
    {
        "question": " 28京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.510311241131866
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5166607897328728
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.68兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8921005992767992
    },
    {
        "question": " 182兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.259005685693806
    },
    {
        "question": " 131兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.115788179583706
    },
    {
        "question": " 2328万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.366946277609261
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.741773243717633
    },
    {
        "question": " 6885日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2756172919229114
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5790397626446129
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.2万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.505396896776148
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.32012760470533
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.5万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.371883716998017
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.41時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1606014676935095
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.4時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2887517915551285
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3565551641443037
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.9兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.68026216992293
    },
    {
        "question": " 1777万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.471471857238813
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.012271440213771
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.81京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.33407250302733
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18510458134018748
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.923817350805458
    },
    {
        "question": " 1246秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3175272543792782
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.2万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.401256906569085
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.574841795053983
    },
    {
        "question": " 438億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7048683726084666
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.5兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.993394306471848
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.565654095532565
    },
    {
        "question": " 222万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.345586917176643
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.263455813620941
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.869569652645055
    },
    {
        "question": " 3034億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5454728931569941
    },
    {
        "question": " 161兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.651297291100853
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31098954271698287
    },
    {
        "question": " 9116万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9598189580861802
    },
    {
        "question": " 373万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.5713980197876216
    },
    {
        "question": " 512万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.70912078572423
    },
    {
        "question": " 1181垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.573603697917559
    },
    {
        "question": " 182兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.32278971977103277
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.22京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.237451227246676
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.5兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.153621081255207
    },
    {
        "question": " 142億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1535981255659178
    },
    {
        "question": " 170兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.231137904249401
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.25597024938748
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.748669059343753
    },
    {
        "question": " 5018億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.138217469528389
    },
    {
        "question": " 4964万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.075996131203675
    },
    {
        "question": " 2873日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.394766468716465
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.1億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.691943190756346
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.162082709484912
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.13時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.409353060656524
    },
    {
        "question": " 124時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.649923657119187
    },
    {
        "question": " 4153万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8976678228279609
    },
    {
        "question": " 1790分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09450878713695543
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.5億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.610363374981981
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.66分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6018665551421782
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.3分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.496732209211324
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.24兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.296538748632208
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.35億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8665355871756035
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.4億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1097546114754575
    },
    {
        "question": " 3736秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.794218425616545
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.27秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.721564815339419
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.5兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.890742419937491
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.57兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.616158363501165
    },
    {
        "question": " 2976万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9173790761506695
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3613098930563585
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.328924634604064
    },
    {
        "question": " 397msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.598586911526019
    },
    {
        "question": " 615京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.290130937994734
    },
    {
        "question": " 105京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0837091543049375
    },
    {
        "question": " 1151京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.50483990551151
    },
    {
        "question": " 112億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.271692252918606
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.22億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5072373807152335
    },
    {
        "question": " 1130億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.052951784612901
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.29usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.862651325931301
    },
    {
        "question": " 433京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1372106646980313
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.32垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.789199316927627
    },
    {
        "question": " 167垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.667189004036219
    },
    {
        "question": " 3150京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.720099827387786
    },
    {
        "question": " 1338兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.126549874857172
    },
    {
        "question": " 206億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.3133938421029425
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.83億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.834716622800676
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.11年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8875423283399693
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.9年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.242307403744539
    },
    {
        "question": " 330年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.239446579280287
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.673105952898945
    },
    {
        "question": " 383日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9639137238116917
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.61日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.141086278385967
    },
    {
        "question": " 905日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.893300970771201
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.24億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.406858369514982
    },
    {
        "question": " 240万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.000853655333952
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.873381482989837
    },
    {
        "question": " 495兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.974276535147412
    },
    {
        "question": " 7016億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.687755587372754
    },
    {
        "question": " 1439万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.379832158583588
    },
    {
        "question": " 162万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.986544672032032
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.15京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.999700592257344
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.423615852765028
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.4万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3540784454236596
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.8億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.799118042193268
    },
    {
        "question": " 5928秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.772939792360972
    },
    {
        "question": " 1571京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.697245110014913
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.232278732072054
    },
    {
        "question": " 4831兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.127693194736302
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.240176030202915
    },
    {
        "question": " 2398億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.379823108157506
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.18msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.7141339245649174
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.474554234225073
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.590390206361447
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.225511583968396
    },
    {
        "question": " 1778兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6935944703974615
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.99兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.175746338689943
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.126954992083625
    },
    {
        "question": " 174億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.240874609187584
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.4usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.751560541878513
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.61京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16450543972893805
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.03京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5447702045329668
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.4京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3899678503601365
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.3京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.121199380689776
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.4兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4964194836950755
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.220030083254697
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.2万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.983162085926523
    },
    {
        "question": " 1428万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.71713854344617
    },
    {
        "question": " 1153年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.782415124027498
    },
    {
        "question": " 1834億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.701023850133383
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5117292702694427
    },
    {
        "question": " 193万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.444508629907926
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.160215611682438
    },
    {
        "question": " 353億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.167645051406021
    },
    {
        "question": " 3803時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1364353448631235
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.26億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.792861439086364
    },
    {
        "question": " 1357万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9742153892604346
    },
    {
        "question": " 20億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.522556708436757
    },
    {
        "question": " 1191万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.854043165012303
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.81分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.35872699407723
    },
    {
        "question": " 1750兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.744156503224174
    },
    {
        "question": " 435兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.701967164202841
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.4兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.967501505641492
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.3億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.956380255786714
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.2206255039109513
    },
    {
        "question": " 168兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7275571356841706
    },
    {
        "question": " 263兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.48375544776434
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.6兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.083311758736777
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.450468765278932
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.88万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8377220017221807
    },
    {
        "question": " 326万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.512910603999776
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.7兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08871846026110353
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.1京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.972090342241573
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.91兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9079880405639846
    },
    {
        "question": " 7973兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.12349312299358
    },
    {
        "question": " 120万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07847218637042519
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.69万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.886144121143516
    },
    {
        "question": " 715usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.854418017359768
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.8京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.326248455437966
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2072946404996894
    },
    {
        "question": " 1834京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.70717685503969
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.8京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.787662594595284
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.207704842046888
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.24兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.627034825823788
    },
    {
        "question": " 765万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.8837777436323337
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7210609200044122
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.240133054778829
    },
    {
        "question": " 3383年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.249891620177834
    },
    {
        "question": " 296万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.908842762924629
    },
    {
        "question": " 78万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.272082537172485
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.5億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.859980904716434
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9535690197275652
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.5時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6141546947784695
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.5時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.337774674744384
    },
    {
        "question": " 688時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.394066080941124
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4065274663379
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.07974748045245
    },
    {
        "question": " 1976分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5175790897746333
    },
    {
        "question": " 1005万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.780481266046921
    },
    {
        "question": " 208分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.097129000581227
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.09分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.390120217940515
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.06億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9863473806082734
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.7兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.683266377435755
    },
    {
        "question": " 822億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3584549915749164
    },
    {
        "question": " 5404秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9545568141464431
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.23秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6262799978084823
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.54兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.050584560099499
    },
    {
        "question": " 225億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4153189282917875
    },
    {
        "question": " 1742万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6846251953309701
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.1兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.209179741350326
    },
    {
        "question": " 1057万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.024049135736242
    },
    {
        "question": " 168万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.224979613605889
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.0689108617553265
    },
    {
        "question": " 221垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.845178208072069
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.289010881634115
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.2京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.894293174208412
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.98億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9983545919297365
    },
    {
        "question": " 866万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9373369705546786
    },
    {
        "question": " 779万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.891675999130937
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.7垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.973410016763849
    },
    {
        "question": " 1302垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.178038716679474
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.99兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4434807847853661
    },
    {
        "question": " 2754京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.6617774267858
    },
    {
        "question": " 140億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1463259057961361
    },
    {
        "question": " 3612万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5577804453222244
    },
    {
        "question": " 67万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.826292196048551
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.89年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.152512195396585
    },
    {
        "question": " 31年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4334318050717005
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4411198318770815
    },
    {
        "question": " 352日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9268996197836303
    },
    {
        "question": " 206日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.47290437176362
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.3日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.402754603819866
    },
    {
        "question": " 2554億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.464720728250121
    },
    {
        "question": " 1911万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.901074272132973
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.92万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.470014010210089
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.88万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.015820924783547
    },
    {
        "question": " 188時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.830057384379314
    },
    {
        "question": " 1121万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3291018495888074
    },
    {
        "question": " 4010億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.444838227201405
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2414157321735235
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.731882012818286
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.5億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.702108210683642
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.614494768758604
    },
    {
        "question": " 384万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.806227550194313
    },
    {
        "question": " 78万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.892279493803075
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.755039129076168
    },
    {
        "question": " 369億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.631100180156174
    },
    {
        "question": " 772万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3312159108760271
    },
    {
        "question": " 852万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.152235736446345
    },
    {
        "question": " 555万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.744385038611606
    },
    {
        "question": " 290msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.462083175730244
    },
    {
        "question": " 115兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5627825288888255
    },
    {
        "question": " 719兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.920264202197777
    },
    {
        "question": " 2111兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.768086863639653
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.344924337372459
    },
    {
        "question": " 505億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.70337020994762
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.98兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.999057390753869
    },
    {
        "question": " 437万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.64080029086229
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.9京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8803959116726745
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.5京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9358333903320206
    },
    {
        "question": " 8189京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3569064048388295
    },
    {
        "question": " 775京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.111136866888081
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.92京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.996566543154665
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.1328583262292478
    },
    {
        "question": " 1055億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.023236728389742
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7105516236218317
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.35946096879571
    },
    {
        "question": " 7018億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.283891615716081
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.1日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7038488523889805
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.9日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2704376726568825
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.5日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.564450151917287
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.949193608057884
    },
    {
        "question": " 453億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.713447613002384
    },
    {
        "question": " 130万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.733912204986057
    },
    {
        "question": " 153万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.46525638123442015
    },
    {
        "question": " 528億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.563949929413969
    },
    {
        "question": " 261分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6393048284215297
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.99分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.379270970967462
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.33分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.414768958218573
    },
    {
        "question": " 432兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.136831852486127
    },
    {
        "question": " 1159万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.12749717276035
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.77兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.274370415757335
    },
    {
        "question": " 4990秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9199582319735853
    },
    {
        "question": " 895万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.951867118845016
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.786142826125101
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.8億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.943363816277438
    },
    {
        "question": " 4515万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0983886029019607
    },
    {
        "question": " 2411万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6040720308889154
    },
    {
        "question": " 1284msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10872105116584652
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.8msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.411389638531261
    },
    {
        "question": " 117兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5686721688031648
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.46京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.800330844175231
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.32京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.412975707657052
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.659277591421702
    },
    {
        "question": " 768億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.885169269222053
    },
    {
        "question": " 1108万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.044593203555552
    },
    {
        "question": " 5099usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.70747692609432
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.7京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2471317537839721
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.7垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.694371608787415
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.47京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.093908077586235
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4428480085902775
    },
    {
        "question": " 138億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.140414875986765
    },
    {
        "question": " 419兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.622023091771064
    },
    {
        "question": " 120万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.079718863157659
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7206648712503956
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.082720655459791
    },
    {
        "question": " 627日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2350088148962537
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.61万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.200697562236015
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.9万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.810141953006354
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.3兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.885414820586606
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.4億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.4614524605275
    },
    {
        "question": " 4324万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.414031629936767
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.3時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.403264538351782
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.5914060964389565
    },
    {
        "question": " 4171億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.899558887886824
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.26万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5628266749316777
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.9分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.006436422433747646
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5169277298845225
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.6億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5636647205235175
    },
    {
        "question": " 1693万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.67225534143103
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3761392833582464
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.4秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.822418471108661
    },
    {
        "question": " 21秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.322531000678621
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.840102443987614
    },
    {
        "question": " 265兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.486644536610896
    },
    {
        "question": " 7839万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3379838939956823
    },
    {
        "question": " 159兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.423711877824863
    },
    {
        "question": " 8985億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.953510510530405
    },
    {
        "question": " 192msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.283011560245962
    },
    {
        "question": " 238京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.878634767459248
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.6兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.867145670834473
    },
    {
        "question": " 4045兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.050565965837248
    },
    {
        "question": " 1214兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.306199946954567
    },
    {
        "question": " 1006兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.002581024107018
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.55兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.550623929624225
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.2usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.840064347137741
    },
    {
        "question": " 861京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4364448833146204
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2606610181837885
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5953524773553402
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.253936425649621
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.02兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7796915828687707
    },
    {
        "question": " 100兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.0010843066305
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.51億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.654108888935876
    },
    {
        "question": " 3797年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.141703166551259
    },
    {
        "question": " 296年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.969384766183095
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.64億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.189268453091889
    },
    {
        "question": " 17万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.611719294406266
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.4日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.580670541738655
    },
    {
        "question": " 251日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.335595494255984
    },
    {
        "question": " 27万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4891127056271047
    },
    {
        "question": " 1508億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.798259117859999
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.3万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.300429822667859
    },
    {
        "question": " 1118時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.60481101217115
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.678841742368221
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.8億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.116125164856566
    },
    {
        "question": " 130分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3357781740461552
    },
    {
        "question": " 2106万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.101647491207725
    },
    {
        "question": " 1049分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.799020183244988
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.2京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.950766019861453
    },
    {
        "question": " 454万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.720974292141475
    },
    {
        "question": " 6411億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.250649651909907
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2930785120902795
    },
    {
        "question": " 921京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.465467241385431
    },
    {
        "question": " 770兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.949855804275651
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.571114252236025
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.09億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.129842780168817
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.025018626030854
    },
    {
        "question": " 220垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.844200628444687
    },
    {
        "question": " 303兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.545121022656137
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5845910205060085
    },
    {
        "question": " 289億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6821348085195806
    },
    {
        "question": " 1385万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1413629385925128
    },
    {
        "question": " 2460usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.3908675230749681
    },
    {
        "question": " 404usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.606231511654807
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.33京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3665696557266551
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.65垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.946963754921231
    },
    {
        "question": " 232垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.809057067840328
    },
    {
        "question": " 2263億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5765405336938068
    },
    {
        "question": " 112兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.049235337116284
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.200335050992564
    },
    {
        "question": " 4373nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.6407909866468964
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.7年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5338544749509255
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.727823194874357
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.779087154212586
    },
    {
        "question": " 258億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8500445339133
    },
    {
        "question": " 1121万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.429943466368101
    },
    {
        "question": " 4740億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.733272478339368
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.4億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.421912140881268
    },
    {
        "question": " 67万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.604308128930667
    },
    {
        "question": " 177時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.803334139137313
    },
    {
        "question": " 237兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.654352967871548
    },
    {
        "question": " 403億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.446938601369882
    },
    {
        "question": " 281分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.670634462219214
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.75分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5376872015775875
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.89兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.271359725453435
    },
    {
        "question": " 636兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.866838572065985
    },
    {
        "question": " 111億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.487232280365475
    },
    {
        "question": " 3564万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.773779168393617
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.6万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.555948702185518
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.64088835028526
    },
    {
        "question": " 2478京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.895300854290427
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.9億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9821587106952276
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.1億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3016780825860526
    },
    {
        "question": " 348億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.763422479246851
    },
    {
        "question": " 7014億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.845944135440147
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.3万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.726547383494914
    },
    {
        "question": " 43兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13441860520760907
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.56644953499956
    },
    {
        "question": " 1710億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6765880326123872
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.3億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9238219115646993
    },
    {
        "question": " 635兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.802948561686543
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.6億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.9325960196924
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.75万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.573602649246544
    },
    {
        "question": " 6712京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.32805654450243
    },
    {
        "question": " 1252垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.160996981806509
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.8京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.125149139299947
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5918910170358123
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.4京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.751020020384267
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.163489107274787
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.1069826474059197
    },
    {
        "question": " 4046年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.169277358330337
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.987187294394832
    },
    {
        "question": " 1007億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.440702131605782
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.705606292126053
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.4日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.01186526384243
    },
    {
        "question": " 418日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.55791620026216
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.1万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2914781385639118
    },
    {
        "question": " 134億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.746605954232331
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.107582991273665
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.25万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.4167988057389
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.24兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.07428330280422
    },
    {
        "question": " 209億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.161171226207596
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.8万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7370819219032936
    },
    {
        "question": " 5935分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.551553761083121
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.12650355347111
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.3分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.671921523957682
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5789155847354
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.4兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.844365942145414
    },
    {
        "question": " 1兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.444550255280664
    },
    {
        "question": " 9210万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.186086261079727
    },
    {
        "question": " 181秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.258793347012994
    },
    {
        "question": " 227京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.856643671485182
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.3兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.957464883925595
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.52兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.257707140344081
    },
    {
        "question": " 206万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5352309038728984
    },
    {
        "question": " 1889億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.27633230830465
    },
    {
        "question": " 444万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.647648974893476
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.19msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.341376974731723
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.6京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9266886859003405
    },
    {
        "question": " 1121京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.113086831836252
    },
    {
        "question": " 976億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4331802732784271
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4884450226951431
    },
    {
        "question": " 6011億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.778920029406281
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.49万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.652353927065321
    },
    {
        "question": " 4654usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.667863982422104
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.96京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09867728229937422
    },
    {
        "question": " 7035兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9107492445517027
    },
    {
        "question": " 3238兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.953920997310834
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.460797844659217
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.4億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5231781955024661
    },
    {
        "question": " 8790万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.9439792750124574
    },
    {
        "question": " 15万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.175800051963831
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.73378294712842
    },
    {
        "question": " 911万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.39710751070157
    },
    {
        "question": " 2082日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.476787805092822
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.2日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.530183459963733
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.273319901057681
    },
    {
        "question": " 4468万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.26994205275662
    },
    {
        "question": " 789万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.674970681729464
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.9万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.500514306187286
    },
    {
        "question": " 1193時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.632816558269635
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.479640412685926
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.03万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3231672153112972
    },
    {
        "question": " 165億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.438942587671548
    },
    {
        "question": " 29分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2403250129436403
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.92分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.061839163248191
    },
    {
        "question": " 3897万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09190743906098975
    },
    {
        "question": " 153万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2481662579554165
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.507937516858867
    },
    {
        "question": " 156万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.415297182347646
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.507817567766907
    },
    {
        "question": " 1658兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.283078623833722
    },
    {
        "question": " 4241億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.071154939698637
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.4兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.988083138872703
    },
    {
        "question": " 1166万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.06652748942419
    },
    {
        "question": " 1010京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.505572560709506
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2303467980073557
    },
    {
        "question": " 859兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.377568606747288
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.6兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.536557504236948
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.257468265902496
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.2594381369529284
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.183910856935555
    },
    {
        "question": " 2742垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9392274903494915
    },
    {
        "question": " 3722京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.634275551445601
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.56京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.188444016064137
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.9兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7251798519532953
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.3京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.519092067410177
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.208524086497823
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.236167653737183
    },
    {
        "question": " 22万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.285695187878162
    },
    {
        "question": " 6875年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.557911530332277
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.5年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.364810112087994
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.95億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.435701917034996
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.1万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3675238352465495
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.226632779139685
    },
    {
        "question": " 586万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.825419449271539
    },
    {
        "question": " 559億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.367409731367534
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.45時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3165452296590083
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.6時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.338836651571798
    },
    {
        "question": " 1656万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4983563747802175
    },
    {
        "question": " 11兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.881246507371136
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.05億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.92539861965943
    },
    {
        "question": " 5310万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.503209315023366
    },
    {
        "question": " 26分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.192939633134799
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.86京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.087309857108954
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.95兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.533537881063746
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.525181274091924
    },
    {
        "question": " 117秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.28858613085381735
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.91秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.59200052517928
    },
    {
        "question": " 463京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.16687664549824
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.4兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.814480391355604
    },
    {
        "question": " 3707億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.012720162904538
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.4万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0757248989439494
    },
    {
        "question": " 4354万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.638862277501236
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.127407891217368
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.534587101217656
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.4京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.79618085859437
    },
    {
        "question": " 373京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.015816744315227
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.69億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1075310014962958
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.244045862553037
    },
    {
        "question": " 4390億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.642498264129348
    },
    {
        "question": " 1515京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6815502989859032
    },
    {
        "question": " 3487垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.60599046180208
    },
    {
        "question": " 139垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.58691888960833
    },
    {
        "question": " 94兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1950289172444615
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.02219617409261354
    },
    {
        "question": " 2023兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.306074908399212
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.6万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.3128768459149796
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.646098168493395
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.9年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.649413668899236
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.1万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.186622669743503
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.4万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.240002044699506
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.2日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.694030557240364
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.1兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.730667213106504
    },
    {
        "question": " 610時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4050119336621747
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.782836049153178
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.05万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.16359456984904
    },
    {
        "question": " 873万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2205097770410656
    },
    {
        "question": " 557万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.587197165582393
    },
    {
        "question": " 163万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.433285010759032
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.17分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.491460572208254
    },
    {
        "question": " 317分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.279291972851967
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.4兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9058524827044305
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4242713500978255
    },
    {
        "question": " 780万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.335770600307939
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.597107273025448
    },
    {
        "question": " 291万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.464349549237038
    },
    {
        "question": " 5192秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.715318441497812
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.765797453892448
    },
    {
        "question": " 205兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.375636745262475
    },
    {
        "question": " 1766億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.690689920374924
    },
    {
        "question": " 3186億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7250291378814575
    },
    {
        "question": " 1350億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.130325148042715
    },
    {
        "question": " 423万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.625952241379164
    },
    {
        "question": " 778msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.891020048550061
    },
    {
        "question": " 865兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4382417242146628
    },
    {
        "question": " 944京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.038334407466953
    },
    {
        "question": " 237億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8193510617467115
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.5京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.962025326307304
    },
    {
        "question": " 4377兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.641204052450577
    },
    {
        "question": " 1154usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.06214687904304239
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.32垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.022612765984139
    },
    {
        "question": " 127兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16812675179624925
    },
    {
        "question": " 112京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.492744360730192
    },
    {
        "question": " 3705億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7906178951223441
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.4兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.56072378755847
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.035728569630079
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.0822712183417815
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.316557418334509
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.9年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.483440723692451
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.506596129116783
    },
    {
        "question": " 2640日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.859222292904368
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.5万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.930492771968454
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.33兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.027344837238028
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.786712247551428
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9115948135389003
    },
    {
        "question": " 145時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.718120791161946
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.29693141775552
    },
    {
        "question": " 2387分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2194956555430605
    },
    {
        "question": " 156億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.413614827838902
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8442386775998176
    },
    {
        "question": " 10分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.778535240997003
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.79兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.33297522788941
    },
    {
        "question": " 309万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5530547418735574
    },
    {
        "question": " 4417万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.088812311041932
    },
    {
        "question": " 6469秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.032667446015193
    },
    {
        "question": " 93万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.96827892127244
    },
    {
        "question": " 33秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.51899757988987
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.3京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.849903772948036
    },
    {
        "question": " 6586兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.882107262234283
    },
    {
        "question": " 5145万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1551207665452667
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.3兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.906126662238995
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.337404139893876
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.058640338489029
    },
    {
        "question": " 63垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.300687287787206
    },
    {
        "question": " 131京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.180161078454174
    },
    {
        "question": " 2139京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.773920946492876
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3077461652927769
    },
    {
        "question": " 227億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.356649449156683
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.21億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.914555918191965
    },
    {
        "question": " 5905垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.272405788175014
    },
    {
        "question": " 3931垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.658027535987983
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.14垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.154753865656316
    },
    {
        "question": " 864兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.158459989289477
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.9兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.755178441215752
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.46億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.649238054994285
    },
    {
        "question": " 4096億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.612384597609083
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.9年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.285932311701421
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.6年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.288128466435658
    },
    {
        "question": " 700日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2829799742394834
    },
    {
        "question": " 5879万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.149483731427996
    },
    {
        "question": " 709億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.907979480552694
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.7万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.298706763474705
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.19時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.569707700080699
    },
    {
        "question": " 4302時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.189991563933563
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7639234181688135
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.7億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.356303228709762
    },
    {
        "question": " 4453億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.870509700579024
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.7分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.695810542363731
    },
    {
        "question": " 1302億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.615972228572798
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.35兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.434940956650852
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.61406742715675
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5150030110628716
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.4秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.483350508826339
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.6兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9253329742977465
    },
    {
        "question": " 148兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.233764935550456
    },
    {
        "question": " 2684億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.872513499498003
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.6億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.088525635641638
    },
    {
        "question": " 644億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.80886414000388
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.4万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.743788845605517
    },
    {
        "question": " 117msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.066436375648772
    },
    {
        "question": " 1179京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5727299843421365
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.58垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.809863211942382
    },
    {
        "question": " 185京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.710807909986963
    },
    {
        "question": " 116億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2859393642207824
    },
    {
        "question": " 2102万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3225438594901484
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.65兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.562840440531726
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.53万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.547584288915422
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5150032152661135
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.314934144769407
    },
    {
        "question": " 481兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1260716740926555
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.48垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.7633506696511
    },
    {
        "question": " 4366億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6401317877159958
    },
    {
        "question": " 1237億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.092507979111971
    },
    {
        "question": " 4642nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.6666829511227057
    },
    {
        "question": " 540万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.294989782908544
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.903683397641359
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.53年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.901228070674456
    },
    {
        "question": " 6028万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.217873689412595
    },
    {
        "question": " 2911万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.844234092561509
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.58万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8189318428630825
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.117513586566504
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0471069374423854
    },
    {
        "question": " 6005時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5566606875428
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.06万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.260587139703587
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.4時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.385154140844925
    },
    {
        "question": " 5140兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.990309243183125
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.45億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.768745884772104
    },
    {
        "question": " 7876万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.118180725339294
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.71万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.211793808871953
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.056597044630056
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.98億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2776231905512936
    },
    {
        "question": " 214万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3933003471558558
    },
    {
        "question": " 2296万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8046895696186365
    },
    {
        "question": " 153秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4065367788214047
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.054081099679999
    },
    {
        "question": " 132京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.621455816187577
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.2兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.699476757268908
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.9兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1502909517961974
    },
    {
        "question": " 2198万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5639362637498584
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.4万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6661878985787757
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07429538935129432
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0993034497592247
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.562270450841506
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2818262822580828
    },
    {
        "question": " 1382万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1405871570736459
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.2134461771489313
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.045991038771009
    },
    {
        "question": " 344京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.038199344464613
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.2垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.032762493562107
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5674294792851464
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.433834271788524
    },
    {
        "question": " 682京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.834073774460492
    },
    {
        "question": " 5061万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.704268198711818
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.181005942079551
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.738957469861609
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.1年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.915512812522005
    },
    {
        "question": " 566万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.190513991946682
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6949554512323806
    },
    {
        "question": " 1406万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.20544445057636
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.91154088993504
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0671262430125967
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.693799259403975
    },
    {
        "question": " 953兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.258579926038603
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.310344931572116
    },
    {
        "question": " 269分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.651435074310801
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.3分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.404214739675092
    },
    {
        "question": " 161分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.985927998645751
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.737832053660856
    },
    {
        "question": " 662億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8842623832032235
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.88兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.212735725574982
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5288762998511114
    },
    {
        "question": " 793万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.89913294645177
    },
    {
        "question": " 401兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1038553624940874
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.39155685123770434
    },
    {
        "question": " 120億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.523142138788958
    },
    {
        "question": " 373兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.793439662788918
    },
    {
        "question": " 4716万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.673547995578224
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.3垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.203161700400564
    },
    {
        "question": " 4712億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7367329767310382
    },
    {
        "question": " 2189億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7839896072861605
    },
    {
        "question": " 731億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0860349174226345
    },
    {
        "question": " 2323兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.36610844334285
    },
    {
        "question": " 243万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3851145787409145
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.049e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.204366760751823
    },
    {
        "question": " 791京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.961871990486591
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.50245280888678
    },
    {
        "question": " 302兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7017490464964373
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.172830539360426
    },
    {
        "question": " 8276兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.917801449801702
    },
    {
        "question": " 102億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.009209972068367
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.74年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.32133879842867
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.87年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9366466071132455
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.731240978111005
    },
    {
        "question": " 3581億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.991693751743842
    },
    {
        "question": " 189日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6575283745981424
    },
    {
        "question": " 1565日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3528269893752825
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.51億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.603106834897364
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.068834677010163
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.23万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.693535420225206
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.05万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.404440358475053
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.8兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.845766080742696
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.6万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1546020113211686
    },
    {
        "question": " 1308億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.338394290098732
    },
    {
        "question": " 3273万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.29308345001966
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.5兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.06330139968766
    },
    {
        "question": " 352万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6100087846832467
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.1兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.767565784991936
    },
    {
        "question": " 3863万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.808781704567986
    },
    {
        "question": " 774秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.888748913932796
    },
    {
        "question": " 6731秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.828101246877383
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.6兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.130985565337232
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.28京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.694496860034127
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.77179044761978
    },
    {
        "question": " 234億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.59101494364369
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.070461172053374
    },
    {
        "question": " 219垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.840769575795136
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.071850138944422
    },
    {
        "question": " 215億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7767646967213093
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24079266582182512
    },
    {
        "question": " 197兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.293614051532916
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.09億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.320967266803324
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.788254225671741
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.4垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.844717293135204
    },
    {
        "question": " 2878京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.902765976956564
    },
    {
        "question": " 8519億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.152255104507448
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.9京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.297888609313516
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.1兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.748842669279094
    },
    {
        "question": " 598億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.776826842800894
    },
    {
        "question": " 2945年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.031337858769282
    },
    {
        "question": " 938年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.914623749326748
    },
    {
        "question": " 4637億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.103973391833323
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.269672346150715
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.965558848900071
    },
    {
        "question": " 1238億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.150373133398826
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16211084558368394
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2624065678158245
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.2時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1793658575612085
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.028253925014283
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.8兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.197594174297713
    },
    {
        "question": " 1863分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.111967487471335
    },
    {
        "question": " 1816万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.481014334969629
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.7分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5237349537235216
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.930345774198436
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.49分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.320356850827945
    },
    {
        "question": " 1179億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.572769100731199
    },
    {
        "question": " 2039万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.373008103569009
    },
    {
        "question": " 3646億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.00554746239538
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.438173158207558
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.644121942155361
    },
    {
        "question": " 2137億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3933513684230854
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.32兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.244547825682148
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.939317581048288
    },
    {
        "question": " 5945msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7741754563083636
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.8msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.599907550906341
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.64msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.421691386087196
    },
    {
        "question": " 4501兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1545166007605356
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.58京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.617475929158166
    },
    {
        "question": " 442億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0891541641807345
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.42兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.867603388024032
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.85兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.454981075725965
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.95兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.997664444612704
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.68万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.428313073280238
    },
    {
        "question": " 543京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.236282217279851
    },
    {
        "question": " 6406京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8700998424560735
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4721954183827277
    },
    {
        "question": " 22兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5651575853156494
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.7億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.42722417082741493
    },
    {
        "question": " 895兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.95182094774667
    },
    {
        "question": " 5901億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.77090239420397
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.832526893164087
    },
    {
        "question": " 818年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8550416040240405
    },
    {
        "question": " 9570年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.701567930512331
    },
    {
        "question": " 762億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.319451584234908
    },
    {
        "question": " 7877日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.276582851222722
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.47日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5509947024892705
    },
    {
        "question": " 11万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.978752071231163
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.309104675114003
    },
    {
        "question": " 9880万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.052237754312892
    },
    {
        "question": " 6701万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4459315181541434
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8424802162341125
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.23時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4151865454217845
    },
    {
        "question": " 464万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9456630804241006
    },
    {
        "question": " 2799万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2886020481744485
    },
    {
        "question": " 362万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.780520833144535
    },
    {
        "question": " 185分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.046242071461831
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.2分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.324679059960707
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.47京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.894310193425735
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.537172066534033
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.178068157348323
    },
    {
        "question": " 796億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.122557050947929
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.072668872661403
    },
    {
        "question": " 148秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.171071160707163
    },
    {
        "question": " 7271兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3628039339233755
    },
    {
        "question": " 558億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8104528886847024
    },
    {
        "question": " 108兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.477701901288908
    },
    {
        "question": " 373万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7933682643977833
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.02892657099821
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.371569824798298
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.6兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12026523621646468
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.71兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4959944690587523
    },
    {
        "question": " 2892兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.904922390566246
    },
    {
        "question": " 3657兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7850111995356635
    },
    {
        "question": " 3415兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.533380054010472
    },
    {
        "question": " 2642億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.421898165493388
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.43670373740261
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.8京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9891159541033234
    },
    {
        "question": " 375垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.637100305152707
    },
    {
        "question": " 3264兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.957492915022314
    },
    {
        "question": " 1397京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.366898238209012
    },
    {
        "question": " 185京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.266324954563043
    },
    {
        "question": " 8034億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.904933867401866
    },
    {
        "question": " 1156nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.06297719246215028
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.755097739663708
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.88年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.401614925957156
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.2年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.086693955688929
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.6億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.198229791246684
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.4万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.186229046477124
    },
    {
        "question": " 3618日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.716764581145669
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.5兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.89923499889054
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.7時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3730388899063841
    },
    {
        "question": " 5341時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.505801382207498
    },
    {
        "question": " 123万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.645686749137962
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.4兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.810692245984969
    },
    {
        "question": " 202万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.147574639405464
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.41億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.028653448908926
    },
    {
        "question": " 1742分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.019307377296766
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.52分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.654430426530848
    },
    {
        "question": " 938兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.473551607562577
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.84兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6482062717954555
    },
    {
        "question": " 9704億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.430649117185537
    },
    {
        "question": " 1504万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.399240449005576
    },
    {
        "question": " 733万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.864928098698103
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.669768660015894
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.510350813107456
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.99兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.28811569630505
    },
    {
        "question": " 453万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8782525682004825
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.4億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.743572406418853
    },
    {
        "question": " 692京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.341365188996611
    },
    {
        "question": " 3414京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.596795865346126
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.712123757080185
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.3兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.673285225104535
    },
    {
        "question": " 8674万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9381992180088603
    },
    {
        "question": " 3265万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.513837941778695
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.2usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.833530484494926
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.9京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9470607194463998
    },
    {
        "question": " 345京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.601762377054347
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6406584520585303
    },
    {
        "question": " 12兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.302170668266701
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.6億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3912613043719526
    },
    {
        "question": " 5893兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.770347855161335
    },
    {
        "question": " 1427億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.154500056359932
    },
    {
        "question": " 130年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.675736357699826
    },
    {
        "question": " 644年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.52924268765163
    },
    {
        "question": " 820万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.351254322645264
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.443483667430877
    },
    {
        "question": " 156万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.249574544790259
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.2億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.545250265729246
    },
    {
        "question": " 116万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.842613314932615
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.8時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.463675518740667
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.1兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.11252925263412
    },
    {
        "question": " 1893分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11891485624920928
    },
    {
        "question": " 150万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.398694195110229
    },
    {
        "question": " 638分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.582835222929937
    },
    {
        "question": " 212兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.826879507384305
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.6万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7317480353933214
    },
    {
        "question": " 604万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2250917941628487
    },
    {
        "question": " 770万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.108196920845826
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.258398248109492
    },
    {
        "question": " 150秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.175007807349647
    },
    {
        "question": " 158兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.700515363109176
    },
    {
        "question": " 1753兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3072222320496625
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.1億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2367320941725053
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23871972348499693
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.3万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.893496651059545
    },
    {
        "question": " 241万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.381620855298529
    },
    {
        "question": " 1286msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.109375451051871
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.713361723245268
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.9京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.794949933922418
    },
    {
        "question": " 3224億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9521123076555824
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.374130923042106
    },
    {
        "question": " 1090万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0375505236628035
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.1万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.519668055000216
    },
    {
        "question": " 297usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.473022096318045
    },
    {
        "question": " 8968京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.453899622124456
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.04垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.766033818639978
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.7京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.737594993456396
    },
    {
        "question": " 362兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.780143900585621
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.3京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.724579584319776
    },
    {
        "question": " 9106兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.95932510068018
    },
    {
        "question": " 380億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.579614424928468
    },
    {
        "question": " 8232年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.857996267550764
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.29億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9549580024705895
    },
    {
        "question": " 157日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5762208683762378
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.97日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4520471048061174
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.119261782605655
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.3兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.784547513210219
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.4億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.859416996973415
    },
    {
        "question": " 174万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.797462430335207
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.1兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.942721874826507
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.86億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.789243130637996
    },
    {
        "question": " 280万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6682597227350175
    },
    {
        "question": " 398分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.377527834470882
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.43分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.704091781921512
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5457452482119927
    },
    {
        "question": " 2947億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.532840883456899
    },
    {
        "question": " 4393万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.086457620740439
    },
    {
        "question": " 684秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0566991676879722
    },
    {
        "question": " 5018億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2017163739397685
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.371296885480604
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.5億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1801045904463674
    },
    {
        "question": " 708万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0721149886363066
    },
    {
        "question": " 2934億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.467417871044066
    },
    {
        "question": " 247msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.393065185268325
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.4msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.637088514514519
    },
    {
        "question": " 793京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.400483179980449
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.77垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.95390782594205
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.1億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.29537596585525905
    },
    {
        "question": " 6891兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.06016086126404
    },
    {
        "question": " 799兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.902279037206663
    },
    {
        "question": " 32万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.505752867364728
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.277100818269838
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.8京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.067187768165876
    },
    {
        "question": " 378兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6415522085729475
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.648273741201929
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.3兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.815815972942323
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.33京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.636395306064868
    },
    {
        "question": " 5776兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.76159717503052
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.94兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.899854888723207
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.13万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.349634152867528
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9967432480474585
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.583524071638242
    },
    {
        "question": " 153万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.343993032620453
    },
    {
        "question": " 141億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2078787690832
    },
    {
        "question": " 360万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.176552971442391
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.3時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5512802993543136
    },
    {
        "question": " 363時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.116139858695457
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.4兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.00670921093061
    },
    {
        "question": " 2556万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.249162556391964
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4461722095292613
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.821226165370207
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.93787619882708
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6642259685196925
    },
    {
        "question": " 4519万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.718515348824966
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.652595927119568
    },
    {
        "question": " 19万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4998205088902012
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.031488779167322
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.761440581968922
    },
    {
        "question": " 3659億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0645894106288667
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.471169507790897
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7664674372492772
    },
    {
        "question": " 534兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.949353479477093
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.369624253715804
    },
    {
        "question": " 192垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.784258788761367
    },
    {
        "question": " 443京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.709570845521712
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.3京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.252206408755635
    },
    {
        "question": " 503億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9233454562811225
    },
    {
        "question": " 1430万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.155249510349986
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.27億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.91733656455418
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.2万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.78708879598896
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.622725857631803
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.2垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.797168956673167
    },
    {
        "question": " 9188兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4068991469783527
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.11兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5463135355620339
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.5京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.388431054831539
    },
    {
        "question": " 4074万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6100571581322687
    },
    {
        "question": " 1979万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.296461415447145
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.491191282996349
    },
    {
        "question": " 1602万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.642423239302181
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.5万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.322219917446119
    },
    {
        "question": " 2075日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.47533736354319
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.71兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.88443630983187
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.9時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5689130962552946
    },
    {
        "question": " 1121時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.827691886252692
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.768556761681212
    },
    {
        "question": " 247時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.94815562207156
    },
    {
        "question": " 1374万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4173215029108477
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.95兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.43809081510816
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.27億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.852212485425212
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.190802727855159
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.948857980708331
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.11京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.460839042602357
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.149352150548538
    },
    {
        "question": " 2633億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.864074691320637
    },
    {
        "question": " 363億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.78188279254584
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.1秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.7000432243893355
    },
    {
        "question": " 9618兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.484290813187923
    },
    {
        "question": " 806兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.969932357293721
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.527965580763219
    },
    {
        "question": " 134億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.348044626788571
    },
    {
        "question": " 8127msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9099060764340283
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.94msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.5958218611701662
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.04垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.348518505585019
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.8京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.959819204261855
    },
    {
        "question": " 186京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.712382464982655
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.7京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.647893223874371
    },
    {
        "question": " 423万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6266905862006422
    },
    {
        "question": " 826万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.9167338649651304
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.9usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.798426749726569
    },
    {
        "question": " 632垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.301617708725108
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.54京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4681240464383105
    },
    {
        "question": " 171兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.675954574180184
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.536843608650291
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05729588500030913
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.44兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.38721140948449
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.099302068131461
    },
    {
        "question": " 2099年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.884222160665502
    },
    {
        "question": " 279億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8840023225261815
    },
    {
        "question": " 2340日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.305694315812937
    },
    {
        "question": " 162万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2683003122350742
    },
    {
        "question": " 1832億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.882684296750165
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.3時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3375794009810598
    },
    {
        "question": " 212時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8830158038299185
    },
    {
        "question": " 110億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.320815331444997
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.65兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.26425194816658
    },
    {
        "question": " 1791分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4749951940805994
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.905029645688636
    },
    {
        "question": " 8200万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4150178005946681
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.278533864565989
    },
    {
        "question": " 9595秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4257302731689949
    },
    {
        "question": " 101億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.22591083947125
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.272008634271847
    },
    {
        "question": " 122兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.588171830504633
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3633048613716472
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.9億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.346294718958096
    },
    {
        "question": " 9628億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.205372400241991
    },
    {
        "question": " 199万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2990878719765537
    },
    {
        "question": " 229万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.360105048623993
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.3msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.625913905320218
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.11京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.825475563492894
    },
    {
        "question": " 1477京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.233005063272621
    },
    {
        "question": " 1251京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.540869507420073
    },
    {
        "question": " 269兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.651539363473501
    },
    {
        "question": " 1081兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.033846993884824
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.1万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.9593014134726916
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.912e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.782688481325877
    },
    {
        "question": " 2110京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.387752086461223
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.59176822267879
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.86京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.908547138832453
    },
    {
        "question": " 2971兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4729209866476385
    },
    {
        "question": " 6476万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.8113341265140126
    },
    {
        "question": " 3508nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.5450270898747633
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.935127271621269
    },
    {
        "question": " 109年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.979591958782498
    },
    {
        "question": " 1552日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6285082231960215
    },
    {
        "question": " 2972万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.853184906923788
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.306695875713633
    },
    {
        "question": " 230万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4201051977177004
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.9時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06593618761208453
    },
    {
        "question": " 293万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.245065126207873
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4447833249535553
    },
    {
        "question": " 6975分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6852187994115078
    },
    {
        "question": " 3805億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.802167423824738
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.38分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.750311171853157
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.351100058142473
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.6兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1301892021752025
    },
    {
        "question": " 2382億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4404646848135965
    },
    {
        "question": " 6974万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.287199290248077
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.477241130683424
    },
    {
        "question": " 2307秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.362985936835523
    },
    {
        "question": " 164京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.716450092812538
    },
    {
        "question": " 302億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.544086013662117
    },
    {
        "question": " 109億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.479928934764688
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.6億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.797070855141778
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.57兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.410327892730713
    },
    {
        "question": " 547msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.737876294052107
    },
    {
        "question": " 434兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1388571639102052
    },
    {
        "question": " 1514億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24368990356137044
    },
    {
        "question": " 529京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.167173465324554
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.2兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.022469747135019
    },
    {
        "question": " 2132万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3287448495276521
    },
    {
        "question": " 364億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.561458330700116
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.338e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.627721597377467
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.6垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.784168248031774
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.2垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.153269400133118
    },
    {
        "question": " 3757京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.796717182098387
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.9億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.37857267377525594
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.4兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.859680140871605
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.44万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.5369495804055033
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.33万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4830800041620815
    },
    {
        "question": " 579年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.704960453946777
    },
    {
        "question": " 166年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.941252579032537
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.8万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3396237305653784
    },
    {
        "question": " 2504万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.778863225415904
    },
    {
        "question": " 39日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.749931927395968
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.8万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7389448746508698
    },
    {
        "question": " 33万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.138696608467304
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.8時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.932663694331778
    },
    {
        "question": " 3206億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.78532945510357
    },
    {
        "question": " 1881分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11606084970386399
    },
    {
        "question": " 2485億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.617246616183095
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.925049798780064
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.939931678927236
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.2億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1164221473361278
    },
    {
        "question": " 720兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.921074800117552
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.18億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.406419253993075
    },
    {
        "question": " 8945万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.173426972677484
    },
    {
        "question": " 996万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.998336935781767
    },
    {
        "question": " 2538億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9056611653593805
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.299015583076625
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.4億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.081265022788755
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.5億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.620540766477145
    },
    {
        "question": " 2220億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.346326215013658
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.1msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.852164051609144
    },
    {
        "question": " 4878msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.6882132807544
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7638030462819163
    },
    {
        "question": " 3482億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6053777104267521
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.8億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3001091067732087
    },
    {
        "question": " 520兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.938185678235489
    },
    {
        "question": " 866兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.937622615697492
    },
    {
        "question": " 1190万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.0755695204749145
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.9usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.9996666606243885
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.031e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.514400407945693
    },
    {
        "question": " 4966京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.759472784471119
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.599965573451804
    },
    {
        "question": " 751億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09735144342353563
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.15京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.854079517364663
    },
    {
        "question": " 3329万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5223117357270433
    },
    {
        "question": " 8644nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.9367224170659549
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.91万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.154886881839965
    },
    {
        "question": " 312年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.214693969147394
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.481955482633301
    },
    {
        "question": " 487日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.067950807215739
    },
    {
        "question": " 3051日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.421008738244314
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.094527153082876
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.2億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.406640458884931
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1672965727098275
    },
    {
        "question": " 837億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.20196087249531
    },
    {
        "question": " 400万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.44373840903709
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.4分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14800828344052497
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1159727076187895
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5052547255051474
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.95兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.532840855619487
    },
    {
        "question": " 1941万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7316513567767515
    },
    {
        "question": " 516秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9346370321463693
    },
    {
        "question": " 90万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.954007855060896
    },
    {
        "question": " 4339京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.138607466935591
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.1億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9148438346449772
    },
    {
        "question": " 217億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7808034982382277
    },
    {
        "question": " 1331万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3461772610338114
    },
    {
        "question": " 4826万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.683594439471824
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.188909685567774
    },
    {
        "question": " 379京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.079629553152919
    },
    {
        "question": " 2337兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.432222751400907
    },
    {
        "question": " 969京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.429841619604932
    },
    {
        "question": " 8731億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.162892598140546
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7581592748356645
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.08兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.783794455530021
    },
    {
        "question": " 886京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4486538776670743
    },
    {
        "question": " 3303京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.58243147307662
    },
    {
        "question": " 205兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7564197674591508
    },
    {
        "question": " 2552兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6287458370168535
    },
    {
        "question": " 298億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4740430346038802
    },
    {
        "question": " 2433億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.3862191744578105
    },
    {
        "question": " 1057万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.023883445689304
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.756092685245763
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.246499174672499
    },
    {
        "question": " 1158万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.501560560380042
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.43万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0268959029663
    },
    {
        "question": " 111万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.204549036778827
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.257880559909828
    },
    {
        "question": " 9日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.890964800001175
    },
    {
        "question": " 244億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.445775211366577
    },
    {
        "question": " 1201時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6994771685223709
    },
    {
        "question": " 1312万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3972098009334855
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.928436206311503
    },
    {
        "question": " 119億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.29673614219483
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.922532074676996
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.7分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.305884064755184
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.21億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4153499474769016
    },
    {
        "question": " 110万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1063460566200045
    },
    {
        "question": " 5608秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19247670861660904
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.2億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.826069266023906
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.6万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.72952543690883
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7243806385324634
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.1京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.464018048874145
    },
    {
        "question": " 1689億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.671247579344461
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.272970695289976
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.65兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.423155240778168
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.190912258537791
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.93垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.96784623767204
    },
    {
        "question": " 4088京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.675015878394746
    },
    {
        "question": " 585京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.210544509819755
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.31785590082464
    },
    {
        "question": " 1327万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1228278580724216
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.72億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.827170074532969
    },
    {
        "question": " 117usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.069331056166908
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.895e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.496622875706791
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.300729508269166
    },
    {
        "question": " 3202兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.949185180312929
    },
    {
        "question": " 2872兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.680005610641576
    },
    {
        "question": " 188兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.274230055367418
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.201215634317236
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.65兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.423335684633715
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.4年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.532656107851003
    },
    {
        "question": " 1373年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.080294486479531
    },
    {
        "question": " 124万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.529650384688956
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.38億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.757535156982328
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.27兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.919183857708314
    },
    {
        "question": " 8528時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5506290307984294
    },
    {
        "question": " 1500万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.954315036852305
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.5時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.907888156202231
    },
    {
        "question": " 127時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.658839271356625
    },
    {
        "question": " 1273兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.384249093496235
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.53兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.389075716213805
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.6万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.144206160933036
    },
    {
        "question": " 2864分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.235110006153648
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.15分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.27577427365232
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.7分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.575621759101274
    },
    {
        "question": " 7275兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.363010653519861
    },
    {
        "question": " 231億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.42637912761456
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.48兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.837858148033614
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.41億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.955034738834999
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.17秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.5016008192743673
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.671508755321176
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.1兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.75419945330303
    },
    {
        "question": " 8260万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3606571125618705
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.48兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.960772380374027
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.3億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.743052800194297
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.297743815601542
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.48msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.65158141268458
    },
    {
        "question": " 3205兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0070027752690587
    },
    {
        "question": " 86京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.998192154413882
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.8京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0240123731356245
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.385193772609954
    },
    {
        "question": " 1484万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1715225666820595
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.5425120493904645
    },
    {
        "question": " 108usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.033973193603469
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.9京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3990711364900479
    },
    {
        "question": " 1145京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1224189020597946
    },
    {
        "question": " 3565京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.99575771471705
    },
    {
        "question": " 272兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.656098512860444
    },
    {
        "question": " 2616億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4175697269242735
    },
    {
        "question": " 2960万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.4713403128497193
    },
    {
        "question": " 577万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.761448165978838
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.86980167090814
    },
    {
        "question": " 2581年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.132480919424191
    },
    {
        "question": " 103年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.513225111748886
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5679696286838174
    },
    {
        "question": " 2459日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.770961988394418
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.89万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0526741630518788
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.2億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.47834786856388
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.04万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.260832186293111
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.750789551072584
    },
    {
        "question": " 142万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9950760337571394
    },
    {
        "question": " 788万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.11853665190503
    },
    {
        "question": " 9769分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.76801385473347
    },
    {
        "question": " 581分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.542444210390022
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.6分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.341481354249368
    },
    {
        "question": " 840兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.425246758474891
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.3億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.679612297275732
    },
    {
        "question": " 433万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.079966495974319
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.2万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8454221809799405
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.9秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.320184440023311
    },
    {
        "question": " 6543秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.815796669802278
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.804913766521393
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.1億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6772788134634775
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.24兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.954593156265843
    },
    {
        "question": " 1105億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.265025613340071
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.261833878034558
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.241974986704748
    },
    {
        "question": " 130垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.613900894687369
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.7兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.907021108518839
    },
    {
        "question": " 293兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9104895878954675
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.69京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.650948737501484
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.266750245376321
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.0380413758136573
    },
    {
        "question": " 268万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.427750012308504
    },
    {
        "question": " 3199京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0062788348987457
    },
    {
        "question": " 1506京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.241376944133669
    },
    {
        "question": " 7970京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.34516237658943
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.2兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.136878683673907
    },
    {
        "question": " 111兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.044261306446348
    },
    {
        "question": " 1396万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.144965837335662
    },
    {
        "question": " 279万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.4456666971766667
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.6年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.724741188932549
    },
    {
        "question": " 725万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.298089331461371
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.639820666250675
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.313577802913049
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.030806101004559
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.49664367761329
    },
    {
        "question": " 4932時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3128563126546267
    },
    {
        "question": " 805万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.684028809592503
    },
    {
        "question": " 252億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.680774011980233
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.990607356438996
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.5万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0346835246072787
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.4分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.288261173978352
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.4分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.770960739336319
    },
    {
        "question": " 4902万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19157383254085558
    },
    {
        "question": " 1294億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1755185865409175
    },
    {
        "question": " 269万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.872961518139836
    },
    {
        "question": " 611秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0082402948294455
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.087944801182399
    },
    {
        "question": " 1159億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5654123411484702
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.7兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.736037830207716
    },
    {
        "question": " 151億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6227327691561517
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.366336354657543
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.1億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9779525669913784
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.5兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.38505911943700677
    },
    {
        "question": " 1775億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31281921101005694
    },
    {
        "question": " 3988億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.044413261042796
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3646861247519615
    },
    {
        "question": " 105万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.022266769435963507
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.3億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.946024884339072
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.343938104759708
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.518e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.902272366266981
    },
    {
        "question": " 315垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.561449406695285
    },
    {
        "question": " 223垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.79167367489969
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.406757151031995
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.5兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.617654206453741
    },
    {
        "question": " 150万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.1773750195347812
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.22万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.3463659531931393
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.728499494486982
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.19546160562942
    },
    {
        "question": " 52年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.436576405648987
    },
    {
        "question": " 369日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.005108053071424257
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.660380794073673
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.5万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5821058812845556
    },
    {
        "question": " 15万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.796262813477699
    },
    {
        "question": " 281時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2269726799099425
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.78818829460242
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.9兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.754687901922976
    },
    {
        "question": " 1063億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8681452604884115
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4002968607739215
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.01分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.557246682640213
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.1億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.046445550352025
    },
    {
        "question": " 3390万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.593667348917814
    },
    {
        "question": " 106億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.470075480897268
    },
    {
        "question": " 1011万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.226401966174716
    },
    {
        "question": " 517秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.713628742927734
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.151116839860645
    },
    {
        "question": " 318兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.003584757297763
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.46兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.454216371126867
    },
    {
        "question": " 1857万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.712560021715346
    },
    {
        "question": " 198億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.519262578564592
    },
    {
        "question": " 1402msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14686623819617495
    },
    {
        "question": " 276msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.4407406846358795
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6937717096679314
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.79兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9548510841327082
    },
    {
        "question": " 428兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.075585855571926
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.1兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.085948917104011
    },
    {
        "question": " 1824兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.261142416930543
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.4788717587941
    },
    {
        "question": " 110万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.04218158785447
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.534712002056965
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.397645505630689
    },
    {
        "question": " 176京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.689416502712375
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.6京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6460124702985635
    },
    {
        "question": " 461億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6635243283001788
    },
    {
        "question": " 3296兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.517975020425107
    },
    {
        "question": " 3907万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.591836967241873
    },
    {
        "question": " 1033万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.576584658987118
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.072892544963086
    },
    {
        "question": " 3167日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9384133585236598
    },
    {
        "question": " 40日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.982063561022451
    },
    {
        "question": " 2744日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5967237724407655
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.060314432966562
    },
    {
        "question": " 76兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.93831750417997
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.2時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.36915828363402015
    },
    {
        "question": " 197時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.07187731023267
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.9時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.263226690601029
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.102794973032585
    },
    {
        "question": " 4193億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.464225935253086
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2748862478172525
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.1分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.659445007416836
    },
    {
        "question": " 2101分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.100606579070504
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7016942903871906
    },
    {
        "question": " 260万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4786749642430974
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.54兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.423167498180316
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.3秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.023579037511709533
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.026156523027975
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.54秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.404513875847834
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6571868083537753
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.51兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.717916727428201
    },
    {
        "question": " 491億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.134608195120344
    },
    {
        "question": " 279億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.666900000394443
    },
    {
        "question": " 3231億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.509351609801856
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.27京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.015943839959471
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.75兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7404825931745849
    },
    {
        "question": " 156億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6371689518571255
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.23076616835096
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.09兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9585844141493745
    },
    {
        "question": " 174億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.241698119668207
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.2108139820330095
    },
    {
        "question": " 6901垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.340123443444307
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.06垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.912200963894496
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.28垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.41119343466454
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.8京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.633817212587444
    },
    {
        "question": " 943億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.974639498845141
    },
    {
        "question": " 675億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.829443792144669
    },
    {
        "question": " 8353nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.9218620958480417
    },
    {
        "question": " 195年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.853027859991194
    },
    {
        "question": " 107年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.97030917108067
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.80564394704143
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.3億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.841655618789114
    },
    {
        "question": " 2452万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.76972655633548
    },
    {
        "question": " 3129日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.653782141040291
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.5日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.820365066484575
    },
    {
        "question": " 226万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4124189222470207
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.645738615190216
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.21時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.636267172156229
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7620236116875985
    },
    {
        "question": " 11時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.598081388219072
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.31兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.198749032313061
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.945387293665316
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.6億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.612227607640269
    },
    {
        "question": " 616分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.568023605327722
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.46万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.168554770917703
    },
    {
        "question": " 9846億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.494464067431475
    },
    {
        "question": " 16億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.267256600708626
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.85万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2110086462031366
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.73万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.979752378440991
    },
    {
        "question": " 249秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.396387247756712
    },
    {
        "question": " 2754秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.439913352622835
    },
    {
        "question": " 745億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.37322314349055086
    },
    {
        "question": " 1531億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2483614317165674
    },
    {
        "question": " 6325万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2447678858093059
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.295948580307681
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.303186477173435
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.153907261713686
    },
    {
        "question": " 149msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.171792509543174
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8753304333927177
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.179650489488377
    },
    {
        "question": " 247京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.836932472987021
    },
    {
        "question": " 7677兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.107069566960796
    },
    {
        "question": " 145億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.16175195200212
    },
    {
        "question": " 2044億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.310569161291745
    },
    {
        "question": " 893万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.950775910387428
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.41垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8823769509812656
    },
    {
        "question": " 7740兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9522462551927533
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.8垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.717642693571126
    },
    {
        "question": " 122京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.306825001602432
    },
    {
        "question": " 3461兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.539223667235696
    },
    {
        "question": " 127万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.10266050140492089
    },
    {
        "question": " 1066億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.027703800826899
    },
    {
        "question": " 4041年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1687615441646715
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.2年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.640801311322857
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.57万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0975136543534667
    },
    {
        "question": " 605億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.839131681481688
    },
    {
        "question": " 1521億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.802022124448024
    },
    {
        "question": " 174時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.019690006308487
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.45時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.531846587345562
    },
    {
        "question": " 132兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.40049171957072
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8883396115645057
    },
    {
        "question": " 135億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.352899459376879
    },
    {
        "question": " 1119万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.826850673658274
    },
    {
        "question": " 2010分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.081297633676433
    },
    {
        "question": " 164分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.994097287818546
    },
    {
        "question": " 3872兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.089112992413401
    },
    {
        "question": " 9359万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0347211407187813
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.5億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0621970635326425
    },
    {
        "question": " 1177億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.29255805508069
    },
    {
        "question": " 1057京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.52544085025105
    },
    {
        "question": " 5236兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.782479386855914
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.27兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.074373666397383
    },
    {
        "question": " 1708万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4543225017548185
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.36億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.922434620870685
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.62msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.665006043061002
    },
    {
        "question": " 227京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.85626916795742
    },
    {
        "question": " 1586億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2638008103422762
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.4兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.005158455568342
    },
    {
        "question": " 3985億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.82229229061008
    },
    {
        "question": " 9676兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.985708903443602
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.55兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.980075624372208
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.1usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.464400925193358
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.596e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.381811642793073
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.2垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.708904370831617
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.50385235233639
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.3兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7310218995982236
    },
    {
        "question": " 507兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.704729402285482
    },
    {
        "question": " 1086万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.0359970293791587
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.94万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.9975291097260617
    },
    {
        "question": " 771年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.607918896474619
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.935290046442411
    },
    {
        "question": " 8762万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.322824382696531
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.195236729700058
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.5万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5554586940006998
    },
    {
        "question": " 1742万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.860932520754445
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.71時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.54336164200414
    },
    {
        "question": " 619万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0708524115264195
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9087415017980947
    },
    {
        "question": " 101分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22802159909400377
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.46万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.317666458469354
    },
    {
        "question": " 825億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.41741615414621
    },
    {
        "question": " 45万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7162827846329733
    },
    {
        "question": " 3768億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.01981209363097
    },
    {
        "question": " 4160万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.840972606403829
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.223746428701778
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.6秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.62948399777446
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.69京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0678828483689795
    },
    {
        "question": " 9960兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.06176480422278
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4671062017052328
    },
    {
        "question": " 303万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7038720043232247
    },
    {
        "question": " 6789億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.831794432798455
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.56垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.909911709646917
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.3京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.821916509441305
    },
    {
        "question": " 995億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4417086598148765
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.59京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.776391194890149
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2132392739858364
    },
    {
        "question": " 1842万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.265252130811889
    },
    {
        "question": " 1855usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.268277983932751
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.129e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.553882205949321
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.82垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.646059341538143
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.504815954152349
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.283952849103034
    },
    {
        "question": " 2889億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4607819414928933
    },
    {
        "question": " 1471億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.167521430525924
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.0124949065726452
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.4年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.34650492690638
    },
    {
        "question": " 55万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1778936620152756
    },
    {
        "question": " 349万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.922634544625293
    },
    {
        "question": " 2680日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.586447983535464
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.987498454582472
    },
    {
        "question": " 617億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.847471956561824
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.912415156317923
    },
    {
        "question": " 784時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.672236284197579
    },
    {
        "question": " 617時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.346927790201933
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.314043061479386
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.68億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.511793477737025
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.4分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15856787828285257
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8855751538137415
    },
    {
        "question": " 8017分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.682162381218678
    },
    {
        "question": " 458兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.161796392815896
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.8万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.715238988103889
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.81万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.277003455061173
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.65996189704886
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.115642118149871
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.779715397871488
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2424436402276156
    },
    {
        "question": " 898兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.396902563327055
    },
    {
        "question": " 105億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.241400466974161
    },
    {
        "question": " 9474msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9765420461683427
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.875604273220599
    },
    {
        "question": " 6693京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.889090540102043
    },
    {
        "question": " 1148兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.503745229299333
    },
    {
        "question": " 3036億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7042184030319527
    },
    {
        "question": " 113万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.051601653138534376
    },
    {
        "question": " 752万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.8760183676827475
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.39万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.9240154830426075
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.1京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3650444870020373
    },
    {
        "question": " 3068兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5503694655628764
    },
    {
        "question": " 133垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.568632620690742
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.77兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.211655546981166
    },
    {
        "question": " 526京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.72121489699109
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.192074135302785
    },
    {
        "question": " 178万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.251605803267542
    },
    {
        "question": " 287年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.019978016578975
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.24万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.569771490153498
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.972570751528092
    },
    {
        "question": " 2537億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.841957067548782
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.593364448764314
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.66日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8270959478111988
    },
    {
        "question": " 4205億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.68122526253687
    },
    {
        "question": " 165億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.83639551810372
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.3万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.07914168289766
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.414554076130166
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.82億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.42425154738707
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.82億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.904944042386946
    },
    {
        "question": " 36分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.334338028214443
    },
    {
        "question": " 1098分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.8186687257912375
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.81京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.183195898643069
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.2兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.678424782874478
    },
    {
        "question": " 165万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.661663891562689
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6959715555103356
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.448171538644669
    },
    {
        "question": " 3310兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.021091545279237
    },
    {
        "question": " 302兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.543501171287053
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.571460717879505
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.8億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.811048636296658
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.7億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9577666836851915
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.263634276440437
    },
    {
        "question": " 4952京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1960172630646095
    },
    {
        "question": " 7635京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.946307075168566
    },
    {
        "question": " 105京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.46492861780236
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.53京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.624655689237041
    },
    {
        "question": " 6084億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.784162639523074
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.174420473953188
    },
    {
        "question": " 3397京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0323532778216666
    },
    {
        "question": " 517垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.776990294965247
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.86京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8998936160884856
    },
    {
        "question": " 8679兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.160294713118212
    },
    {
        "question": " 837億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9228079743931137
    },
    {
        "question": " 104兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.016383629029654
    },
    {
        "question": " 7565億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.87883659423728
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.776679007587556
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.17369808393618
    },
    {
        "question": " 367億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.002301739822833
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.1日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7438756209364037
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.146732949792579
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.29億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.856291284763069
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.5万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.33998571801105
    },
    {
        "question": " 96時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.760213838265342
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.93兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.119961626386088
    },
    {
        "question": " 9145万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.802816098637278
    },
    {
        "question": " 144億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.381347088385766
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9617127718603589
    },
    {
        "question": " 5513億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2425547748963
    },
    {
        "question": " 9893億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.058812910947111
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.28億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.075099719812538
    },
    {
        "question": " 4861万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.908545470576155
    },
    {
        "question": " 262万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.417563916940761
    },
    {
        "question": " 1442秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.1590671050231
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.917748694628338
    },
    {
        "question": " 1456億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2266005432878906
    },
    {
        "question": " 4711万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1167948017706097
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.5兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.860238436936305
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.035713310152042
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.7万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.986966069628631
    },
    {
        "question": " 4675msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.669818152111581
    },
    {
        "question": " 2354兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8730588557879102
    },
    {
        "question": " 1477億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23280581060507455
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.5兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3187367065577345
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.2億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0491200112889496
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.8兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6415000320569195
    },
    {
        "question": " 523万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7184014261644815
    },
    {
        "question": " 1685垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.727714858453694
    },
    {
        "question": " 1016京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.070279092259673
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.97垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.042193113983187
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.64京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.783452955952228
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.09京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.611981658528251
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.5億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.4550476742590828
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.55万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.5500717844094336
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.8万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.116460985052957
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.2万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.408119193203948
    },
    {
        "question": " 665日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2605937616970988
    },
    {
        "question": " 378日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7357886602611305
    },
    {
        "question": " 314億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.554149939163429
    },
    {
        "question": " 2326万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.986374395817434
    },
    {
        "question": " 139時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.92030169451996
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.25時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.067799792894066
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.841189335936943
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.2兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.037074968471986
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.6億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3930621976935935
    },
    {
        "question": " 634億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.024217751073223
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.7万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.220503965160736
    },
    {
        "question": " 318億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0042685705782213
    },
    {
        "question": " 189万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3389814371238462
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.81億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4352207440108025
    },
    {
        "question": " 4745秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8980458789100552
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.07717308246786
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.3京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.466494322720736
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.2億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4104367397569095
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4913620374210135
    },
    {
        "question": " 273億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.658648364858141
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.3万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4032512513572035
    },
    {
        "question": " 261msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.416877664985272
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.514747097059691
    },
    {
        "question": " 9850兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.056932335533824
    },
    {
        "question": " 686京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.28032232356078
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.02兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.001557560472999
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.9兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.59066250028549
    },
    {
        "question": " 103億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.011773043250402
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.01usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.8454319641930637
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.386e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.424761910465103
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.8垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.832560165002808
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.3兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1864192919712835
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.448716306313215
    },
    {
        "question": " 158兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.199079016448621
    },
    {
        "question": " 114万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.05674050577847756
    },
    {
        "question": " 2026億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.306583490314278
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.34年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.364323869246524
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.8年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.39098760757856
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.615134743340558
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.537691588205988
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.5万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7981779406257139
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.02億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.924743554750332
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.045236707762704
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.13万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.266831589959594
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.26時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.5228655799375135
    },
    {
        "question": " 148億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.450067671085357
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.170685497659506
    },
    {
        "question": " 1591億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.423580512638917
    },
    {
        "question": " 524分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.497449114786432
    },
    {
        "question": " 2895億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9628507970888984
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.9兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.525766820107023
    },
    {
        "question": " 5865秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.21197013475185877
    },
    {
        "question": " 293億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.688667176119798
    },
    {
        "question": " 996兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.49940496583053
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.095378816835089
    },
    {
        "question": " 1980万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7404580357971347
    },
    {
        "question": " 3779億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.799211984211304
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.33兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.801193557004002
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.6msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.760512051953096
    },
    {
        "question": " 1064京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.52828265156154
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.292112707617191
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.67京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.197150348922116
    },
    {
        "question": " 3441兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.758546484833647
    },
    {
        "question": " 722億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.858723734822559
    },
    {
        "question": " 656億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.8165901475460355
    },
    {
        "question": " 3310usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.519776080741058
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.981e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.403234850547781
    },
    {
        "question": " 101垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.068768458212556
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8836175980736438
    },
    {
        "question": " 3468兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.761894351132277
    },
    {
        "question": " 80京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.903303318082665
    },
    {
        "question": " 111億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.044904022596764
    },
    {
        "question": " 7327億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.864900339874817
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.7万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.80934801062768
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.19万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.799326520573423
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.07億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.221037825833907
    },
    {
        "question": " 509万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.086531654003448
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.8万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.970003525540793
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12426500179747779
    },
    {
        "question": " 1395時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7642987065439308
    },
    {
        "question": " 9370時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.749891967899854
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.1万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.956716474942295
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.66時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.981589947849399
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3243753592167846
    },
    {
        "question": " 1928億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.126794338787313
    },
    {
        "question": " 2984万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.696719889672552
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.299347634481803
    },
    {
        "question": " 908兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.459115613168976
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.7万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9701684165174196
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.582055783672311
    },
    {
        "question": " 498万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9189770046907535
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.86兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4949663989802264
    },
    {
        "question": " 238兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.440191027254594
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.80318165732696
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.4兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.010104467274257
    },
    {
        "question": " 1370msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13678282157229327
    },
    {
        "question": " 7060兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.349983279496901
    },
    {
        "question": " 320京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.56818301327331
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.81京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.893041590967558
    },
    {
        "question": " 417兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.842260502991521
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.2兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3835694765697655
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.5万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.648397872566596
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.9京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2723119179934874
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.37京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7040376949975986
    },
    {
        "question": " 382京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.025994731551866
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.86京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.169081753372467
    },
    {
        "question": " 238兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.376747013027654
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.1兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.991820030350064
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.34億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.523405024238544
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.6万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.018362401405266
    },
    {
        "question": " 2271年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.298767722288442
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.84268208858933
    },
    {
        "question": " 546日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17485659485991012
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7400578943696186
    },
    {
        "question": " 6814日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.991731978967093
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.2億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7316781005562945
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.745987644584241
    },
    {
        "question": " 232時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.143401979946786
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.1億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.772638356064857
    },
    {
        "question": " 379億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.420094887791604
    },
    {
        "question": " 1050分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2430934120402537
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.35分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.149447238377038
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.632118789145041
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1388168013129425
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.5億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.756430185103179
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.9億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.060955381506453
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.6秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.500144555607417
    },
    {
        "question": " 958億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.48270401548725195
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4811640893938762
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7984047880397402
    },
    {
        "question": " 694万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.063174968379676
    },
    {
        "question": " 300万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4769352582832704
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.6万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.68692697554576
    },
    {
        "question": " 2627兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9207211953192271
    },
    {
        "question": " 2468兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.455917186824385
    },
    {
        "question": " 372京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.013744360845058
    },
    {
        "question": " 4878兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.91006159473549
    },
    {
        "question": " 298万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47478602605314224
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.16万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.7893458602919199
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.7usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.952558307613161
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.9垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.190082466671705
    },
    {
        "question": " 648垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.875363310740742
    },
    {
        "question": " 648兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.255331316689151
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.2京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.606398296411364
    },
    {
        "question": " 255兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.406742608484143
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.15兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.498421797350847
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.0306055624711896
    },
    {
        "question": " 257万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.972428235191936
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.249737828618386
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.88万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.994350540121403
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7031288191682967
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4545815879472554
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.32万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.679038198646319
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.102847976437664
    },
    {
        "question": " 42時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24282358754210476
    },
    {
        "question": " 195万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.067838299070036
    },
    {
        "question": " 601時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.335254652946549
    },
    {
        "question": " 1881億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.553770825280473
    },
    {
        "question": " 3367分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.36890044541044165
    },
    {
        "question": " 139万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.365533109145251
    },
    {
        "question": " 401分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.381680703413329
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.739898150624195
    },
    {
        "question": " 9122万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.02358748124103
    },
    {
        "question": " 104万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4588841190071498
    },
    {
        "question": " 1878億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.495515257460346
    },
    {
        "question": " 472万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.674341236358705
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.83秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.893916960051108
    },
    {
        "question": " 171兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.73492000428173
    },
    {
        "question": " 152兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.246448330854564
    },
    {
        "question": " 3814兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.025042097321464
    },
    {
        "question": " 892万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.172225517367774
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.470644708794328
    },
    {
        "question": " 549兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2409787172405051
    },
    {
        "question": " 7476京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.937166307655621
    },
    {
        "question": " 1877兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.717080841357145
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.8兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.991158622050063
    },
    {
        "question": " 145億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.160692758621271
    },
    {
        "question": " 2679万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.428022279650916
    },
    {
        "question": " 977万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.989850680261782
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.83垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.084537856746512
    },
    {
        "question": " 4918京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.755312586879283
    },
    {
        "question": " 964兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4277995191833845
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.247304912803061
    },
    {
        "question": " 1017億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.007520675262401
    },
    {
        "question": " 1295兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.112382709110964
    },
    {
        "question": " 2328nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.36704341415740305
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.750816537853069
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.7万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.414608156768926
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.843559231016255
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.89億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.126827779730211
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.724767451961378
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.019180347283717
    },
    {
        "question": " 379億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.636566311722735
    },
    {
        "question": " 166億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.84075077201103
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8489834276820947
    },
    {
        "question": " 4287時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.188486581751093
    },
    {
        "question": " 380万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8595606578066861
    },
    {
        "question": " 1940億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.129470840078175
    },
    {
        "question": " 884万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.168238320727809
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.72万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.348116201059254
    },
    {
        "question": " 123兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.591834168195541
    },
    {
        "question": " 1594億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.265994378717403
    },
    {
        "question": " 2708億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.87629647106772
    },
    {
        "question": " 899秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1755884114071824
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.27万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.513928688159659
    },
    {
        "question": " 12京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.578892515340973
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.4京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.757369066276642
    },
    {
        "question": " 9190兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.406998555770064
    },
    {
        "question": " 4672億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.891312410270849
    },
    {
        "question": " 282億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.449711303768341
    },
    {
        "question": " 3545兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0507556337566
    },
    {
        "question": " 5559兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.808493606941577
    },
    {
        "question": " 479億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1236835094584918
    },
    {
        "question": " 707兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.071203989102796
    },
    {
        "question": " 1508兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.178353525604834
    },
    {
        "question": " 156億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.194096991487181
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.73垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3894711342613935
    },
    {
        "question": " 2799垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.510446419435391
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.35京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9684408780680913
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.21兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.18619377580493
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.4兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.735426287789226
    },
    {
        "question": " 1758万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.2451399424777576
    },
    {
        "question": " 4721nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.6740729959679748
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.617862180293454
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2539570727385065
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.8年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.180549697963591
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.44億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.084975364653607
    },
    {
        "question": " 8462万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.30765736024825
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.06日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.84261006350265
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3275141306788045
    },
    {
        "question": " 184時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8853525639652227
    },
    {
        "question": " 2489時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.174188638840054
    },
    {
        "question": " 8100時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.464763519228925
    },
    {
        "question": " 35億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.823172106481131
    },
    {
        "question": " 1458分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.005536846327425238
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.582141972216804
    },
    {
        "question": " 873万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.719205899491907
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6546262994989205
    },
    {
        "question": " 10万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0638921939003878
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.5億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.203318040526486
    },
    {
        "question": " 693億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.062674947321337
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.264925227051085
    },
    {
        "question": " 1901兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.78016971591931
    },
    {
        "question": " 4317億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.69867293851301
    },
    {
        "question": " 9640万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4277645192996125
    },
    {
        "question": " 4526万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.877525598543429
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.48億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.650998805672478
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.9万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.475163200965936
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.664704590227414
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2515863441356745
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6135112251006496
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.21京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.01467547032061
    },
    {
        "question": " 128兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.106422924526175
    },
    {
        "question": " 6340億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.802110353605334
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.43万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.734875786381833
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.4京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2287663101942337
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1443138005904716
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.1京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.806845547266947
    },
    {
        "question": " 789京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.118871369456372
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.169143736063193
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.9兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.9861035577327035
    },
    {
        "question": " 1793億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.253527740611998
    },
    {
        "question": " 328万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.07838261030046
    },
    {
        "question": " 426年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.350369703374215
    },
    {
        "question": " 761日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31891973252539896
    },
    {
        "question": " 8711万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.32027664765546
    },
    {
        "question": " 2813日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.607578829055917
    },
    {
        "question": " 345万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5957728683452297
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.7億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.050935539348131
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.87万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.365682458930807
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.7時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.966133796448526
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.6万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22182217962763429
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.19兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.698588388093466
    },
    {
        "question": " 211分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5470431565488809
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.71分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2118005933189844
    },
    {
        "question": " 241億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.883078624421377
    },
    {
        "question": " 582億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.828510861584638
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.751224739772743
    },
    {
        "question": " 948秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1984320625384148
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.251874579988813
    },
    {
        "question": " 927京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.468486145435781
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09095372582897832
    },
    {
        "question": " 3697万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.011584163217788
    },
    {
        "question": " 494万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9156537693625308
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.87万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4585446485879672
    },
    {
        "question": " 393京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0954617501671065
    },
    {
        "question": " 766兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9479416392112867
    },
    {
        "question": " 3401億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.975369073425739
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.3兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.485160304358372
    },
    {
        "question": " 116万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06470125581462094
    },
    {
        "question": " 1152億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.061409264023611
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.72京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3889735207771827
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.135539713182409
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.7京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8857501011839135
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.8兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9915571857388015
    },
    {
        "question": " 351億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5451057601017826
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.4億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.482384429812514
    },
    {
        "question": " 2029万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.307324092680036
    },
    {
        "question": " 1227万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.651088169459813
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.55億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.095568376368742
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1938546954887337
    },
    {
        "question": " 552万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7991404592965963
    },
    {
        "question": " 2566万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.029139557188605
    },
    {
        "question": " 232時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.92119198626883
    },
    {
        "question": " 9334万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.249398553605675
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.4兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.64758008564911
    },
    {
        "question": " 322億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.729414652210949
    },
    {
        "question": " 2523兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.903130366497369
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.02兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.843366150337631
    },
    {
        "question": " 3963秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04177618748754219
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.63501689096118
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.48秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.9285917037448534
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9125151516499395
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5322730083394356
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.644056840860122
    },
    {
        "question": " 112万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2706594054831366
    },
    {
        "question": " 167億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.222341508820977
    },
    {
        "question": " 511京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.209423652762268
    },
    {
        "question": " 9373兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.035366938899455
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.533983111828968
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4266253098454109
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.4億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.924239765317178
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.44億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.5365809417938365
    },
    {
        "question": " 393usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.593896758457209
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.7垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.453877553460379
    },
    {
        "question": " 136京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.198152788587265
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.8兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.783134357516091
    },
    {
        "question": " 1193億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2984250150562473
    },
    {
        "question": " 3927兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.594063836656716
    },
    {
        "question": " 889億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.948867627097392
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.83兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.582986333431464
    },
    {
        "question": " 71万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.793943201390743
    },
    {
        "question": " 360年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.277459683364283
    },
    {
        "question": " 395億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.03463185881651
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.606914453643116
    },
    {
        "question": " 661日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.978507712687754
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.057473993048582
    },
    {
        "question": " 280億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.505355497702354
    },
    {
        "question": " 798万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.52175105923069
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.2万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.413639168309726
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.629053759446721
    },
    {
        "question": " 240時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.936103575462017
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.292314581801158
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.936626117276191
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2472282771295
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.5分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5189068665464465
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.527811159571399
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.521838547151699
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.21億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9508292082873675
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.7万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9097053603938736
    },
    {
        "question": " 2279秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.357805916674122
    },
    {
        "question": " 2423秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.384319587947381
    },
    {
        "question": " 4943億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1951986617002475
    },
    {
        "question": " 764兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.946313810244477
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.461903577183001
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.3万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6732656759574118
    },
    {
        "question": " 5221万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.717757755174713
    },
    {
        "question": " 5658msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.7526880427833
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.132673388607415
    },
    {
        "question": " 59京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.272204388812191
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.95垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.75786011853753
    },
    {
        "question": " 225兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.795600921436586
    },
    {
        "question": " 559兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9694947923254915
    },
    {
        "question": " 8635億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.936250174661892
    },
    {
        "question": " 441万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.644613002891468
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.2垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.828472549781239
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.33京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.864594977678091
    },
    {
        "question": " 378京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.020880678153505
    },
    {
        "question": " 1567億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.41692984447981973
    },
    {
        "question": " 19兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.279532926687322
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.2273210790219498
    },
    {
        "question": " 1564億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.194227412762935
    },
    {
        "question": " 21万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.885402148491263
    },
    {
        "question": " 6079日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2215322798181905
    },
    {
        "question": " 1059日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.405293683192203
    },
    {
        "question": " 2212万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.402360852124431
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.8万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1224600584708675
    },
    {
        "question": " 57時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.311962508126317
    },
    {
        "question": " 1479万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4492208663390571
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.5万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3118647122088385
    },
    {
        "question": " 3641万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.783114595706968
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.6万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.112081916462115
    },
    {
        "question": " 485分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.463902800062526
    },
    {
        "question": " 4679万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17131477316033816
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.26兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.576250554438876
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.71万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.013044574457348
    },
    {
        "question": " 373秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7937567948514168
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.6秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.556215482432944
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.844400719027544
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.490130052035005
    },
    {
        "question": " 120億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5239248028816927
    },
    {
        "question": " 223兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.570918373386837
    },
    {
        "question": " 121億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.081115805377149
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.1万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.935231104936868
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.1兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08208745306256593
    },
    {
        "question": " 116京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.129591490195911
    },
    {
        "question": " 165兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.661167805552772
    },
    {
        "question": " 386兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8082481590204065
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.211677274538373
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.2061808542495023
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.9usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.986365742733025
    },
    {
        "question": " 102垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.511067649608713
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.7垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.900451297296414
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.26垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.36054681682551
    },
    {
        "question": " 551兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.962945438736135
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.39京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.530229272896724
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.390031628648818
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.8億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.856325306041712
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.54年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.111197978927339
    },
    {
        "question": " 1628年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.154239472716958
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.521746992247419
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.97万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9102349044839584
    },
    {
        "question": " 1652万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.59810645610005
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.52976428819346
    },
    {
        "question": " 451日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.590778932270597
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.309526905753611
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.2億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.555443905114801
    },
    {
        "question": " 186万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.046648787497826
    },
    {
        "question": " 318時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.058831224357643
    },
    {
        "question": " 634兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.081199291556524
    },
    {
        "question": " 178億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.092729572926981
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.76万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.211293987534484
    },
    {
        "question": " 3763分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.353721330814317
    },
    {
        "question": " 191分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.05874717957451
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.9億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4644309950786427
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.11兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.387696418669025
    },
    {
        "question": " 735億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.31012111505682
    },
    {
        "question": " 1047億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.241710575134288
    },
    {
        "question": " 1348秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.12953343500318
    },
    {
        "question": " 629京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.299908976290208
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.212248904874608
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.1兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.013437210111691
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4479199802944256
    },
    {
        "question": " 1217msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0853503861972027
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.2172437338002213
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.716551571317778
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.69兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6301328889971867
    },
    {
        "question": " 2001億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7448753137646145
    },
    {
        "question": " 126億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3211812192572436
    },
    {
        "question": " 417億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.619918233229764
    },
    {
        "question": " 3770億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.576388476789717
    },
    {
        "question": " 204usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.3102897527701085
    },
    {
        "question": " 243京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8874905596088476
    },
    {
        "question": " 5281兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7862251720300337
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6212314797346434
    },
    {
        "question": " 1893京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.499085942456114
    },
    {
        "question": " 810京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.908394873268609
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.1387237697062496
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.06272983074705
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5928638307321092
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.58年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.603143146004486
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.832918442613938
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.853313628047686
    },
    {
        "question": " 132億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.558878908756455
    },
    {
        "question": " 247日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7736173674787468
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.8日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.699378556447213
    },
    {
        "question": " 4771億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.736127033760361
    },
    {
        "question": " 1074時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.65087085153113
    },
    {
        "question": " 296時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.028196241936728
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.89兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.96900074504447
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.9億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.442090937405986
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.320585972863677
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.861139439997626
    },
    {
        "question": " 322分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.285464583340921
    },
    {
        "question": " 138億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6401410645423926
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.94兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.837449191714326
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.784586388140456
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.8億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.811153016945082
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.171069220749747
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.36秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.866818279354172
    },
    {
        "question": " 1002億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5019408047332918
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.59億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.725685357430117
    },
    {
        "question": " 162億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6537615580364857
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.48050212512419
    },
    {
        "question": " 166万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2195995211014274
    },
    {
        "question": " 128msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.107860681424911
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.709139441328928
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.1京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.556666405248968
    },
    {
        "question": " 1467京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.61020976272381
    },
    {
        "question": " 1670兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.444597787949361
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2957783161526644
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.261108198095763
    },
    {
        "question": " 112京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5502560960744527
    },
    {
        "question": " 119兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13872176744649245
    },
    {
        "question": " 143垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.59941824871489
    },
    {
        "question": " 288兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.681373115549935
    },
    {
        "question": " 443億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.646733290008644
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3447915174417906
    },
    {
        "question": " 344億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.537186937184376
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7901792430901406
    },
    {
        "question": " 376億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.01306983711503
    },
    {
        "question": " 4067万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.989454164837392
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.83日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.924057222684528
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.6日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.328053808407534
    },
    {
        "question": " 398億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.657810948881224
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.6億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.50071971068193
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.915316278307191
    },
    {
        "question": " 1002時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.557160933010543
    },
    {
        "question": " 3004億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.756978466690004
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.29兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.640560353574715
    },
    {
        "question": " 294万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.690792446059632
    },
    {
        "question": " 2242分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.128712472596347
    },
    {
        "question": " 2625分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.197329790420786
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.46分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.705624451671124
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.1億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3650529188333493
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.08兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.970923064977736
    },
    {
        "question": " 846万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.371123437479704
    },
    {
        "question": " 214億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.551620392350795
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.85万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.58515352558491
    },
    {
        "question": " 5052秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.703504468184178
    },
    {
        "question": " 4956億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1963465159018138
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.6京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.980583543881071
    },
    {
        "question": " 8012億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.347460187855541
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.365552097673402
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2249186327685535
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.12msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.708920880689557
    },
    {
        "question": " 695msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.841740899032404
    },
    {
        "question": " 624兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2960819784131217
    },
    {
        "question": " 1644京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.279326490440129
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.96兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4419029097383413
    },
    {
        "question": " 314億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.718954354788392
    },
    {
        "question": " 7997万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9029514899569133
    },
    {
        "question": " 6882usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.8376979170244447
    },
    {
        "question": " 728万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.86224955264558
    },
    {
        "question": " 1107京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.545516520740266
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.34垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.033935790226052
    },
    {
        "question": " 155京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.634783322966241
    },
    {
        "question": " 1811億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.479876783998906
    },
    {
        "question": " 969京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.986329692565757
    },
    {
        "question": " 4530万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6560958905916012
    },
    {
        "question": " 128万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.1056015093296963
    },
    {
        "question": " 346年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.101373382176128
    },
    {
        "question": " 8990年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.896264219267632
    },
    {
        "question": " 1066年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.748569429009375
    },
    {
        "question": " 1298万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.550813104475172
    },
    {
        "question": " 1329日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.503860921964603
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.327799285734449
    },
    {
        "question": " 275億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.497095878513157
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.4万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9701188316365412
    },
    {
        "question": " 1846万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.044307760197416
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.6時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.398793439203587
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.18兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.900646460417912
    },
    {
        "question": " 104億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.857266352180474
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3642185283959574
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.068029543294547
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.935225823285508
    },
    {
        "question": " 2234億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.850368328728553
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.2兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.709146107300386
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.88万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.90308313420706
    },
    {
        "question": " 5086万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.928239395553934
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.23435106108271
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.1秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.663671052779149
    },
    {
        "question": " 165京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.718892382746102
    },
    {
        "question": " 6937兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.90466223850529
    },
    {
        "question": " 140億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.591339486065852
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.69兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7887302921996255
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.140886842458335
    },
    {
        "question": " 505万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.70354442688286
    },
    {
        "question": " 8242msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.916050381979344
    },
    {
        "question": " 357兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0539960750296395
    },
    {
        "question": " 1423京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.216802374684649
    },
    {
        "question": " 1021兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.452568553348733
    },
    {
        "question": " 691兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.061207561927386
    },
    {
        "question": " 137兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.136466202887116
    },
    {
        "question": " 2819usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.4500199788484638
    },
    {
        "question": " 113万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.053477422985058
    },
    {
        "question": " 1272垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.605784329671749
    },
    {
        "question": " 1648兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.28048949349303
    },
    {
        "question": " 394京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.039055572277684
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.8京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.633725751626786
    },
    {
        "question": " 3782億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5777033177142927
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.484032403660923
    },
    {
        "question": " 316億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.4994850313425845
    },
    {
        "question": " 1228年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.651570474962937
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.8万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.648669677525733
    },
    {
        "question": " 117年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.788948496976706
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5463779347950046
    },
    {
        "question": " 7578万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.259779772335907
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.72日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8325217625290833
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.06日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.893867402655346
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.3兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.460375495169911
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8273935175644103
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8763812111873444
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.3万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.20268983563175
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.6億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9083551790600612
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8798062112074401
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.95万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.817931285198222
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.5万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.699604140350035
    },
    {
        "question": " 836兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.423582504878009
    },
    {
        "question": " 8548万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9953552566508757
    },
    {
        "question": " 348万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9850277457636887
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.317772025615228
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.694638504465723
    },
    {
        "question": " 209兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.38374019131483
    },
    {
        "question": " 965億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.428056226030624
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.475858686789175
    },
    {
        "question": " 8837msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9463221804224087
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.25msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.352899510226328
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.6京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8546461725228074
    },
    {
        "question": " 1839京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.32805639871192
    },
    {
        "question": " 248京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.838686868432893
    },
    {
        "question": " 5405兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.954665594394662
    },
    {
        "question": " 1676兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.224391342925735
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.6万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.6775478491460913
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.399686019075221
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.352e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.139842586845697
    },
    {
        "question": " 2768京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.505681669120182
    },
    {
        "question": " 13垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.557102680220343
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.38兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5985864917265802
    },
    {
        "question": " 5108億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7082851821458176
    },
    {
        "question": " 3396万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.530994374622826
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.0311552728201243
    },
    {
        "question": " 250年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.959375438438398
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.194877062564859
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.94年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.094556747508335
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.8億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.249586688455169
    },
    {
        "question": " 1456万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.54321647066165
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.325458419742593
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.9万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8956918424184221
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.7億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.591405349203521
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.8時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4482004535756983
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.769644324973774
    },
    {
        "question": " 1782万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5303047304791728
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8691710610522096
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.3万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7811672065134436
    },
    {
        "question": " 280分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2256088505618
    },
    {
        "question": " 5488兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.240633497767204
    },
    {
        "question": " 383万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.646241849098108
    },
    {
        "question": " 591万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.215242840220184
    },
    {
        "question": " 122億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.30731741621668
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.9万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.897289205462961
    },
    {
        "question": " 661京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.321564790073245
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.36676342629675673
    },
    {
        "question": " 8611億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.378751527324103
    },
    {
        "question": " 5381万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9526984144962363
    },
    {
        "question": " 2705億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.432117204789895
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.91京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9651536867869046
    },
    {
        "question": " 995兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.061527503278089
    },
    {
        "question": " 1178億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.514811335125572
    },
    {
        "question": " 3989兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.822717108058504
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.092200450608142
    },
    {
        "question": " 2797億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.44661805532243
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.9万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.490530820842292
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.6京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1507835939851685
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.4兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.047630879818063576
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.61597831685601
    },
    {
        "question": " 3226億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7305002612952649
    },
    {
        "question": " 443京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.646072426186588
    },
    {
        "question": " 7952兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.900463515221361
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.13億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.615795136283488
    },
    {
        "question": " 240万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.94222745150169
    },
    {
        "question": " 32年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.225879507328392
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.76893619872334
    },
    {
        "question": " 971万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.424769233396868
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4073293781165586
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.50242375576576
    },
    {
        "question": " 1926日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.221114758525438
    },
    {
        "question": " 7916万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.955994542611825
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.46億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.159192324272978
    },
    {
        "question": " 272時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9903221896526935
    },
    {
        "question": " 537兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.00902030774847
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.980960173825185
    },
    {
        "question": " 2874万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.680272303297967
    },
    {
        "question": " 6315分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.578498159449973
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.861083939039451
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.5分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.431241355100248
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.1京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.734024609904317
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.1万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6090664084823361
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.860813902493836
    },
    {
        "question": " 232秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5866795261440816
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.32兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0228169051283764
    },
    {
        "question": " 660億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.883031240321806
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.7億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.87525513274444
    },
    {
        "question": " 132万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3428485247928867
    },
    {
        "question": " 545万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7363832683665157
    },
    {
        "question": " 2474msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.393455414539872
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.3msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.799255286621245
    },
    {
        "question": " 811兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.41035686678868
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.225332857183494
    },
    {
        "question": " 1619億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6528605981776079
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.7億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.708655249866191
    },
    {
        "question": " 265億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.422617711100726
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.182316507334095
    },
    {
        "question": " 188万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.273350391674404
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.1垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.279949005242736
    },
    {
        "question": " 496兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7590059168587904
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.99兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2882613369686249
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.95京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.691228755904891
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.5億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2434066137777613
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.12億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.709394634520428
    },
    {
        "question": " 908万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.9582720642940536
    },
    {
        "question": " 6994日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2824427596711219
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.6日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.906533876081634
    },
    {
        "question": " 628万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.956219028811233
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.52億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9880012437076084
    },
    {
        "question": " 4367時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.259987358962766
    },
    {
        "question": " 19時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.834108522863961
    },
    {
        "question": " 162時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.76569040640308
    },
    {
        "question": " 394兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.875243733709778
    },
    {
        "question": " 5698分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5973435594205456
    },
    {
        "question": " 1908億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.502433334319756
    },
    {
        "question": " 5985万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.555249558126112
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.6億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.109890158412292
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.22兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.781048318658353
    },
    {
        "question": " 159万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.646117213134349
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.401536262568076
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.03万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.955681095494386
    },
    {
        "question": " 736秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.866779647876525
    },
    {
        "question": " 306兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9868182926398132
    },
    {
        "question": " 641兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.870669366865978
    },
    {
        "question": " 1466万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6098767494914037
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.963444931783343
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.3兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.633611066299471
    },
    {
        "question": " 100万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.002131322171431
    },
    {
        "question": " 305msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.484181696340746
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.2垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.388888529101614
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.3京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.58138283046294
    },
    {
        "question": " 214兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.773183122642619
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.41678577143527074
    },
    {
        "question": " 5359億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7290768061399575
    },
    {
        "question": " 4782万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.679578972235348
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.9垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.897412877825646
    },
    {
        "question": " 23京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.425150156059714
    },
    {
        "question": " 94京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.416698649909164
    },
    {
        "question": " 3571兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.774583481511451
    },
    {
        "question": " 137兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1375139753907275
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.281095021162066
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.68万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.670114215061309
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.3万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.013656520632786
    },
    {
        "question": " 13万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.056202047624836
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.751190089120857
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.722943899258383
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.3万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.202013439032182
    },
    {
        "question": " 352億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.604100751646454
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.2億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.153404346231916
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.7時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.53254883080951
    },
    {
        "question": " 309兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.769567703547875
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.65億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.40438077908163
    },
    {
        "question": " 5683万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9764392345091855
    },
    {
        "question": " 147分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9441976561554046
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.855585082686428
    },
    {
        "question": " 4470万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15153399905784126
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.6億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0059324091476265
    },
    {
        "question": " 5955万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.218588577922933
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.242499285285643
    },
    {
        "question": " 306万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.4861990435435
    },
    {
        "question": " 366京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.064322133765048
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.9億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9141575955454493
    },
    {
        "question": " 9958兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.441871351114619
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.1兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.181103434497611
    },
    {
        "question": " 1023億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.009757861562752
    },
    {
        "question": " 105万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.019677213604954
    },
    {
        "question": " 435兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1398947303008644
    },
    {
        "question": " 2960兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.534812353102474
    },
    {
        "question": " 4892兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.133157178387167
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.7億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.123466710066996
    },
    {
        "question": " 2042億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.309955107833377
    },
    {
        "question": " 758万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.8799506748160164
    },
    {
        "question": " 415万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.617546902560427
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.953e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.791919510893795
    },
    {
        "question": " 4319京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.698870110463078
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8602449548461495
    },
    {
        "question": " 545京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.958401303915663
    },
    {
        "question": " 786兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.895665018791862
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.192049419591166
    },
    {
        "question": " 1713nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.23375983127822964
    },
    {
        "question": " 2387年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.098446771915565
    },
    {
        "question": " 193億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.722315297257536
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.637397403808045
    },
    {
        "question": " 206日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.250265735453977
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.5億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.733799852910253
    },
    {
        "question": " 361億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.177533661218245
    },
    {
        "question": " 119時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8535080739913816
    },
    {
        "question": " 7719時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.443849541354048
    },
    {
        "question": " 1553万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4705068744380323
    },
    {
        "question": " 3870億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.429314127434628
    },
    {
        "question": " 746分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0944127569437423
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.888070021295056
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.8分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.501116826931465
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.8兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.424321999444956
    },
    {
        "question": " 158億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.262227293432604
    },
    {
        "question": " 110億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.484060830059864
    },
    {
        "question": " 5826万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.987243170544642
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.249826224644663
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.950843788786297
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.07035895948875
    },
    {
        "question": " 713兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.297085902389947
    },
    {
        "question": " 891億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.171918528295922
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2959904586738347
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.32垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.227098720386388
    },
    {
        "question": " 3678兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.629129878875845
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.8京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.085256574920077
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.618627645890808
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.2兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.327055648485049
    },
    {
        "question": " 223万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3484593273039396
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.2万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.383283695562676
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.727e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.738421826203368
    },
    {
        "question": " 7049京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.911637083253588
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.8兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1048076531786888
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.41兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7545431083227125
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.4京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.483503172248287
    },
    {
        "question": " 6489万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.8122042979394992
    },
    {
        "question": " 183億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.261465036437534
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.917700655032032
    },
    {
        "question": " 128万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.546384415368662
    },
    {
        "question": " 246万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.771159962480238
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.5万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.68312356333976
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.108720313308419
    },
    {
        "question": " 507時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3244826543783728
    },
    {
        "question": " 680時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.389020427992815
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.648494589865562
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.15兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2409263574873295
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.84兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.426252050547177
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.5億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7660953472769005
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.2分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.282882314955513
    },
    {
        "question": " 3408億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.033655577419884
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.538254789071462
    },
    {
        "question": " 8497秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.37298981708883905
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.348412491929771
    },
    {
        "question": " 1046兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.520524496441802
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.6兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.671775628152494
    },
    {
        "question": " 5559兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.18868518120198
    },
    {
        "question": " 5193万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.937292956806339
    },
    {
        "question": " 3660msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5634578930121448
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.6msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.659341945074678
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.736927150336496
    },
    {
        "question": " 6132京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.851093776857704
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.527782779052675
    },
    {
        "question": " 151兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.401895293145242
    },
    {
        "question": " 420億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.623649482656466
    },
    {
        "question": " 3802億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.580047525198673
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.5京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47904809007303206
    },
    {
        "question": " 153兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24871271234026548
    },
    {
        "question": " 1024兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.453801976339325
    },
    {
        "question": " 926億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1883533318164865
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.7億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5015332108952075
    },
    {
        "question": " 9731万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.988155572392305
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.1億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.929722077179217
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7865966370094206
    },
    {
        "question": " 589万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.207544855119883
    },
    {
        "question": " 793日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.279488644931173
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.8万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.515743312696696
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.2億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.884940904207113
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.1時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5979358869637741
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.803750715623805
    },
    {
        "question": " 466時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.22436900852751
    },
    {
        "question": " 921億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.24352986082663
    },
    {
        "question": " 7721万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.729344872364774
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.53万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.769187654825415
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.7万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.208798597073464
    },
    {
        "question": " 21億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8230236166513514
    },
    {
        "question": " 52万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7795270878583427
    },
    {
        "question": " 80億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.346603804049402
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.3億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.826847955404328
    },
    {
        "question": " 123兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5927245953880815
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1779904076439398
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.8兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.132242315809289
    },
    {
        "question": " 172億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4577886040998305
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.3億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.522083892979924
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.1msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.924983234590433
    },
    {
        "question": " 3694兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0687059044290446
    },
    {
        "question": " 1631億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2759308130203042
    },
    {
        "question": " 782億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3369401144094506
    },
    {
        "question": " 1914億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5038148919859866
    },
    {
        "question": " 994万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9975068195849524
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.45万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.7366611149932376
    },
    {
        "question": " 516万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.712347826413916
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.526369398108983
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.3兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.037890054760465475
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.1兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8263061273391503
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.7兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9355845099479283
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.7京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.271095229521107
    },
    {
        "question": " 115万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.06210457590074325
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.69万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.8256557482566727
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.1年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.107724232210199
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.33年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.242587904374709
    },
    {
        "question": " 1234万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.529140262244644
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.637598842507016
    },
    {
        "question": " 2503日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.334951142641607
    },
    {
        "question": " 2509万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4570015770932705
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.3時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6076987601844475
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.565701224424881
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.18時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.1771794595586655
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.4万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10151855819785727
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.6億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.776313037341449
    },
    {
        "question": " 1322万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.34292909653169
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.98951236919725
    },
    {
        "question": " 1950分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.068235787591435
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.958515439886373
    },
    {
        "question": " 958億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.045083502780083
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.67372895678014
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4527282239024983
    },
    {
        "question": " 553万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.742567005214205
    },
    {
        "question": " 59京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.271729584273613
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.62兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.999014510162503
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.7億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2934015054568553
    },
    {
        "question": " 1583万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4214107226792256
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.48万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3950571102885556
    },
    {
        "question": " 6780京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3324024634052964
    },
    {
        "question": " 2122兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.390268538233428
    },
    {
        "question": " 750京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.31897377632895
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5041558461421878
    },
    {
        "question": " 252兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.401927805669667
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.15271301996126
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.6万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.819391716502189
    },
    {
        "question": " 714垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.354644179390842
    },
    {
        "question": " 7204兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.921049272984121
    },
    {
        "question": " 3944兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.039662866579418
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.9京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.333935449759426
    },
    {
        "question": " 4646億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6670721005902287
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.6億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.4716971745988543
    },
    {
        "question": " 475億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.676876194983155
    },
    {
        "question": " 86万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.496761883131486
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.4年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.165741651804003
    },
    {
        "question": " 4129日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.053589524277827
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.66万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9432457729728725
    },
    {
        "question": " 126日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.259246397483377
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.92日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7089658374471135
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.32億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.857934174548294
    },
    {
        "question": " 330時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1378477060340142
    },
    {
        "question": " 937時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.528009037075321
    },
    {
        "question": " 1172兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.348273776311848
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.85億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.608601050807396
    },
    {
        "question": " 895億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.173557013608487
    },
    {
        "question": " 5751万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.537905480674645
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.58分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.657751227379113
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.2億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9028813434146852
    },
    {
        "question": " 325兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.575389312754336
    },
    {
        "question": " 330億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.961572115691304
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.21万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0147167767476613
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.5万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.993497756463896
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.606211630609048
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.7京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.874306095590082
    },
    {
        "question": " 116兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.506550064065998
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.6万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5363192783015258
    },
    {
        "question": " 243万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.384864871237677
    },
    {
        "question": " 709万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.850574062449324
    },
    {
        "question": " 1043msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.01825564350428
    },
    {
        "question": " 667垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.325111520561324
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0674767148002395
    },
    {
        "question": " 100京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.444619146366545
    },
    {
        "question": " 4114兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.836123589890729
    },
    {
        "question": " 344万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5362395109929285
    },
    {
        "question": " 157億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.1967635589440935
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.283359940517808
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9838312145181707
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.5垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.305717953841992
    },
    {
        "question": " 954兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4230529008513213
    },
    {
        "question": " 29兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.683605737307666
    },
    {
        "question": " 2874億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4585612671823687
    },
    {
        "question": " 142兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.152261568339407
    },
    {
        "question": " 5184万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.7146777601079295
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.53年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.597279009962702
    },
    {
        "question": " 2715万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.871483821482826
    },
    {
        "question": " 4619万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.044731972405142
    },
    {
        "question": " 9024万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.012897046124944
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6605554525161
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.8時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.177357187367871
    },
    {
        "question": " 271億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.712338078650923
    },
    {
        "question": " 176万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.088317619541577
    },
    {
        "question": " 641万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.028407859149572
    },
    {
        "question": " 962万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.761179829635587
    },
    {
        "question": " 71分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.6295859820900915
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.4分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.510686906792476
    },
    {
        "question": " 5176億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.215213903889369
    },
    {
        "question": " 973万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0516166161006746
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.8億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.781656374672236
    },
    {
        "question": " 1842秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4872325526092245
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.7300558064226
    },
    {
        "question": " 369億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06877280886884107
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.95億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5326463947961546
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6445830920957034
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.447327888543368
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.92億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.772403903180865
    },
    {
        "question": " 6948msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.841845118747653
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8869747680405533
    },
    {
        "question": " 425京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.692374714633302
    },
    {
        "question": " 1618億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6527463469115877
    },
    {
        "question": " 139兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.364626797918857
    },
    {
        "question": " 275兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.439019021804617
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.101115645415097
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.97usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.9529299271812213
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.576507771563345
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2030755243790807
    },
    {
        "question": " 3057京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.928934640488269
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.68垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.650770171435944
    },
    {
        "question": " 147京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.166308190102026
    },
    {
        "question": " 1735万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.2392680530299438
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.5万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.658242982592489
    },
    {
        "question": " 3330年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.084715591036659
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.88年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.179933422433065
    },
    {
        "question": " 9781万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.428084461038244
    },
    {
        "question": " 2483万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.775123972962394
    },
    {
        "question": " 394万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.753867400117663
    },
    {
        "question": " 130万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.170235329308705
    },
    {
        "question": " 9220時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.584546240601109
    },
    {
        "question": " 276時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.21863710403982
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.83万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.450164796436583
    },
    {
        "question": " 1034時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.570647715510985
    },
    {
        "question": " 2381万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6560685644128748
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.93兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.68237944957028
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3992955177797226
    },
    {
        "question": " 406分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.386472152349993
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.68万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.343541674846955
    },
    {
        "question": " 4576億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.161661032320746
    },
    {
        "question": " 27兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.495284797814053
    },
    {
        "question": " 191億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.724285213059494
    },
    {
        "question": " 182秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.48085329874351435
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.542859309897894
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.37兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4729964367420596
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.2京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.514230063124307
    },
    {
        "question": " 4903万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1341764521995357
    },
    {
        "question": " 189万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4980562691172394
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.417686955596414
    },
    {
        "question": " 531msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.725336715242085
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.726263697132733
    },
    {
        "question": " 488京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.751855964921754
    },
    {
        "question": " 2376億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8195660936109492
    },
    {
        "question": " 314兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.718832709919923
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.502199967254157
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.64万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6667120110646882
    },
    {
        "question": " 1580usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.198719723957186
    },
    {
        "question": " 409垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.112453961221227
    },
    {
        "question": " 564垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.81479467795982
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.5垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.849696212519333
    },
    {
        "question": " 1493京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.395880280524416
    },
    {
        "question": " 551億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7409118899529419
    },
    {
        "question": " 257兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.410544476348708
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.33万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.367625327650066
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.096929734573235
    },
    {
        "question": " 1510日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6165871511801935
    },
    {
        "question": " 2519日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.781436983902685
    },
    {
        "question": " 249日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.553886332363922
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.37322020776223
    },
    {
        "question": " 1028億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.63187511822418
    },
    {
        "question": " 1411万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.927569633310826
    },
    {
        "question": " 265万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.979867222847052
    },
    {
        "question": " 324時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.066341554186403
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.78時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.999717865694365
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2883541015057913
    },
    {
        "question": " 2388億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.219739918951815
    },
    {
        "question": " 188分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49702762472119244
    },
    {
        "question": " 189分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0537365702884545
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6404678144209042
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2158906204726403
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6835086649866629
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.35万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.088299444147559
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3631656565975954
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.4京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.252444224797444
    },
    {
        "question": " 307兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.55125446364758
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6910646535882423
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.6億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.884405088339439
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.8万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9913132553974477
    },
    {
        "question": " 147兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6676857840553807
    },
    {
        "question": " 201兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3671707686136756
    },
    {
        "question": " 295京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.914145406517907
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.57億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1006716205249512
    },
    {
        "question": " 1272億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.104420316696013
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.1億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.717150668699247
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.86垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.337254927325148
    },
    {
        "question": " 360京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.619659737434726
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.62881978341124
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.6京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.53486972768095
    },
    {
        "question": " 637億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8043367718298098
    },
    {
        "question": " 1413兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.150032223495128
    },
    {
        "question": " 1906nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.28008093527318145
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.09年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.432840613027591
    },
    {
        "question": " 3449万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.975355111409988
    },
    {
        "question": " 405日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.766152814204373
    },
    {
        "question": " 2689万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4871140708788353
    },
    {
        "question": " 5482時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3587145326217107
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.89時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5480546742824615
    },
    {
        "question": " 49時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.246799191308636
    },
    {
        "question": " 7813億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.172146781972345
    },
    {
        "question": " 8225億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.756791434115513
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3075423667702912
    },
    {
        "question": " 672分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.605512895749837
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.3分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.6972014955293515
    },
    {
        "question": " 15分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.95564502791055
    },
    {
        "question": " 117兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.570296399633207
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1453340032040753
    },
    {
        "question": " 6151万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.232639483358977
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.27万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5781146626443396
    },
    {
        "question": " 305秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.484831549508474
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.52京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.315555809675772
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.433173711386847
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.567116113555164
    },
    {
        "question": " 3101億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7133113432716085
    },
    {
        "question": " 284億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.453369463928925
    },
    {
        "question": " 338万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.52860223656784
    },
    {
        "question": " 2263垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.855922540550955
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.79兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.642512619015215
    },
    {
        "question": " 1016億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4506947269171888
    },
    {
        "question": " 154兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4092770230767595
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.4兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.23990349079136
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.1億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.756687548779663
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.3万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.693066857089624
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.2京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4977644185298788
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.6京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.016009359523547
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.5京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.164003138423187
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4002976062350854
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.135320391625669
    },
    {
        "question": " 129兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.11044800015882
    },
    {
        "question": " 3374万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.528113167283829
    },
    {
        "question": " 1568年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.757711291886604
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.012755479768527
    },
    {
        "question": " 185年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.987705704929388
    },
    {
        "question": " 3654万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.000517126655231
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.5万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.850353771787932
    },
    {
        "question": " 136万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.293258968323762
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.986543667290258
    },
    {
        "question": " 327万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.571712444655603
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.876759098265143
    },
    {
        "question": " 5609万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.527008622689943
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.98時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.555480583991952
    },
    {
        "question": " 2456億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.66962874312509
    },
    {
        "question": " 5689万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.596659498283126
    },
    {
        "question": " 401分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.824893677102746
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.3分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.677590377452006
    },
    {
        "question": " 264兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.923604598007856
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.86兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.519546432042944
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4975516157639923
    },
    {
        "question": " 5557万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.966669992211207
    },
    {
        "question": " 594秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.77393243878309
    },
    {
        "question": " 4468秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.650146382018885
    },
    {
        "question": " 727兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.362804837335654
    },
    {
        "question": " 1494億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.237934722491065
    },
    {
        "question": " 701兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.289530580058004
    },
    {
        "question": " 5122万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9312650897255677
    },
    {
        "question": " 180億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.255917912604563
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.193657935446615
    },
    {
        "question": " 8581京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4347583430732165
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.28垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.694469989165347
    },
    {
        "question": " 161兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.649446680564724
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.34634404160182
    },
    {
        "question": " 104兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.017894713918725
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.83兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.945728425587989
    },
    {
        "question": " 6678usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.824662213654511
    },
    {
        "question": " 44京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1448786670132338
    },
    {
        "question": " 174兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30489931916668045
    },
    {
        "question": " 546京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1811055162710975
    },
    {
        "question": " 4031京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.82731082638662
    },
    {
        "question": " 282兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.450570084298527
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.428724217873932
    },
    {
        "question": " 842億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.9253452249454455
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9486165234974338
    },
    {
        "question": " 2537年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.346891838326575
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.68894181792469
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5668623632492045
    },
    {
        "question": " 1250億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.154442477137685
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.4億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.168670173568945
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.149109394360863
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6855951989384055
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.9時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.3948846998939715
    },
    {
        "question": " 1269億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.38269902451059
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.2万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.400695387193783
    },
    {
        "question": " 292億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.687293041349154
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.73万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7191235981654875
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.047089666201401
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.525820663518116
    },
    {
        "question": " 796億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.96457331094229
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.5万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1113476149871624
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.4万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.158612460312034
    },
    {
        "question": " 7132兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.354383446967407
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.130910030129062
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.24億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9544044008750383
    },
    {
        "question": " 536万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.95140484268572
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.5万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.788874307333462
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.87垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.495387705962973
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.1京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6093328424971265
    },
    {
        "question": " 6291兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.242404233688581
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.9億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.844372191527176
    },
    {
        "question": " 3351兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.525138685925086
    },
    {
        "question": " 7702億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.886608640805319
    },
    {
        "question": " 117垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.567526404575331
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.71京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8202797509200273
    },
    {
        "question": " 3607京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.000877449148051
    },
    {
        "question": " 124京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3164083044119055
    },
    {
        "question": " 5376億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7304913640918405
    },
    {
        "question": " 7590兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.880246174230464
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.217665273278554
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.93年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0293339217826745
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.845708379992985
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.843004670005762
    },
    {
        "question": " 576万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.197821703425211
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.560328183825522
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.57億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.990602420771669
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.3万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.418983094887839
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.4万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.607028556475238
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.7時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.216675688021871
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.9億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.921627940377166
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.4万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7470619193865287
    },
    {
        "question": " 4168分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8417272861947176
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.4万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.536809084845746
    },
    {
        "question": " 553兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.24408187063709
    },
    {
        "question": " 1213億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.147265205903317
    },
    {
        "question": " 501億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.143893449237229
    },
    {
        "question": " 940秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1949993003609893
    },
    {
        "question": " 19兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7806567100123356
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.44億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9349675229900478
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.721936379365424
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.04兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.828390090382027
    },
    {
        "question": " 6344億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.802386680448983
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.018000695897087
    },
    {
        "question": " 137兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6372046256078356
    },
    {
        "question": " 550兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.803904380654226
    },
    {
        "question": " 228京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.801184755306076
    },
    {
        "question": " 180兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.477488328513777
    },
    {
        "question": " 356億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.552045447447714
    },
    {
        "question": " 1768usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.2474893958817015
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.34万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.727388650280197
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.790852724817812
    },
    {
        "question": " 330京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.582542376712628
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.6垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.15621262609049
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.4京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.571295820291314
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.3兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.593943505429271
    },
    {
        "question": " 135万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.12882543200042118
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.03万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.7802703020048283
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.7年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.971954093449792
    },
    {
        "question": " 22年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.284629032606519
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.97億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.339265555792561
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.6万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.804317683933619
    },
    {
        "question": " 1067日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.186410495458382
    },
    {
        "question": " 952日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.915160441883284
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.9億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.519097222028147
    },
    {
        "question": " 437万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.26027402008348
    },
    {
        "question": " 1554万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.969551704081539
    },
    {
        "question": " 6386時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.361515948528647
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.8時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.430434313162987
    },
    {
        "question": " 283万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7309555452690242
    },
    {
        "question": " 6165億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.631609063952808
    },
    {
        "question": " 245億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.6102813916696
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.8億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3922913975741555
    },
    {
        "question": " 689億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.901995661933308
    },
    {
        "question": " 4417秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08884911039909071
    },
    {
        "question": " 1079億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.254697189654188
    },
    {
        "question": " 134万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.127425435619724
    },
    {
        "question": " 158兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.700674260151564
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.61京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.726759774936234
    },
    {
        "question": " 397億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0425677287687245
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.296888543294623
    },
    {
        "question": " 143万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1567742106592247
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.78msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.943496085897458
    },
    {
        "question": " 2109京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.825350551382725
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.07341801592418
    },
    {
        "question": " 1425兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.597537190310263
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.9兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.936871778328094
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.5億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.628341586359637
    },
    {
        "question": " 187億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.27114540850773
    },
    {
        "question": " 678usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.831010481506661
    },
    {
        "question": " 295京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.971361576275379
    },
    {
        "question": " 183京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.326767348087772
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.28京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.959049729415346
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.4京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.02829345138054
    },
    {
        "question": " 765億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8836567846254815
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.22億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.5077310717529033
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.2634199155028714
    },
    {
        "question": " 260万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.976953510393155
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.976142829998306
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7510174843772255
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.612631796015803
    },
    {
        "question": " 215万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7703452766030345
    },
    {
        "question": " 3467日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9201332781904314
    },
    {
        "question": " 344万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.694420048512887
    },
    {
        "question": " 5684日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.691148029861468
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.6日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.492291586765937
    },
    {
        "question": " 9880億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.052245606920577
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.54万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.02539479171102
    },
    {
        "question": " 148時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.949852224097489
    },
    {
        "question": " 196万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.848336199697126
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.7万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2221403265729216
    },
    {
        "question": " 109億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8801022821539455
    },
    {
        "question": " 218分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5594510198816227
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.6分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6898504116106547
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.697633143346735
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.254603776902012
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.1万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1261810053676977
    },
    {
        "question": " 4190万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.844092943275106
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.147369161719984
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.3京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.886949164977335
    },
    {
        "question": " 1900兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.342301523984917
    },
    {
        "question": " 370億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.01182388858217
    },
    {
        "question": " 239兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.600131720576877
    },
    {
        "question": " 4006億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.602743583829156
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.502657371342524
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.194411162907524
    },
    {
        "question": " 11京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.542152527254574
    },
    {
        "question": " 1258兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1632563374431
    },
    {
        "question": " 259億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8570169536660455
    },
    {
        "question": " 5565億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9673218103043526
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2604097820084768
    },
    {
        "question": " 256億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.408256583858954
    },
    {
        "question": " 275usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.438776974572782
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.861082036846522
    },
    {
        "question": " 548兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8023067945566009
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.3兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3625264445474796
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.576631952603774
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24558427425395268
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.0334262770042395
    },
    {
        "question": " 432万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.6353611200531732
    },
    {
        "question": " 4708年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.235094646463683
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5882086051804905
    },
    {
        "question": " 3696万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.005385616603206
    },
    {
        "question": " 6094日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.165123382110108
    },
    {
        "question": " 135万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.289393902584665
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.99万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.537906669423338
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.10864314362953
    },
    {
        "question": " 4063億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.666309850705856
    },
    {
        "question": " 189万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.89553330534919
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.82時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.389971617573704
    },
    {
        "question": " 115兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.33941568503051
    },
    {
        "question": " 1468億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.008238755008463
    },
    {
        "question": " 645分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0317296103811513
    },
    {
        "question": " 1737万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.018064576583416
    },
    {
        "question": " 2019分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.083274185931655
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.19億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1236152056061555
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.8兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.733772162527814
    },
    {
        "question": " 2706億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.876079876977354
    },
    {
        "question": " 149万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.396167820978344
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.400515067058411
    },
    {
        "question": " 3588秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.554808106063103
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.022365798295535
    },
    {
        "question": " 9747万msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05238991204326138
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.33兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.364521228271229
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.8万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8734969976005125
    },
    {
        "question": " 24億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.379634697341409
    },
    {
        "question": " 208万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.319040491065161
    },
    {
        "question": " 793msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.899141023104022
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.2垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.805875070618967
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.8兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.881434823884571
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.5京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.12011247788828
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.42京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.955494605245667
    },
    {
        "question": " 1878万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2736385970600428
    },
    {
        "question": " 2084億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.318989246322847
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.3垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.461607963017624
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.4垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.595282650342895
    },
    {
        "question": " 196垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.735271146085502
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.17兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.011877398815484
    },
    {
        "question": " 4448兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.648138416939928
    },
    {
        "question": " 539万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.7319286591140373
    },
    {
        "question": " 2407nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.3814521284591199
    },
    {
        "question": " 2635年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.98313956521189
    },
    {
        "question": " 2657年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.366957009191431
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.4年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.257349562943205
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.25億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.789195593346318
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.580511352524202
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.83日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.741324000828522
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.370935275621529
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.411048491020937
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.87兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.644753323611653
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.7億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.995223470342995
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.6万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.725713413841171
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.93時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.022896860455653
    },
    {
        "question": " 269万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7092470282646246
    },
    {
        "question": " 830億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.760847991612307
    },
    {
        "question": " 3637分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7826380412913134
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.8万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2673823282220855
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.823123884831522
    },
    {
        "question": " 2592億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.477179561954687
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.472920657568182
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.5万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.746542086263772
    },
    {
        "question": " 1325秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.122260393147544
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.16秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.618773398358325
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.3兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4006538861209656
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.46兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.712385323119069
    },
    {
        "question": " 623億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.23824940022217
    },
    {
        "question": " 4485億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.873579218396635
    },
    {
        "question": " 2246万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.35146961646274
    },
    {
        "question": " 336万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.526450375348105
    },
    {
        "question": " 144兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6602444276249853
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.5兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9692195217532733
    },
    {
        "question": " 340億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9751147394749293
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.79京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.799965342835145
    },
    {
        "question": " 120兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.078878675463738
    },
    {
        "question": " 1325万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.1222361507911955
    },
    {
        "question": " 6296京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3002987984034715
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.19京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5667239985805157
    },
    {
        "question": " 1186兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.517798335532573
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.313547780286637
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.25兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.511755667371702
    },
    {
        "question": " 6687万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.8252424809507595
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.045289326671285
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.931514977147538
    },
    {
        "question": " 2983年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.417111977258648
    },
    {
        "question": " 1581万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.636536366335806
    },
    {
        "question": " 6322日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.181040843757241
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.1日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.033826545029113
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4143818527179945
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.9万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.636261725551289
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.58万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.173587651311548
    },
    {
        "question": " 170時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.009773971569562
    },
    {
        "question": " 122億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.365032011936835
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.03180603854463
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.41万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.755190337360698
    },
    {
        "question": " 110分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.819918931178503
    },
    {
        "question": " 5757万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2614277428766376
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.074451129819561
    },
    {
        "question": " 412万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.058240268187026
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.1万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.584945865039492
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.88万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.588384437191079
    },
    {
        "question": " 2135秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.329346776708356
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.92京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.966076561875571
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24041825752399437
    },
    {
        "question": " 623億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.237925249781734
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.5兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.869997725798909
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.51兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.5457030556951
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.52msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.401055786763607
    },
    {
        "question": " 1795msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.254172560347179
    },
    {
        "question": " 194垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.788283414039284
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.8兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.825652774874987
    },
    {
        "question": " 2363兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.817072490428603
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.5億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0577459714922197
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.4兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.773875129180271
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.2199298260731206
    },
    {
        "question": " 142垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.654041880439048
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.11垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.555714802458819
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.9兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.269183561422771
    },
    {
        "question": " 5036億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9239712865593275
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0342276682078295
    },
    {
        "question": " 630億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.7991356377472805
    },
    {
        "question": " 2865億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.45709850642127
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.91万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.405820932629574
    },
    {
        "question": " 137万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.575525801057209
    },
    {
        "question": " 30日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.85706127107464
    },
    {
        "question": " 4647日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8255448804989705
    },
    {
        "question": " 418万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.678527052161359
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8090077121275447
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.2兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.626297249457382
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.19億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.698297628706989
    },
    {
        "question": " 869億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.160648191899531
    },
    {
        "question": " 2348分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1488744692660156
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.9万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.888149107257332
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.869818803818033
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.219841380461875
    },
    {
        "question": " 639億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.24945356566569
    },
    {
        "question": " 261秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6386318651264922
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.57秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.5532610786225605
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.32秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.800713612595066
    },
    {
        "question": " 6747京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.330333575843383
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.05京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.67144184244583
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.02億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0477901684624156
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.4万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.758239726308948
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.16万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8551585493795864
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.283051141404791
    },
    {
        "question": " 5715京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.258184438749068
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.7兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0067197068029685
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.6億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05184934739853708
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2267880070779835
    },
    {
        "question": " 2930兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.466822483157596
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.211096790534993
    },
    {
        "question": " 1975usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.295645004792048
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.091e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.539147795744963
    },
    {
        "question": " 571兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8202830711448883
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.6垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.327873753073037
    },
    {
        "question": " 5088兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.928439446804319
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3041418728869374
    },
    {
        "question": " 204万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.3098529375956083
    },
    {
        "question": " 107億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.029868686887609
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.9万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.174420987654774
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.52兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.984033378172182
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.2日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3158359177251375
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.224561349104885
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1212938681664244
    },
    {
        "question": " 1821万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.880176673843144
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.894798675255843
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.706798420578125
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.7527157866711285
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4442465155492945
    },
    {
        "question": " 9500億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.819366103759851
    },
    {
        "question": " 235億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.592830700531195
    },
    {
        "question": " 6348分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.580787110991182
    },
    {
        "question": " 340億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0332565981503503
    },
    {
        "question": " 245兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.452853091626027
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.638509834242981
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.470249608529339
    },
    {
        "question": " 1154秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.06229300057045
    },
    {
        "question": " 6224兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.295266243913161
    },
    {
        "question": " 3889億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6533652017702254
    },
    {
        "question": " 4797兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.124676150119297
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.6万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5753322693255158
    },
    {
        "question": " 176億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.246570205949019
    },
    {
        "question": " 1272兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6058137852908594
    },
    {
        "question": " 606兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.845663060403657
    },
    {
        "question": " 298京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.918391684401124
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.11億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5463105412740554
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.264580551884913
    },
    {
        "question": " 638万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.804699478242388
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.099780198830741
    },
    {
        "question": " 6533垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.316279707422116
    },
    {
        "question": " 5900京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.834326369095603
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9868900792869206
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.93京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.689045197711594
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.2億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6255261711955606
    },
    {
        "question": " 75億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.875128595522146
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.2万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.6353500161674215
    },
    {
        "question": " 8625年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4980740991336905
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.82年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.081003832674892
    },
    {
        "question": " 1715日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6720039741053951
    },
    {
        "question": " 9066日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.8938939071029
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.35492201844385507
    },
    {
        "question": " 501時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3192445058138158
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6137396209368635
    },
    {
        "question": " 538億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.572040954484476
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.2億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.06849170711659
    },
    {
        "question": " 360分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.33466684781174
    },
    {
        "question": " 50分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.477100856446695
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.5兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.177505591138127
    },
    {
        "question": " 449万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7157214116597697
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.7億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.157389273950724
    },
    {
        "question": " 4014億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.825402874491074
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.42万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.53384924481084
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.59秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.981686515663762
    },
    {
        "question": " 5122京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.210605366571006
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.64億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6246840928660768
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.06億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2927287906352234
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.5億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.044911886598417
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.22万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5074604993289165
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.559808025984987
    },
    {
        "question": " 118兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.13364537882849
    },
    {
        "question": " 188京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.717026882811062
    },
    {
        "question": " 1728億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.459270563812397
    },
    {
        "question": " 389万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5896473992560836
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.117162789143716
    },
    {
        "question": " 133万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.12387184743176
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.753298229784665
    },
    {
        "question": " 1122京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.113493004883962
    },
    {
        "question": " 1298兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.556903741544229
    },
    {
        "question": " 4870億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9094049979485908
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.45兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.537946340378059
    },
    {
        "question": " 5255兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.720565399077774
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.5万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.751923725057913
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.15年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.432824993197837
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.9年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.45263910183969
    },
    {
        "question": " 118万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5113714672082006
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.8万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.980038690885029
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.16万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.658395059869683
    },
    {
        "question": " 2336日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.30491427262854
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.8兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.811954985097971
    },
    {
        "question": " 164億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.833802330076104
    },
    {
        "question": " 749万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.65264712637052
    },
    {
        "question": " 365時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.11829352971349
    },
    {
        "question": " 1735時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.79571874994231
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.423203605501142
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.33万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.208835282887084
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.8億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.597687988290164
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3351303954497338
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.003299793849294
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.7兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1610517943559255
    },
    {
        "question": " 217兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.39978656053497
    },
    {
        "question": " 4384万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.085539766006196
    },
    {
        "question": " 6223秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0158447011945437
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.326542154539717
    },
    {
        "question": " 1501億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6775878182637796
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.28京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.695226265846443
    },
    {
        "question": " 6833万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2783167918495197
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.1万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.136230567208435
    },
    {
        "question": " 3416億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.5335084077813
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.86万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.586562668313716
    },
    {
        "question": " 288兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9609764483436756
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.7兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.777271669782003
    },
    {
        "question": " 159京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.644504746581516
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47088820426704037
    },
    {
        "question": " 599億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.777176919430751
    },
    {
        "question": " 108億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.035356308002712
    },
    {
        "question": " 879usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.943827670568931
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.081e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.819463473850132
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.19京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9204848013096862
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.27京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.165203480777397
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.1京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.986371195278014
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.4京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.379970205536599
    },
    {
        "question": " 1075億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.031362591815394
    },
    {
        "question": " 3104億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.491882527867785
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.2万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.348761762913572
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.03万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.547550995221457
    },
    {
        "question": " 948年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.697462338593803
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4837482083709728
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.412024658326583
    },
    {
        "question": " 686万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.994528616929557
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.9日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.366045230429737
    },
    {
        "question": " 13兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.173049658701599
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.1億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.037230188159588
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.82万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.461522854225983
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.9時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.436391705813185
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3197613553810092
    },
    {
        "question": " 2666万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.267471169464336
    },
    {
        "question": " 145分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3829126728365495
    },
    {
        "question": " 652分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.592333646068777
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.7分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.279230404886697
    },
    {
        "question": " 102分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.788848636331718
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.864161897035356
    },
    {
        "question": " 700兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.908363089503466
    },
    {
        "question": " 246億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.835367895389828
    },
    {
        "question": " 281秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6711159459313687
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.337131372585796
    },
    {
        "question": " 2398秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.379932234827848
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.28京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.46890533529913
    },
    {
        "question": " 2707億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4960121626900795
    },
    {
        "question": " 2549万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8501408558645518
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.49億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7642759333079567
    },
    {
        "question": " 1546万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.189176257550571
    },
    {
        "question": " 2158msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.3340336098813
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.7msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.564918409678567
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.8兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2553847548533972
    },
    {
        "question": " 5921京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.835893816550364
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.97兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.219437114015331
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.33兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.858120550243079
    },
    {
        "question": " 104万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.015569613166740437
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.069338127770151
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.267606498575488
    },
    {
        "question": " 202垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8076074150083805
    },
    {
        "question": " 3992垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.664682436751287
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.41兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2505567758276306
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.5兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5536960029145916
    },
    {
        "question": " 133兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.124146246970557
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.2兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.558660664350453
    },
    {
        "question": " 1240万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.093408762556145
    },
    {
        "question": " 254年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.125858026199408
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.42万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8211365900756649
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.709414576970239
    },
    {
        "question": " 2221日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.504910689397705
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.40724997603197
    },
    {
        "question": " 1153万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1193776358829837
    },
    {
        "question": " 319万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.123348182312952
    },
    {
        "question": " 1564万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.972473984857842
    },
    {
        "question": " 4738万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.954921037752625
    },
    {
        "question": " 1883億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.11652342281389
    },
    {
        "question": " 577分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9826499719525494
    },
    {
        "question": " 313兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.996221920727116
    },
    {
        "question": " 798億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.965380673712391
    },
    {
        "question": " 3434億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.979535884025695
    },
    {
        "question": " 3719秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7922349287229578
    },
    {
        "question": " 1885秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.275398739525349
    },
    {
        "question": " 1255秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.09869993411941
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.48秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.541895792781498
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.97京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.100006075685293
    },
    {
        "question": " 138億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2029457697122403
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4916977244009075
    },
    {
        "question": " 2857万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6777363902729334
    },
    {
        "question": " 8420msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9253171189095266
    },
    {
        "question": " 6231msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.794578519902329
    },
    {
        "question": " 3081兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9898602032314927
    },
    {
        "question": " 1520兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.24523961210822
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.4京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.975272635942065
    },
    {
        "question": " 2355兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.593861135259418
    },
    {
        "question": " 4607万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6634285726432074
    },
    {
        "question": " 909万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.9587646944882806
    },
    {
        "question": " 516usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.712874191560489
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.94京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.27469356198783657
    },
    {
        "question": " 1515京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.24377536804829
    },
    {
        "question": " 995兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4415371475263727
    },
    {
        "question": " 1709兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.454519457965979
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.3京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.709771923528697
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.27791509339585
    },
    {
        "question": " 397億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.59845191853832
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.87年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.779294830220424
    },
    {
        "question": " 1239日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5306451404348633
    },
    {
        "question": " 589万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.1503060539851
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.196728220732304
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.9億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.679227480403911
    },
    {
        "question": " 8508時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.549624441470634
    },
    {
        "question": " 2859時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.234374106338051
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.7万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.435396367702737
    },
    {
        "question": " 2482時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.951167095590513
    },
    {
        "question": " 6456億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.089335604031981
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.15億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.339852376205144
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.42億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.867332197674952
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.39分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1566502034583577
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.94兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.452722094609216
    },
    {
        "question": " 3608万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6207396034610597
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.587974814983147
    },
    {
        "question": " 1249秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.318365326464389
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.856056543660657
    },
    {
        "question": " 2903秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.462796027286027
    },
    {
        "question": " 253京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.90403240467064
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4053610557518861
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6637743061433052
    },
    {
        "question": " 184万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4866365106654245
    },
    {
        "question": " 3026万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.480813668891152
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.543121478462435
    },
    {
        "question": " 790msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.89753526325316
    },
    {
        "question": " 4756京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1784443627722885
    },
    {
        "question": " 362兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6222824177057564
    },
    {
        "question": " 129京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.553168826172698
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.85兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.215195750768058
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.1兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.281952951431014
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.8万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.9442506823339478
    },
    {
        "question": " 9764usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.98961836153687
    },
    {
        "question": " 939京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.473768249665942
    },
    {
        "question": " 531垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.78889261647917
    },
    {
        "question": " 2895京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9053259012905315
    },
    {
        "question": " 4194億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8444658892941848
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.9兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.856965673112576
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.4846576877118465
    },
    {
        "question": " 89億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.94924406497027
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.1万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.5070472400453
    },
    {
        "question": " 4909年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.411607278447566
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.93万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.434511402352284
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.3万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.239589888563753
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.7日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.962674020488484
    },
    {
        "question": " 134日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.06411518269231
    },
    {
        "question": " 4021億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6618569794875935
    },
    {
        "question": " 187時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8919172190689795
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8680513010291477
    },
    {
        "question": " 153時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.740278467286291
    },
    {
        "question": " 2265億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.634418616038705
    },
    {
        "question": " 9739分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8301762452789418
    },
    {
        "question": " 959分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2038375425742653
    },
    {
        "question": " 120万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8563553780360476
    },
    {
        "question": " 8243分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.694243550871327
    },
    {
        "question": " 125兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5987806080053515
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.36兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.702983991917272
    },
    {
        "question": " 9715秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43113980213037695
    },
    {
        "question": " 252秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6226046233317484
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.57京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.911563366103627
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.01億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9670749045544391
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.35兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.17182893764199
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.1万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6210854408806099
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.41万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3826146602922662
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.7msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.4273097606392104
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.39垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.879294668676343
    },
    {
        "question": " 155兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2541044223374316
    },
    {
        "question": " 605京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.225590305742088
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4720479618514855
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.308173387265816
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.5億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.94704136435648
    },
    {
        "question": " 546京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2382814319302735
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.432021953231865
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.552009550251272
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.92京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.120748772186847
    },
    {
        "question": " 1276億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.105955600800531
    },
    {
        "question": " 2791兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.4457001474084
    },
    {
        "question": " 249万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.396022802655204
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.96万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.159993208250809
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.5年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.218837500273559
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7402879980208408
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.252383658012772
    },
    {
        "question": " 2202万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4002667623832386
    },
    {
        "question": " 478時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2995421435486243
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.687065160035241
    },
    {
        "question": " 620万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0718094911452103
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.021694997960327
    },
    {
        "question": " 409分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8336145377739412
    },
    {
        "question": " 694分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.61937984038436
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.57分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.711175418545773
    },
    {
        "question": " 9970万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49990422287604197
    },
    {
        "question": " 3800万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.64330814053948
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.802986621560952
    },
    {
        "question": " 2390億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.60015747768486
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.66万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.752616403547817
    },
    {
        "question": " 1007億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5040343479985809
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.26050841989736173
    },
    {
        "question": " 1069億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.472796030850161
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.729193963382622
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.26万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8610709571131934
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.7万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.393252539682614
    },
    {
        "question": " 1244京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.595924976720859
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.6京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.052985200381039
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7879812975448823
    },
    {
        "question": " 596兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.997287207660902
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.070952432114983
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.072174354040053
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.03usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.904531180449581
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.2京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8846272030048696
    },
    {
        "question": " 1244垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.158290694119644
    },
    {
        "question": " 406京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0520199464330515
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.3京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.793639102937943
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.9兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2987817031238365
    },
    {
        "question": " 162万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.2104699308177571
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.5億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.677088404349528
    },
    {
        "question": " 1424年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.874234452805512
    },
    {
        "question": " 445億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.08558183866592
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.49日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.922673043456885
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.27万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.076019290596632
    },
    {
        "question": " 6376万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.862031927617636
    },
    {
        "question": " 309億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.109237971007426
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.1万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.837701078118766
    },
    {
        "question": " 649兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.09144267768188
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.099740926161726
    },
    {
        "question": " 181万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.479587222991638
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.050679470876805
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.935880501285169
    },
    {
        "question": " 2166万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3990986845621673
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.99億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.919154349308389
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.1万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7002511049349227
    },
    {
        "question": " 2538京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.905769040294196
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.93兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.836690489811132
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6497188427082055
    },
    {
        "question": " 2391万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6004566148943873
    },
    {
        "question": " 535億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.728177276525381
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.9兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4645261640894771
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.1兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3871519583912293
    },
    {
        "question": " 495億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.138214570318018
    },
    {
        "question": " 767兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.106884234090605
    },
    {
        "question": " 335兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.524781435628343
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.12兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.493957777255424
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.312175202061372
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.42e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.475249618758156
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.6京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7585807051619593
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.73京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.331891086305827
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.2兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0924810514341114
    },
    {
        "question": " 7128億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8529405235383773
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.55億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.7444895866655497
    },
    {
        "question": " 1237万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.092285680979715
    },
    {
        "question": " 2032年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8701956253425145
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.823815373694265
    },
    {
        "question": " 970億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.424480071467409
    },
    {
        "question": " 8801万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.324746218695562
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.5万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.744313172055552
    },
    {
        "question": " 1147日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.99604458332939
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.25万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7773443118781098
    },
    {
        "question": " 157万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.816882446269957
    },
    {
        "question": " 789時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.453505203304074
    },
    {
        "question": " 332万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8007137691551258
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.2万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3461380200213047
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.351811257054781
    },
    {
        "question": " 111万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.822799045887965
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.834030965737394
    },
    {
        "question": " 90兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.455478757056606
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.6兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.975398747020066
    },
    {
        "question": " 669万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.268949282831608
    },
    {
        "question": " 127億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.326403827781396
    },
    {
        "question": " 5786億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.263568997438369
    },
    {
        "question": " 619億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8554191371328894
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.15億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.232684748927598
    },
    {
        "question": " 1579万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4202615075649794
    },
    {
        "question": " 9497億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.977582622628852
    },
    {
        "question": " 14万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.147489270112391
    },
    {
        "question": " 9546兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.481000973725851
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.3兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4830938046909523
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.713017627163907
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.71827961685385
    },
    {
        "question": " 148兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.17141764294557
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.128646216483153
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.748131490255846
    },
    {
        "question": " 5194垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.778973374209633
    },
    {
        "question": " 3119兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9377262188001083
    },
    {
        "question": " 547京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9594587962218375
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.448346376973618
    },
    {
        "question": " 3618億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.558527049920766
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.6万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.712290777820485
    },
    {
        "question": " 110年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.605420269415564
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.28年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.804843109682063
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.634278773683305
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.7日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0497976942850844
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.81万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.103278879873578
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.45日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.474647536406621
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.54万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4619043187457783
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7073046119481194
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.000585088115484
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.5万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.39857992271978
    },
    {
        "question": " 694万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1206381158955847
    },
    {
        "question": " 5824億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.606851030563963
    },
    {
        "question": " 5899分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9926630218578145
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.7分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3463791548686586
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.9兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.497048333116633
    },
    {
        "question": " 6068億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.846525713729246
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6903276230370923
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.02億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9228715708192325
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.155211724173418
    },
    {
        "question": " 9508京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.479289658979752
    },
    {
        "question": " 182億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3233974954812107
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.9億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7431022012743975
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.477284566964449
    },
    {
        "question": " 6289億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.79856240703732
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.4msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.483527412905616
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.92垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.45180265324869
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1362505658242572
    },
    {
        "question": " 1946兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.732740142833864
    },
    {
        "question": " 1243兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.316282536691265
    },
    {
        "question": " 916万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9620099879900612
    },
    {
        "question": " 17万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.230980275595147
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.340635211616569
    },
    {
        "question": " 124垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.595679181072006
    },
    {
        "question": " 2257垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.417077911894129
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.7垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.931514141188373
    },
    {
        "question": " 3762京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.797283593528721
    },
    {
        "question": " 2402兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.380517341677851
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.43億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.5350277698712977
    },
    {
        "question": " 132億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.121613443733961
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.09年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5054853917773015
    },
    {
        "question": " 41億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0509002515974135
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.493908787504317
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.52日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.559520761875181
    },
    {
        "question": " 1381日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.0767328551192
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.44兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.86618144135445
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.852020826428335
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.5億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.240730404088666
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.977403389538275
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.7万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1343137475198946
    },
    {
        "question": " 1022分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.787439983181515
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.1兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.734274914222468
    },
    {
        "question": " 3012億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5422996950018275
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5436008010262527
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.413825698927774
    },
    {
        "question": " 130秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.115343362497683
    },
    {
        "question": " 5104兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.209077714746703
    },
    {
        "question": " 464億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7297519907720713
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.25兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.409791187618932
    },
    {
        "question": " 3383億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.751187100113344
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.15兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.91120415893063
    },
    {
        "question": " 593msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.773271631985789
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.9垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.092559830283303
    },
    {
        "question": " 1794億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31739720529250004
    },
    {
        "question": " 1486兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.615862799953582
    },
    {
        "question": " 1495億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.396623984430014
    },
    {
        "question": " 597億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.775861894554599
    },
    {
        "question": " 149万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.1729513701960634
    },
    {
        "question": " 584万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.766232835984118
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.783e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.079047130842136
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.233997547357592
    },
    {
        "question": " 148兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6142718028415504
    },
    {
        "question": " 3360億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7481274550720762
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.5京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.512233578354627
    },
    {
        "question": " 2909億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.463716772315866
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.09億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.850342581332399
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.08年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0507372741615892
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.997661857003633
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.5万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8443436864085148
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.8万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.653337274832212
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.6万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.549765093443792
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.42万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.861611226810542
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.5日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.342765421110771
    },
    {
        "question": " 300億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.53502167343734
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7871107192150966
    },
    {
        "question": " 188万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.051756106826728
    },
    {
        "question": " 5722時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.313850769800009
    },
    {
        "question": " 242億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.663705880259594
    },
    {
        "question": " 975億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.830860313577272
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.01億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.921667944366608
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.3分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.521142455211954
    },
    {
        "question": " 4682億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.17164207139674
    },
    {
        "question": " 116兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.127267368898504
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.664754847744967
    },
    {
        "question": " 1053億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.244157836139193
    },
    {
        "question": " 625万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.796039902840047
    },
    {
        "question": " 2812兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.950209278303128
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.152295837146853
    },
    {
        "question": " 7215億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.301959161651863
    },
    {
        "question": " 295兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.691883929338292
    },
    {
        "question": " 2億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.300129757470906
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.85msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.835486918558768
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.7msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.962316663154373
    },
    {
        "question": " 796兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4023839287533313
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.88京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.522404173339337
    },
    {
        "question": " 253兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.847155567091727
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.6兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.735459682152414
    },
    {
        "question": " 6370億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.804118400982378
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.1万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.4789164298975166
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.04usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.847385986390398
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.3京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8486003798142872
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.1垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.78884270963899
    },
    {
        "question": " 1873兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7163325617362313
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.34垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.745300442963512
    },
    {
        "question": " 2373兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.375286915839538
    },
    {
        "question": " 6832兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.834545459084282
    },
    {
        "question": " 784億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.894136138063911
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.66万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.126341070709637
    },
    {
        "question": " 173年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.959881931292849
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.1年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.232307272652573
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6157589235181735
    },
    {
        "question": " 2141日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.71090794000779
    },
    {
        "question": " 122万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.244272360181665
    },
    {
        "question": " 6213万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8508241202849067
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.92万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9040979967638423
    },
    {
        "question": " 5784万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.540399645445842
    },
    {
        "question": " 187万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.828798649759348
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.581993800137118
    },
    {
        "question": " 1326万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9643342836442663
    },
    {
        "question": " 8619万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1572852725820155
    },
    {
        "question": " 178万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.029757908856766
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.94分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.065598252232521
    },
    {
        "question": " 382兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.082881447390285
    },
    {
        "question": " 7480億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.937396636742975
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.92億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.036738846488788
    },
    {
        "question": " 2187秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5616192016137043
    },
    {
        "question": " 318秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.501797830732057
    },
    {
        "question": " 6457京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.311242706469898
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5471155168635977
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.9億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8212238487439945
    },
    {
        "question": " 8872億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.169882881102909
    },
    {
        "question": " 2637万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.421098614436206
    },
    {
        "question": " 298msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.473759874050975
    },
    {
        "question": " 4602京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1641348863563605
    },
    {
        "question": " 9205億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.027536650811628
    },
    {
        "question": " 2315兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.808299969500176
    },
    {
        "question": " 2349兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.592660841040678
    },
    {
        "question": " 610兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.785255095134207
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.2529334241889833
    },
    {
        "question": " 4995usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.698578143846823
    },
    {
        "question": " 300垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.978555090683313
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.3京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7900443529701535
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5865480625978154
    },
    {
        "question": " 383京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.80458965491661
    },
    {
        "question": " 527京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.721994940743224
    },
    {
        "question": " 4005億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.602565346288503
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.41億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.381816101593797
    },
    {
        "question": " 116年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.008026442666031
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.450799015149645
    },
    {
        "question": " 166日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5997729015298265
    },
    {
        "question": " 186日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.427516875978453
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.266196347841166
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.4万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3670918161622725
    },
    {
        "question": " 1075時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6512199806231431
    },
    {
        "question": " 4909時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.247260540581815
    },
    {
        "question": " 855兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.211401699474457
    },
    {
        "question": " 789万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.738497674828676
    },
    {
        "question": " 8811分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1668794152641735
    },
    {
        "question": " 866万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.715466575092861
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.79万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.669876127801677
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.7京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.943624981049716
    },
    {
        "question": " 4428万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.709731054875765
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.66兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.007702970644734
    },
    {
        "question": " 3382億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.751009561685004
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.542495843026986
    },
    {
        "question": " 1164億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5672061392139061
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3242891734700875
    },
    {
        "question": " 1137億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.499346475653397
    },
    {
        "question": " 4779億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.901156571900428
    },
    {
        "question": " 1020msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.008795036278244073
    },
    {
        "question": " 742msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.870175163803956
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.81msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.7644292565044495
    },
    {
        "question": " 162垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.71084277548959
    },
    {
        "question": " 3164京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.563741479411119
    },
    {
        "question": " 1822兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.704288211240299
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.8億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.145333387016992
    },
    {
        "question": " 518億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7142208779648875
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.8億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.96733492622034
    },
    {
        "question": " 6437usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.808693084169677
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.124e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.288206630196413
    },
    {
        "question": " 452京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.718756944801667
    },
    {
        "question": " 399京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.044134892694057
    },
    {
        "question": " 1066京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.249634790907422
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.9億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4893332119738736
    },
    {
        "question": " 714兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.85342399731924
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.92万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.7721436370916743
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.768136283483612
    },
    {
        "question": " 387年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.308635402992307
    },
    {
        "question": " 1202日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5177681231282782
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.3万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.78287553618876
    },
    {
        "question": " 5558万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8024334720274435
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.9万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3748122125911575
    },
    {
        "question": " 534時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.505784213428886
    },
    {
        "question": " 1052万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3012511738026256
    },
    {
        "question": " 1311億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.959096705581289
    },
    {
        "question": " 488分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9106028482901929
    },
    {
        "question": " 158分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9759218642082326
    },
    {
        "question": " 602分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.558069825948372
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.53兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.903657154395058
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2972697330010075
    },
    {
        "question": " 890万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3932612014941874
    },
    {
        "question": " 176万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.466802042377317
    },
    {
        "question": " 7345秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.865982480309131
    },
    {
        "question": " 241兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.883650482733686
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.7兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.839130016166263
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.12億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.058699203645651
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.38万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08967458873143541
    },
    {
        "question": " 9707msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9870832592876677
    },
    {
        "question": " 3770msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.576305778953962
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.3兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12794620104658816
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.42兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5974131191643248
    },
    {
        "question": " 877京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.38691504787766
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.2億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8570020020821243
    },
    {
        "question": " 6168億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.790120974130637
    },
    {
        "question": " 482万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6828468059444406
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.2万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.73361371590636
    },
    {
        "question": " 592京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2732775268111336
    },
    {
        "question": " 789京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.960433526337252
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.450431630746908
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.2京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.701576693305386
    },
    {
        "question": " 714京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.853660055727163
    },
    {
        "question": " 19兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.277776191162707
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.148438570010276
    },
    {
        "question": " 1090万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.599533447177654
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.08年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.430399915116782
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.6年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.295785008993553
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7752849224286316
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.695661298612698
    },
    {
        "question": " 4735日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.833659594878202
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.100271784766569
    },
    {
        "question": " 827万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.975112423094024
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.7時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2696451689621526
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1066883021395
    },
    {
        "question": " 301時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0342713207385446
    },
    {
        "question": " 1761億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.525015442247737
    },
    {
        "question": " 2823億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.29234438810533
    },
    {
        "question": " 985分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2152437954533457
    },
    {
        "question": " 2502万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.176454109649674
    },
    {
        "question": " 640億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3076358472268486
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.3億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.98930779553318
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.851092665033978
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5555245971051654
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.95兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.098061558187344
    },
    {
        "question": " 8645億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.000268455633007
    },
    {
        "question": " 4630兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.109251416801408
    },
    {
        "question": " 341億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.754824178699822
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.5億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.941918772393253
    },
    {
        "question": " 115msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.059760371153377
    },
    {
        "question": " 513京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.211563743686691
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.218716429197997
    },
    {
        "question": " 3904億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0351887582378705
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.282314919488831
    },
    {
        "question": " 190億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.278802309819531
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.086959522955122
    },
    {
        "question": " 1604usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.205156039814156
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.915e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.273165621279798
    },
    {
        "question": " 3600京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.619777544292707
    },
    {
        "question": " 616兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2331883080850745
    },
    {
        "question": " 147京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.387934910033915
    },
    {
        "question": " 808億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9076301522012873
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.1825179981431937
    },
    {
        "question": " 301万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.4784158867579142
    },
    {
        "question": " 427年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.192808313270236
    },
    {
        "question": " 2145年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.273958284898839
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.901693561215737
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.587016640848571
    },
    {
        "question": " 262日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.798199603943341
    },
    {
        "question": " 8145万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9684148727175437
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7835141654979845
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.1時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5345396273698935
    },
    {
        "question": " 1514時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7363558508922985
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4575339015009323
    },
    {
        "question": " 383万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.424902206907566
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2542256345163714
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.87京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.188325013562647
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2998571610632328
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.84億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0279926383738225
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.99億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.82304486133677
    },
    {
        "question": " 4584億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1624241267383262
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.34417873203934746
    },
    {
        "question": " 2626万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8629172724720946
    },
    {
        "question": " 2222万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.568529199201728
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3108953333648365
    },
    {
        "question": " 872兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.441892205529025
    },
    {
        "question": " 1748京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.305959792079404
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.3億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3536521779394408
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.77億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2117685748386076
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1256821128938705
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.36万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.9223968342568043
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.062e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.527358385046528
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.3京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9285199805198956
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.23京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.408951514473629
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.3兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2099110189188194
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.196226519574019
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.266198330144174
    },
    {
        "question": " 159万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.2013111242253123
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.139159865459984
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.4年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.281752061613318
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.6万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.096273570764525
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.488842319649551
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.290016347046759
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2559545535697294
    },
    {
        "question": " 834億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.541154152050149
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.4時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4354479310175154
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.1億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1304658451980796
    },
    {
        "question": " 64億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.647706264331453
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.4万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5725720767045557
    },
    {
        "question": " 244万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.164908980722355
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.882321157198659
    },
    {
        "question": " 265兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.924791789172216
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.6億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.602678644247765
    },
    {
        "question": " 4082億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.05454614884244
    },
    {
        "question": " 1467万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.388318266742375
    },
    {
        "question": " 118秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.071088465110744
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.059582482021558
    },
    {
        "question": " 4697京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.172984095875558
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.1京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.988495175262994
    },
    {
        "question": " 258億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8552943811670817
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.2万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.768247816769515
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.074828150980416
    },
    {
        "question": " 2694msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.430476787101895
    },
    {
        "question": " 505msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.703696764351267
    },
    {
        "question": " 207垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.816223841872388
    },
    {
        "question": " 641京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.870648170726005
    },
    {
        "question": " 893京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.394716001416729
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.87兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.216029984436096
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.9兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.428964018911871
    },
    {
        "question": " 2571万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.410119693075987
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.7usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.704716713034827
    },
    {
        "question": " 214京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8310721222909776
    },
    {
        "question": " 1106兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1071511526011535
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.1兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9896051055741739
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.439772910310396
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.3京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.48113905148713
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.418119050749073
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.9億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.7476483644012255
    },
    {
        "question": " 248年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.956961780626779
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.88年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.558362085398861
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.5年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.409915474972145
    },
    {
        "question": " 147億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.605554986062759
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.7日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9323936431810163
    },
    {
        "question": " 6940日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.777831970869055
    },
    {
        "question": " 132万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1794307268197133
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.36万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.486543327339997
    },
    {
        "question": " 100万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.778041063483325
    },
    {
        "question": " 183万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.819853748367793
    },
    {
        "question": " 2170億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.61571203779455
    },
    {
        "question": " 6735万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.669998504771971
    },
    {
        "question": " 5372分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.951956080846572
    },
    {
        "question": " 614万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.566432657654087
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.05分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.626063993036085
    },
    {
        "question": " 588兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.270467443299568
    },
    {
        "question": " 729万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9259637267414875
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.503214423095501
    },
    {
        "question": " 297万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.694545256556527
    },
    {
        "question": " 2975秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.473479422777291
    },
    {
        "question": " 121秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.084068838418043
    },
    {
        "question": " 1306京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.617050576892373
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.9京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.818505680736836
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.49億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3180276125166657
    },
    {
        "question": " 3153万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7205680088005932
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.6億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.390382352243251
    },
    {
        "question": " 337msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.527928663516024
    },
    {
        "question": " 3208兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.007499230181826
    },
    {
        "question": " 2227億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.41117551820654574
    },
    {
        "question": " 68兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2759268377601245
    },
    {
        "question": " 5833兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.987766517566618
    },
    {
        "question": " 144兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.158519119835198
    },
    {
        "question": " 434万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6373394562290864
    },
    {
        "question": " 7559usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.878473213844195
    },
    {
        "question": " 9442垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.476271480762772
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.56京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.614515054703598
    },
    {
        "question": " 2216兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.789223857698353
    },
    {
        "question": " 1013億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22743557492719169
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.31兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.519777371888859
    },
    {
        "question": " 11兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.039543688055991
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.202530395367269
    },
    {
        "question": " 254年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.967279555036212
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.546786874526282
    },
    {
        "question": " 1025日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.391035806087351
    },
    {
        "question": " 124日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.252987677730513
    },
    {
        "question": " 1379日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.075924664012051
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.18日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.55804057488902
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.73万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8157904463724663
    },
    {
        "question": " 5048万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3229306404546985
    },
    {
        "question": " 1421時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.930823032046193
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8147242008906
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6752995536808335
    },
    {
        "question": " 301万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3204659816472226
    },
    {
        "question": " 2716億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.655849514600638
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.863638234902565
    },
    {
        "question": " 483兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.185381884763478
    },
    {
        "question": " 965億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.048139139283463
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.32万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3084904884274562
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.348840328614392
    },
    {
        "question": " 7434秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.871199075948496
    },
    {
        "question": " 440兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.144630481497517
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.4兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.546645575897596
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.7億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.875200651736807
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.4億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.110676943787641
    },
    {
        "question": " 7187msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.856561034326282
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.3万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.683782562762193
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.78京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.263024630260859
    },
    {
        "question": " 1943京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.352010559730413
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6694846931930694
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.89億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6829063060703955
    },
    {
        "question": " 380万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5792351488525049
    },
    {
        "question": " 538万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.730561949772132
    },
    {
        "question": " 244usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.386719016091835
    },
    {
        "question": " 1195京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5786220444483368
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.3垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3250027698816425
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.9京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.552986197710862
    },
    {
        "question": " 928億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18942730982782097
    },
    {
        "question": " 1145兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0589685243085025
    },
    {
        "question": " 4641万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6665895237264239
    },
    {
        "question": " 1032万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.013817602025607
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.58万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.441764586180554
    },
    {
        "question": " 2169年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.056845720669912
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.71899710966137
    },
    {
        "question": " 5875億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.20672934184223
    },
    {
        "question": " 621万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.173582844159355
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.74日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.730701146812778
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.1日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.217572443488473
    },
    {
        "question": " 7844万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.952011303883655
    },
    {
        "question": " 134億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.748177954742236
    },
    {
        "question": " 470時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.228735618106488
    },
    {
        "question": " 227時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.912662406508833
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.7兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.847921252519286
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.2万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.188753993407416
    },
    {
        "question": " 1186万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.295956444261279
    },
    {
        "question": " 222万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.12496280936185
    },
    {
        "question": " 146分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.943547494604584
    },
    {
        "question": " 366兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.065107303790633
    },
    {
        "question": " 11万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10354657939778411
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.26兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.360686143517112
    },
    {
        "question": " 356億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.773093482675307
    },
    {
        "question": " 473兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.176170539432055
    },
    {
        "question": " 447億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7142826422880475
    },
    {
        "question": " 7666兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.3282716841792
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7435938661138974
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.52兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.741635463422357
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.360499786648694
    },
    {
        "question": " 311msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.492834393627259
    },
    {
        "question": " 545垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.237976015984987
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.4兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5470404217412144
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.2京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.951155967591883
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.2億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0223195050528977
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.98億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9020034573740974
    },
    {
        "question": " 1382万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.140391747174981
    },
    {
        "question": " 889usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.9488337312564274
    },
    {
        "question": " 1124垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.55196052810703
    },
    {
        "question": " 1796垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.317874860217643
    },
    {
        "question": " 153垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.629245610552548
    },
    {
        "question": " 1560兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.414880764048876
    },
    {
        "question": " 8414億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9250054592601615
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.056054679561164
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.1億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.2814030275394215
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7362692416694996
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.67万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.696332614064174
    },
    {
        "question": " 106年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.745327064570593
    },
    {
        "question": " 603億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.2183323772767
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.83日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.326094585972005
    },
    {
        "question": " 4016日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.762177907543181
    },
    {
        "question": " 398日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.536376061054705
    },
    {
        "question": " 6746億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8865653342539135
    },
    {
        "question": " 817万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.53197334004289
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.32万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.503989698013955
    },
    {
        "question": " 1026時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.567533862580452
    },
    {
        "question": " 137兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.417386838386829
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.9億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.463539259697283
    },
    {
        "question": " 1850万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.489043051651922
    },
    {
        "question": " 545万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.514859676488896
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.880446667041223
    },
    {
        "question": " 5533億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.244135254833182
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.78兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.641177328447143
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.732465454456351
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.24490734910127
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.78秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.5779288244412055
    },
    {
        "question": " 144兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.658306965874819
    },
    {
        "question": " 2291億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.423503591112549
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.455192230404165
    },
    {
        "question": " 381万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8029224910862285
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.4億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5319464820101985
    },
    {
        "question": " 5628msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.7503777322941
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.3msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.261389960812555
    },
    {
        "question": " 2197垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.842970613610591
    },
    {
        "question": " 2390兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.441872807457829
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.09兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.29405979263926
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.55京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.153919586412947
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.4億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.561509115780186
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.3381491542194468
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.180841583664777
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.09垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.286137266400417
    },
    {
        "question": " 372京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6343506445273075
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.2垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.951898529215716
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.8京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.632880894764669
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.333328774230553
    },
    {
        "question": " 945億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.975231179292916
    },
    {
        "question": " 7212nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.8580612485994721
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.92059034923138
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.816695415765896
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.713322754056463
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.5億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.023496463961636
    },
    {
        "question": " 67日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.984427352581125
    },
    {
        "question": " 9202時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.021392228104780697
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.98万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.618745310310374
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.25万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.638675998281753
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.07万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.261290493416706
    },
    {
        "question": " 430万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9123770372260165
    },
    {
        "question": " 1835分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10530157556583264
    },
    {
        "question": " 268万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6494127355476245
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.4万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.302498815679125
    },
    {
        "question": " 115兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.560690386357383
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.92兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.059998953674302
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.7億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.205229641780709
    },
    {
        "question": " 2794億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.668153996441731
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.24秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7950340596923358
    },
    {
        "question": " 970秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.986885127985813
    },
    {
        "question": " 5022京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.202082183094099
    },
    {
        "question": " 214億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3939830831617046
    },
    {
        "question": " 361万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0013156475799869227
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.55兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.772537045145985
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.62億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.749756698996159
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.9万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.838515387724001
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.035941787384909
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.36垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.140644477359686
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.114086162918877
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.25京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.360324445326075
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.4億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.050776339351269
    },
    {
        "question": " 833万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9206174197693495
    },
    {
        "question": " 2671万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.426754335428194
    },
    {
        "question": " 381万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.580429696363812
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.7垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.170945734538627
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.339131333490159
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.3垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.791316116382779
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.94兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.81749746535264
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.29京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6327410213363445
    },
    {
        "question": " 9711万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.9872852634337346
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.28万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.722651133552231
    },
    {
        "question": " 135年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.850535724414314
    },
    {
        "question": " 6750万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.26702377664232
    },
    {
        "question": " 6034日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.938948630804455
    },
    {
        "question": " 2702万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4892588477189412
    },
    {
        "question": " 194時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9079665397169367
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.8万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.524934555544473
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.7兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.062886098049454
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9611725930478499
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.423522680592999
    },
    {
        "question": " 788分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.674418600933468
    },
    {
        "question": " 271分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.210671778652848
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.68分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.663229563559966
    },
    {
        "question": " 3992兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.10236138182033
    },
    {
        "question": " 662万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8841719856582873
    },
    {
        "question": " 4521億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.098931707937206
    },
    {
        "question": " 130万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.336971844873723
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.6万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.98519728637361
    },
    {
        "question": " 1382億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6417137944029716
    },
    {
        "question": " 8048兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.96917593182661
    },
    {
        "question": " 210兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.766802847588407
    },
    {
        "question": " 1705億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.453537912292183
    },
    {
        "question": " 8691万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.939064895643757
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.75万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.942219040684297
    },
    {
        "question": " 1368垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.637398629896165
    },
    {
        "question": " 2130京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.391857264467507
    },
    {
        "question": " 27京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.875229778641466
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.480554745238088
    },
    {
        "question": " 29兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.461731106279954
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.1534255760298
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.5万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.406822134472607
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9215961358235054
    },
    {
        "question": " 678京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.894915396816712
    },
    {
        "question": " 4516京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.098425964844951
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.480361956830407
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.68京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.565420542660411
    },
    {
        "question": " 212億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.327197980407542
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.6億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.629394398953106
    },
    {
        "question": " 147年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.111234335419113
    },
    {
        "question": " 404億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.043995523654203
    },
    {
        "question": " 783日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.273773415727984
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.5兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.96883833058174
    },
    {
        "question": " 36億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.17570335055387
    },
    {
        "question": " 1433万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.934475339302296
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.777730457738934
    },
    {
        "question": " 4148万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8972317509330239
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.02448315115638
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.1億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.813824014763359
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.9分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.509721136173267
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.831451048990564
    },
    {
        "question": " 1396億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.646138413514862
    },
    {
        "question": " 8143万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.974286765589321
    },
    {
        "question": " 481億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.125844184423487
    },
    {
        "question": " 1232秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3123518308032633
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.1秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.741257110085997
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.6兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9420921693528124
    },
    {
        "question": " 449兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7153422843562005
    },
    {
        "question": " 953億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.422617732757173
    },
    {
        "question": " 5254万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.942308832766982
    },
    {
        "question": " 4823msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6832965544548775
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.102845069890456
    },
    {
        "question": " 5631msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.750581887168691
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.8垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.338792245976203
    },
    {
        "question": " 182京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3233622529826015
    },
    {
        "question": " 1702兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.674756164000161
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.23京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.730882108799797
    },
    {
        "question": " 213兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.328333644651106
    },
    {
        "question": " 2727億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.435682906593481
    },
    {
        "question": " 565万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.752056601729313
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.05京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.40688425600326705
    },
    {
        "question": " 117垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.130810910885414
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.463841560904566
    },
    {
        "question": " 309京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.711880166474781
    },
    {
        "question": " 118兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0732612609151495
    },
    {
        "question": " 403兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.605485644341849
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.21705189603318
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.8万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.064650110886546
    },
    {
        "question": " 3268日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.952012720363351
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.615247044413514
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.85日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.10540139651511
    },
    {
        "question": " 3394日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.467187285793006
    },
    {
        "question": " 1718万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.292603012543005
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.5万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.088890019180519
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.69億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7091783394529703
    },
    {
        "question": " 119億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.916913768130776
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.64億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.043748930592645
    },
    {
        "question": " 4046万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.385125058367835
    },
    {
        "question": " 1249分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.874792470425236
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.93分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.677369536554883
    },
    {
        "question": " 60兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.279282800201434
    },
    {
        "question": " 5675億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.817490059364574
    },
    {
        "question": " 21億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.765378340149985
    },
    {
        "question": " 2631万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.641951941556897
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.02秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.604343594709597
    },
    {
        "question": " 33兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.019284064597728
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2904857061045951
    },
    {
        "question": " 383億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.026622620002261
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.91兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.993130700206371
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1138374453595046
    },
    {
        "question": " 9048msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.956570402866879
    },
    {
        "question": " 2008msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.302786203403972
    },
    {
        "question": " 263垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.92049118872981
    },
    {
        "question": " 326兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.576530612432393
    },
    {
        "question": " 654兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.259334268478504
    },
    {
        "question": " 6506億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.035176921621083
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.28億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3588138147482987
    },
    {
        "question": " 123億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.089898623390326
    },
    {
        "question": " 2549京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9074973834129123
    },
    {
        "question": " 25垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.462296636602125
    },
    {
        "question": " 1005兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4457626725795913
    },
    {
        "question": " 1414兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.37235073522786
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2027505921715385
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.7兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.9276320608959425
    },
    {
        "question": " 1688nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.22746887518252823
    },
    {
        "question": " 687年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.779731196435074
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.9年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.332275703740043
    },
    {
        "question": " 2113日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7625987935087875
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3902345533917093
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.063762269809773
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.305612700311183
    },
    {
        "question": " 121万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.703476091849303
    },
    {
        "question": " 1597万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.981345308605702
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.56361074120033
    },
    {
        "question": " 5169万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9927880720204505
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.99兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.744334476796816
    },
    {
        "question": " 3703億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.790385738307437
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.21分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.402549385121958
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.5分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.340422095802704
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5592710718101401
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.308481516471534
    },
    {
        "question": " 5903万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.214755210996399
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.1億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8359791959408565
    },
    {
        "question": " 163秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.2115074937087424
    },
    {
        "question": " 3759秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.575063377182094
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.769244030318882
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.27117845325409
    },
    {
        "question": " 123兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.532128615694797
    },
    {
        "question": " 5196万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.937518065201056
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.23億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.915157014800356
    },
    {
        "question": " 14msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.1452591391683935
    },
    {
        "question": " 579京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.263847987520899
    },
    {
        "question": " 2632京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.483743531932566
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.668137950594144
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.5兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.619248032674667
    },
    {
        "question": " 5753兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.759923017864761
    },
    {
        "question": " 4433万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.6467210168231
    },
    {
        "question": " 392京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0946009510808716
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.47京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8741511098698123
    },
    {
        "question": " 17垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.674001932053134
    },
    {
        "question": " 245兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6111719293154865
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.55兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6583159240535403
    },
    {
        "question": " 529兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.723498410769327
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.035060506103191
    },
    {
        "question": " 684年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.397086602418689
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.695156164860537
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.9万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.870454369579983
    },
    {
        "question": " 229億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4172755207703025
    },
    {
        "question": " 143時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7748467851528729
    },
    {
        "question": " 805万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1853939517314194
    },
    {
        "question": " 566万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.594794340988731
    },
    {
        "question": " 273億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.658412220117537
    },
    {
        "question": " 625億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.29740688595583
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.6兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.692552067268768
    },
    {
        "question": " 7435万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.314960557623699
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.718799654573812
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.93万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.692611176917481
    },
    {
        "question": " 328秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.516047106981684
    },
    {
        "question": " 1091億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5389396799130475
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.332725607165295
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.41京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.825918285004862
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.3万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0364501534489357
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.190328757509189
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.2万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.827486845483111
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3295148665717855
    },
    {
        "question": " 2922京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.529142072301015
    },
    {
        "question": " 348億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9851373029751243
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.293549230970644
    },
    {
        "question": " 3025億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.480672131294297
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.94億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.594949333910532
    },
    {
        "question": " 130京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6156624252480412
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.78垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.825600066499352
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.66京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.00707080499341
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4569968268694966
    },
    {
        "question": " 102京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.008993512742764
    },
    {
        "question": " 61兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.785090466489217
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.14808693062101
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6623991028055363
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.315876018273899
    },
    {
        "question": " 2361万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.810780077077822
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.6万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.066582129956581
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.24日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0183662240416815
    },
    {
        "question": " 180日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.192821935708102
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.32兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.422683726830813
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.3億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.427689416001204
    },
    {
        "question": " 578万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.539965126147589
    },
    {
        "question": " 111時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.60223646127373
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.4億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7628895779300686
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.3万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.203416711780636
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2740132052864466
    },
    {
        "question": " 401万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.381667808578936
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.9億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.821137671513522
    },
    {
        "question": " 9571億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.04447840055474
    },
    {
        "question": " 248億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.837691066614745
    },
    {
        "question": " 345万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.759928541222661
    },
    {
        "question": " 7225秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.858846055451289
    },
    {
        "question": " 8332秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.920760913188428
    },
    {
        "question": " 817億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.41346726904253117
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.317402872911393
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.94億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7308993922626148
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.9万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1803375945936245
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.39兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.529967403282665
    },
    {
        "question": " 148msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.169361863238829
    },
    {
        "question": " 6209京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.294199673303019
    },
    {
        "question": " 2194億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4046860057578572
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.9京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.392484981320798
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.2京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.768055649493933
    },
    {
        "question": " 2661兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.425080401971716
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.8億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.9626850585341495
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.77万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.5760759751894895
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.538555903646149
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.49垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.802727236849231
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.66垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.38112590977898
    },
    {
        "question": " 9154兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1834645645899835
    },
    {
        "question": " 333兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.522919734348285
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.3兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.815046483950781
    },
    {
        "question": " 3160nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.4996549217772972
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.87万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.530433077909038
    },
    {
        "question": " 8829万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3836155266661665
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.776630625389743
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.02日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.762838799215915
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.69日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.761653933039726
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.491973354000658
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.9時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4184148102847385
    },
    {
        "question": " 260時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.192336394376107
    },
    {
        "question": " 5323時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.282454393915254
    },
    {
        "question": " 869億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.218144353717169
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.16億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.461007729394547
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2918601129579517
    },
    {
        "question": " 266万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.203271984711783
    },
    {
        "question": " 2789億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9465717340472253
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.9億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0409013411869585
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.985988420900995
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.6億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.215565113624702
    },
    {
        "question": " 414秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.617064621157052
    },
    {
        "question": " 9626京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.484662860058386
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.5京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.990408388607193
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.36億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.08315466963483
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.3万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8273893790246123
    },
    {
        "question": " 161億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.207775885439057
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.45垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.476612086181969
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.06京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.845780157146843
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.11京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.057456272386169
    },
    {
        "question": " 981兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.21332416451908
    },
    {
        "question": " 113万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0540892398166859
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.0545530902629274
    },
    {
        "question": " 1367usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.135770611252102
    },
    {
        "question": " 1081垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.535151913959707
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4999742197426333
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.5垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.028964346836977
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.35兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1433901685811763
    },
    {
        "question": " 50兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.698661285901427
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.7億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.640398855006526
    },
    {
        "question": " 484万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.684580063445363
    },
    {
        "question": " 636万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.365786670433984
    },
    {
        "question": " 277年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.163805009668327
    },
    {
        "question": " 219億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.779087538847684
    },
    {
        "question": " 3億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.858031657438572
    },
    {
        "question": " 2263億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.412171034487926
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.087886343096054
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8962727422353165
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.634380387184851
    },
    {
        "question": " 3915億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.872079765533474
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.27億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.356768853696103
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.491724073413498
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9234228519143015
    },
    {
        "question": " 396分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.376078174510864
    },
    {
        "question": " 1310兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.618349303455087
    },
    {
        "question": " 426億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.693099069254206
    },
    {
        "question": " 7044秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2914902240933748
    },
    {
        "question": " 963秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2054343746859064
    },
    {
        "question": " 437兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.142044391878406
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.56京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.615493700236652
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.11京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.936997113523937
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.6万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7069337908275819
    },
    {
        "question": " 109億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.036282991512755
    },
    {
        "question": " 647京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.311966059295267
    },
    {
        "question": " 162兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.272304170470768
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.7京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.148984901100983
    },
    {
        "question": " 125兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.319451961742027
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1141067192914322
    },
    {
        "question": " 309億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.489833889678003
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.3usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.9879943452059985
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6686410922744415
    },
    {
        "question": " 420京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.686963521168228
    },
    {
        "question": " 3455兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.982171162770996
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.44兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9573836965925684
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.7兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.901696712023193
    },
    {
        "question": " 7033万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.8471500829130172
    },
    {
        "question": " 3407万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.532414868806369
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.11万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.85140552077848
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.66年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.544081665455121
    },
    {
        "question": " 37億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0054366581325835
    },
    {
        "question": " 6340日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.182274013318566
    },
    {
        "question": " 110日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.199696915093489
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.232265446362346
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.308801385451069
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7417946835942155
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.4万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.600378922914757
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.7万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.851531252515901
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.1兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.24820797142565
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.88961472554578
    },
    {
        "question": " 190億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.500814816640856
    },
    {
        "question": " 791万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.67654039252502
    },
    {
        "question": " 2584分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.190453958697995
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.794948803746648
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.2兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.399761938303728
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.8兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.888266796502359
    },
    {
        "question": " 354万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.99284146051657
    },
    {
        "question": " 3513秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7675025606595451
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.3秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.605076295957109
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.43秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.646539701921256
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.78京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.332394551894444
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.122048544332769
    },
    {
        "question": " 1256億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.542723192696348
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.3億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.858272989601052
    },
    {
        "question": " 8965億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.952569623551272
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.89msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.589391932984771
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7477496864486675
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.340532467610295
    },
    {
        "question": " 7988億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.346115457832074
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.227491264304534
    },
    {
        "question": " 8870億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.947947983221415
    },
    {
        "question": " 703億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.847086706781647
    },
    {
        "question": " 6408垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.307903451113167
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.91垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.835140200523425
    },
    {
        "question": " 556京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.188750434717072
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.270646898561596
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.103060538829606
    },
    {
        "question": " 3627億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.559506078896544
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.77兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.890242061671263
    },
    {
        "question": " 29万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.024819612827054
    },
    {
        "question": " 159年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.921207057402953
    },
    {
        "question": " 228万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7956339550204765
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.068911903444878
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.4億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.74229994535345
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.23億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.129547304747915
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.9時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.712226132557619
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.346899713498669
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.33万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5687329790643845
    },
    {
        "question": " 106分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24914228361221813
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.9分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.22420516314255
    },
    {
        "question": " 101分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.781566821042833
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6223398823566184
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18173565430008254
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.09兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.150828768805903
    },
    {
        "question": " 1131億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.275488338500141
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.238270193501914
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.97秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.998686814247183
    },
    {
        "question": " 2725兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.936534527481809
    },
    {
        "question": " 1987億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.361588616890272
    },
    {
        "question": " 373万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.015623157835926715
    },
    {
        "question": " 162兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.430831672364468
    },
    {
        "question": " 145億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.160813298141971
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.4万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.931516877280487
    },
    {
        "question": " 573垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.259622315862977
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2788111853828044
    },
    {
        "question": " 134兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.572054497148935
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.25京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.850370613366872
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.03億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9044664256124673
    },
    {
        "question": " 690万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.8386950873780346
    },
    {
        "question": " 998万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.999275159661634
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.112e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9942411742000985
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.256135068635382
    },
    {
        "question": " 8025兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3481606550620526
    },
    {
        "question": " 363兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7819498218543
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.016216585684391
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.25兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.720151510694452
    },
    {
        "question": " 1118万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.048401606999812
    },
    {
        "question": " 610年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.505664239278993
    },
    {
        "question": " 26億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.852279996589862
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.6日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0840382853881088
    },
    {
        "question": " 110日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.197895263297091
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.06日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.640473193897276
    },
    {
        "question": " 6150万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8463448661206723
    },
    {
        "question": " 360億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.175946585763093
    },
    {
        "question": " 431時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.412415269074758
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.32万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.42071631117683
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.778151785560529
    },
    {
        "question": " 7684億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.164928467386362
    },
    {
        "question": " 3979億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.44142668393142
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.362202251801385
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9127296492813706
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.6兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.390790635741416
    },
    {
        "question": " 820万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.977355384734678
    },
    {
        "question": " 27兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.875016097377124
    },
    {
        "question": " 1566億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.416560666449632
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.194535076671146
    },
    {
        "question": " 4126億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1167527428254354
    },
    {
        "question": " 5719兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8208298808729655
    },
    {
        "question": " 8280万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3617323157494365
    },
    {
        "question": " 7347億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.087960818950766
    },
    {
        "question": " 2260万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.354024215815645
    },
    {
        "question": " 167兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7230716563053041
    },
    {
        "question": " 1665兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.284853143733741
    },
    {
        "question": " 140億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.588401096155029
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.6兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.133456263733853
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.2兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.326714446033692
    },
    {
        "question": " 1241万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.093795524724154
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.74垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.073535109122446
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.47京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.603473484244454
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.1垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.185185735514048
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.369775235655101
    },
    {
        "question": " 539億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.73162353191741
    },
    {
        "question": " 1648万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.2170593431577559
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.38億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.641146283926534
    },
    {
        "question": " 698年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.406006002197767
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.117908639240946
    },
    {
        "question": " 217億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.774699167759305
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.393214769765821
    },
    {
        "question": " 140日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3056144037002815
    },
    {
        "question": " 9782日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.926948152747862
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.79万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5026186021274548
    },
    {
        "question": " 6105時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.40548989178477
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1060324598964444
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.76時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.446312322002834
    },
    {
        "question": " 5161億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.992075603925546
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.75兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.670835386161352
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.41588023496481
    },
    {
        "question": " 8952分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.730061331446345
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.04分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.734480798339604
    },
    {
        "question": " 8788億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.445088646787379
    },
    {
        "question": " 26万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47926408371033014
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.92億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7280861768464195
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.9億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.600146937471304
    },
    {
        "question": " 1141秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.057225433119062
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.41秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.382693916615032
    },
    {
        "question": " 3531京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.049088624133976
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.191715208722249
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.43億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1785205642969894
    },
    {
        "question": " 6227万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.016154406242028
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2087146040714725
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.4万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.497175266843104
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.7京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8577089163005085
    },
    {
        "question": " 3466億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6033274064460115
    },
    {
        "question": " 250兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.841400416469785
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.595588190414006
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.217535635431572
    },
    {
        "question": " 493万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.692949786094836
    },
    {
        "question": " 5468京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.239013305903522
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.126063693869829
    },
    {
        "question": " 56垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.1921231380929
    },
    {
        "question": " 8155兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.133265243518257
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.5京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.31143677983168
    },
    {
        "question": " 287兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.458275537184486
    },
    {
        "question": " 1396nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.14474424990969625
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.4万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.294962429713632
    },
    {
        "question": " 2062日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.751890127597965
    },
    {
        "question": " 666日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2037496131684415
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.81兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.638954048119915
    },
    {
        "question": " 194万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9069144384585925
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8851530625043784
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.719617144602902
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.6億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.788969792845312
    },
    {
        "question": " 6877分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0592333960424245
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.189154100884338
    },
    {
        "question": " 235億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8719244193273816
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.18兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.976050140580792
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.512096618714484
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.35万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7471677222860382
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.6兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.205471012653245
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.180358943186608
    },
    {
        "question": " 609億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.228487019777562
    },
    {
        "question": " 329兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.738887338581089
    },
    {
        "question": " 706億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.848582668102435
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.3msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.920769894353491
    },
    {
        "question": " 2309京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.864536002592336
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.49垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.875585636258483
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.670429216591441
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.9億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2215652597162405
    },
    {
        "question": " 539億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.731926209108172
    },
    {
        "question": " 756億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.87856035731735
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.59362308052679
    },
    {
        "question": " 5644兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8151173745470128
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.678385714943282
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.488214107445096
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.3億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3847308632190627
    },
    {
        "question": " 466兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.66811384254721
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.335519979473876
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.27万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.076804129249963
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.25年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5709218883194955
    },
    {
        "question": " 6895日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2762114940605396
    },
    {
        "question": " 3759日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.955321709338501
    },
    {
        "question": " 944万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0323921932904585
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.927114999909358
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.78時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4578518492764734
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7201794630531495
    },
    {
        "question": " 1907兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.55962822691987
    },
    {
        "question": " 2273分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19827550949638506
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.53億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.625065904519742
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.2万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.082722427367525
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.84401635780361
    },
    {
        "question": " 4648億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.168463350363426
    },
    {
        "question": " 645兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.872894465851058
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.79兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.888959208046021
    },
    {
        "question": " 2044億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.532414301411661
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.345290406206191
    },
    {
        "question": " 9278秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.967462044048636
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.009279761326658
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.33京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.366262323186358
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.55億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4700055681678905
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.633724994089861
    },
    {
        "question": " 1132万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.27570332265873
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.89万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5905022433004157
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.8990323998180845
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.1msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.9872124254144765
    },
    {
        "question": " 5325兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.227510165981632
    },
    {
        "question": " 5742兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8225472731947665
    },
    {
        "question": " 319京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.947193350951927
    },
    {
        "question": " 4476兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.872763480605068
    },
    {
        "question": " 701億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.845752745986804
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.2億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.963697637754549
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.75307429061189
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.431904903625951
    },
    {
        "question": " 5214兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1608512256362764
    },
    {
        "question": " 5623京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.971821003106006
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.8兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.393979651155625
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.17億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.790421728522625
    },
    {
        "question": " 1019万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.008345766054923
    },
    {
        "question": " 2426万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.947184564285127
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.380263595413795
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.790628144822858
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5041085947909172
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8153128358170925
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.41億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8644726711864035
    },
    {
        "question": " 1191時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6956797362053821
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.112530811743931
    },
    {
        "question": " 629時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.355033816940683
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.90093394830016
    },
    {
        "question": " 124万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3728602893138655
    },
    {
        "question": " 111万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.888030459922708
    },
    {
        "question": " 380億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.801758890923336
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.3万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.164524582478156
    },
    {
        "question": " 240兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.880595585536126
    },
    {
        "question": " 103兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.076916139715461
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.4億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.309264398853203
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.5億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.573642857845916
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.37544273505155
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.565626875246917
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4365369536601358
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.4兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.249933185210427
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.323951971086929
    },
    {
        "question": " 395万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.596869034519301
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.87万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.687456467736043
    },
    {
        "question": " 68msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.83281212023541
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.42京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2353202940653745
    },
    {
        "question": " 660京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8830293620937475
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.4億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.25238890642021894
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.1億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.114634974624352
    },
    {
        "question": " 335兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.524801127362402
    },
    {
        "question": " 270万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.4307301087289943
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.88万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.273572691953271
    },
    {
        "question": " 2793京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.947233485275685
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.11京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.38838949779978
    },
    {
        "question": " 3207兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.949747155546701
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.2兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.200601310187823
    },
    {
        "question": " 519億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7152596949189847
    },
    {
        "question": " 518兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.714559257837122
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.4億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.309011957418077
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.107293033846258
    },
    {
        "question": " 277億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.880090717556873
    },
    {
        "question": " 168万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.60568694763365
    },
    {
        "question": " 1883日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.433123211021156
    },
    {
        "question": " 587日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.70503178661624
    },
    {
        "question": " 291万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.521498492886037
    },
    {
        "question": " 1923時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.903859120763578
    },
    {
        "question": " 194万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.843157980377041
    },
    {
        "question": " 3079億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.767702022387832
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.9億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.301869500167676
    },
    {
        "question": " 7299分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0850891668536
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.9分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4929064835437442
    },
    {
        "question": " 440兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.144532915727522
    },
    {
        "question": " 664億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.885733909509673
    },
    {
        "question": " 9032億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.399505515279328
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.43億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.956669973969585
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.82秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6827208761161643
    },
    {
        "question": " 8758京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.44359898061673
    },
    {
        "question": " 123兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.153951283107844
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5604483224405374
    },
    {
        "question": " 196兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.514703647245328
    },
    {
        "question": " 4545msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6575774373266086
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.148443160321355
    },
    {
        "question": " 4340兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.138737177389615
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.5兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.886551381421615
    },
    {
        "question": " 162億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6534516762311127
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.38514934434528
    },
    {
        "question": " 476万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6776868297945049
    },
    {
        "question": " 417万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6205973228725186
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.388219106168908
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.16垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.290437471165757
    },
    {
        "question": " 822兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9782285227807974
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.8京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8882892517836565
    },
    {
        "question": " 3554京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.772624785622174
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.043599439235123
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.3億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.3616529633591474
    },
    {
        "question": " 75億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.8749261531563715
    },
    {
        "question": " 509万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.269158244029605
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.962253682926178
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.32億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.163819122954902
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.6日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0668389042764046
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.607656160579059
    },
    {
        "question": " 966億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.042411499120169
    },
    {
        "question": " 270時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0505708201963704
    },
    {
        "question": " 7138万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.631754638576675
    },
    {
        "question": " 126時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.65648172171349
    },
    {
        "question": " 3775億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8562175349614245
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.213724292827778
    },
    {
        "question": " 5692万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.977086079476065
    },
    {
        "question": " 9297分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.746482827318319
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.515791226472966
    },
    {
        "question": " 125万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.160426469396152
    },
    {
        "question": " 152億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.62516517162167
    },
    {
        "question": " 1040万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.238695563874255
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.0173463244441323
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.08秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.3189967908751505
    },
    {
        "question": " 991京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.497182987296632
    },
    {
        "question": " 5061兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.767699598636419
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.704200202273196
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.305110871633834
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.177931337635105
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.572774265099883
    },
    {
        "question": " 3758京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.638445125186939
    },
    {
        "question": " 3629兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.003493846347804
    },
    {
        "question": " 4551兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.879955924212723
    },
    {
        "question": " 548億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7384246103426255
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.2万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.4658257319438857
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.8万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.600197976089163
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.84京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3361280101965203
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.64垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6248554668067055
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.56417507081797
    },
    {
        "question": " 4025億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8265911758479283
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.73京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.888127032839347
    },
    {
        "question": " 8924億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.950542282398327
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.0756385390381
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.75万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.011649298199808
    },
    {
        "question": " 574万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.917507703782606
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.93万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.40406609771459
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.24日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.902299776686597
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.5億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5696400862640285
    },
    {
        "question": " 6296万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.418883476511938
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0359686657171405
    },
    {
        "question": " 3287時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.073066061454705
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.77兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.855286818867227
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.99221728719842
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.13億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.182467921091634
    },
    {
        "question": " 265億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9245025608273045
    },
    {
        "question": " 496兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.75919740952792
    },
    {
        "question": " 23億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8049046730629925
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3225261733902025
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.9秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.880061909614915
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.9兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3329040740305063
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.7億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8322226897200167
    },
    {
        "question": " 7014兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.289643662421627
    },
    {
        "question": " 418万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8432558219033157
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.89億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7699458382352375
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.5msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.921733528354876
    },
    {
        "question": " 672京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.328721511357322
    },
    {
        "question": " 756兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9421232474963395
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6156755242150345
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.39兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.752639575335145
    },
    {
        "question": " 1079億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.032975931511862
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.074727114746086
    },
    {
        "question": " 1511usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.179387510801115
    },
    {
        "question": " 1451垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.662741960639721
    },
    {
        "question": " 4182兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6848568254494045
    },
    {
        "question": " 7垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.288956349925426
    },
    {
        "question": " 149京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.395988619366685
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.35兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.525098365993945
    },
    {
        "question": " 2115万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.3253672021779805
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.098569917992343
    },
    {
        "question": " 2010億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.740866303038766
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.615073787366502
    },
    {
        "question": " 6131日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.724064425899389
    },
    {
        "question": " 9507時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03553701345989424
    },
    {
        "question": " 280時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0672413481351084
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.39万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.199196624402537
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.788190730081917
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.387488512104419
    },
    {
        "question": " 136万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.976023204314263
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.51億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.097479186610608
    },
    {
        "question": " 2378分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1543894632780605
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.7分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.353977663924054
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.6兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.916326014878573
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.8万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.40189808127796267
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.9万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.377751160555065
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.3万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9147223576358536
    },
    {
        "question": " 5190秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.715205302708476
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6712916942568343
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.166320490554139
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.5億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8497820610666027
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.97兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.918305456981828
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.85兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.45461481398118
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.436073163348293
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.4兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1950447049921855
    },
    {
        "question": " 1062京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.089492221491318
    },
    {
        "question": " 2597億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.858243780311707
    },
    {
        "question": " 832兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.141942040262565
    },
    {
        "question": " 409兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.611917821897832
    },
    {
        "question": " 458万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.661138020296939
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.291e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.861146545329919
    },
    {
        "question": " 706京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.912256503698279
    },
    {
        "question": " 1250兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.540614712438367
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.4京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.675777202944308
    },
    {
        "question": " 73京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.863254023938882
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.060797370387002
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.4億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.523331856997581
    },
    {
        "question": " 107万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.5931029396698
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.59万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.87664653414898
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.12億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.053060114606144
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.9万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.840552378455838
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2394830508460815
    },
    {
        "question": " 9441億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.03251781843095
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.778232665071055
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.36万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.304018443259118
    },
    {
        "question": " 4109時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.169984864348896
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.341031641984038
    },
    {
        "question": " 9261分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8083096460247374
    },
    {
        "question": " 864分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1584109299443335
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.99分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.680728190602293
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.76分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.219367266675565
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.870058007877557
    },
    {
        "question": " 277億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.506585002280865
    },
    {
        "question": " 7032万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.290774802644611
    },
    {
        "question": " 491億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.912812958538613
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.45秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.975409226234964
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.4京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.012165685467999
    },
    {
        "question": " 987兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.057944505167852
    },
    {
        "question": " 2067兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.75894652743786
    },
    {
        "question": " 464億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.888556722782308
    },
    {
        "question": " 1184msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0734756647981194
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.2万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.32568486687263
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.140554626413273
    },
    {
        "question": " 988京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.495968169068553
    },
    {
        "question": " 1783京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.314534977631032
    },
    {
        "question": " 968億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4295885589108914
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.392239591641793
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.5兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.498523043527174
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.74億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.8886413430333775
    },
    {
        "question": " 1996usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.300214710333824
    },
    {
        "question": " 7570京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3802969209347964
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.78京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0071859482855743
    },
    {
        "question": " 290兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9064008348746808
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.26兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9429052170598438
    },
    {
        "question": " 165億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2177877495176515
    },
    {
        "question": " 218億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.338154191375575
    },
    {
        "question": " 199万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.2984723938199734
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.57万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.971742963203667
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.038758734887945
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.775198385815729
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.8年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.169445544324034
    },
    {
        "question": " 2823万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8883390860873845
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.2万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.097781769523169
    },
    {
        "question": " 2017日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.46300228114968
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.1兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.740067002783952
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.5時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47985625376591345
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.5万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1842100507740945
    },
    {
        "question": " 109万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.594879600170053
    },
    {
        "question": " 9481億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.256197558947838
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.44億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.577456957610641
    },
    {
        "question": " 1142分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2795113174120964
    },
    {
        "question": " 2171万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.11486637431468
    },
    {
        "question": " 109分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.814863784353426
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.526028837648527
    },
    {
        "question": " 493億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.756107223356802
    },
    {
        "question": " 1042億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.461660327400992
    },
    {
        "question": " 4768秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9001413816559498
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.7兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8943821434566477
    },
    {
        "question": " 159億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2652159266592253
    },
    {
        "question": " 328兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.959694499494537
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.06億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.829876202754771
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.67億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.985428360548233
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.53万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.743031981220908
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.7京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.269618461534115
    },
    {
        "question": " 172京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.300028603363858
    },
    {
        "question": " 1746京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.685696075171432
    },
    {
        "question": " 46兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.884509767751861
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0069433024442924
    },
    {
        "question": " 7437億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.871401117325156
    },
    {
        "question": " 328万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.515447095214412
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.746024074931193
    },
    {
        "question": " 1667兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2853977581610188
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.6京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.298633298078471
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.238780387287248
    },
    {
        "question": " 302京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.479879392759736
    },
    {
        "question": " 214億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.329874269724731
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.56万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.81723031565716
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.6年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.307078781414729
    },
    {
        "question": " 811万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3468047052783
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.9万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.293276806174548
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.5日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.64300664338526
    },
    {
        "question": " 883日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8823400825900976
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2721004260304405
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.52万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1660214145378407
    },
    {
        "question": " 185兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.547288494278918
    },
    {
        "question": " 1437億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.99902713115196
    },
    {
        "question": " 2453分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6115204275749273
    },
    {
        "question": " 3295万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.295964685531056
    },
    {
        "question": " 130分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.890543913626983
    },
    {
        "question": " 48兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.182378415468564
    },
    {
        "question": " 1852億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.331202330191477
    },
    {
        "question": " 199億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.742435619313111
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.7秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03297661651849304
    },
    {
        "question": " 216秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.334325247553926
    },
    {
        "question": " 2871秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.458072966637848
    },
    {
        "question": " 478京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.180526288854889
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.462585544242367
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.66億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.381282216083487
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7795436460958873
    },
    {
        "question": " 1583億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.199359545923647
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8714205525573786
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.153265920947898
    },
    {
        "question": " 438京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.085595041988848
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.440698277365401
    },
    {
        "question": " 2143万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3310208122191447
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.7億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.966943578973637
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.6垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.178667667161965
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.5垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.935397681514135
    },
    {
        "question": " 276京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.885268613569426
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.66垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.890652368859406
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.5億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.422924926683399
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.3兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.594164443780036
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.137435697798417
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.44年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9499175142305023
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.059899035743058
    },
    {
        "question": " 2047年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.03181465464087
    },
    {
        "question": " 163億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.650633731368068
    },
    {
        "question": " 189万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.657117664528399
    },
    {
        "question": " 120万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1378868301729206
    },
    {
        "question": " 50億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.319066962770433
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.92万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0622871525814315
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.85時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.141782597090128
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.3兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.797356146306763
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.180567796522253
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.76万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6631056047864843
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.838356731992475
    },
    {
        "question": " 155分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.96761562932562
    },
    {
        "question": " 2669兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.927489904517303
    },
    {
        "question": " 1471万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.231098420030868
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.6億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.869190943852632
    },
    {
        "question": " 152秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.40433251924423597
    },
    {
        "question": " 11秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.03952109606638
    },
    {
        "question": " 7283京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.363517800909213
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.174122640579037
    },
    {
        "question": " 3533億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.991889908291537
    },
    {
        "question": " 26兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.636471204920174
    },
    {
        "question": " 1158msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06374231200218183
    },
    {
        "question": " 153msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.185531968512685
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8177941695548347
    },
    {
        "question": " 2808億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.511919714070822
    },
    {
        "question": " 569兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.198718403563348
    },
    {
        "question": " 3677億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.787314625186098
    },
    {
        "question": " 1284億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.108730288315182
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.27兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.630589299176497
    },
    {
        "question": " 210万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.32127897953537
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.22垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8467107848958393
    },
    {
        "question": " 6399京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.869632850935986
    },
    {
        "question": " 117京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.511500950828187
    },
    {
        "question": " 6568億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0392623003897528
    },
    {
        "question": " 16億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20410881087699284
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.52億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.4008410061062424
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.45049109683555
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.34年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.199392870505303
    },
    {
        "question": " 1818年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.202099951202569
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.83年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4860953844911755
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.1年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.898475144410735
    },
    {
        "question": " 174万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6776216882799906
    },
    {
        "question": " 3020日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.860190288158108
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2338509418068053
    },
    {
        "question": " 4054日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.544357681759184
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.8万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6237575747067323
    },
    {
        "question": " 189時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.895161380398446
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.39万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4209310333450755
    },
    {
        "question": " 164万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49341015366546115
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.94633530365347
    },
    {
        "question": " 2000万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.522838827457833
    },
    {
        "question": " 1192万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.854580538184125
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.59分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.712192617929741
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.915167353754296
    },
    {
        "question": " 858兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.996864485535399
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.711579067804562
    },
    {
        "question": " 757秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1010953420877634
    },
    {
        "question": " 2160秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.334521975314723
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.194710651098868
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.94垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.788566323699898
    },
    {
        "question": " 116億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1261990843086642
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.55京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.9939569332785
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.080211539595007
    },
    {
        "question": " 434万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6375750331733583
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.068602246205079
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.586778199946644
    },
    {
        "question": " 209京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.38410287109989
    },
    {
        "question": " 12京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.522201806724475
    },
    {
        "question": " 1278億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3283537432142363
    },
    {
        "question": " 317億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.501282328121384
    },
    {
        "question": " 4973usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.6966053643878467
    },
    {
        "question": " 267usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.426439322229571
    },
    {
        "question": " 33京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0191150783853453
    },
    {
        "question": " 3091兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5536544202803837
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.26兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4102666527945209
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.486866233695432
    },
    {
        "question": " 2783兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.444490810634864
    },
    {
        "question": " 9007万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.9545667580039627
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.4兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.732670655483663
    },
    {
        "question": " 3793年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.141233547688651
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.968700569381409
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.34年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.447869259483663
    },
    {
        "question": " 5467億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.17542863659025
    },
    {
        "question": " 324日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8912571439501784
    },
    {
        "question": " 1328日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2815071022939115
    },
    {
        "question": " 461億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.72134862171824
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.9億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.2420719087102
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.114704613604435
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.575603058261658
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.63兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.59188763611143
    },
    {
        "question": " 583億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.987801683824236
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8838433466124316
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.4分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.38414699201996
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.1億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9655064803313127
    },
    {
        "question": " 160兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.267369099200067
    },
    {
        "question": " 98億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4347717017316
    },
    {
        "question": " 5878億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.99110804128308
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.790707345025016
    },
    {
        "question": " 172京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.736957795296178
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.4京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.680082900650941
    },
    {
        "question": " 372万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.014113309969090437
    },
    {
        "question": " 1424億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.375504778684714
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4204042048952192
    },
    {
        "question": " 751万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.875534200578286
    },
    {
        "question": " 2245兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.852359037021506
    },
    {
        "question": " 2189兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.403803999537912
    },
    {
        "question": " 101京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.449694223997978
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.591568600963893
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.076430762264721
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.93億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.840475485112072
    },
    {
        "question": " 32万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.505413655639181
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7642462120544593
    },
    {
        "question": " 449京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.715376689911109
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.95垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.441339858237614
    },
    {
        "question": " 3537京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.77045823838986
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.188117559536574
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.4億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.931465627848306
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.23万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.9152097071615282
    },
    {
        "question": " 700万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.407592770694176
    },
    {
        "question": " 144年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.877798790588595
    },
    {
        "question": " 182億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.697584588387581
    },
    {
        "question": " 2605万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.796074541774042
    },
    {
        "question": " 209万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.479495830119651
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.99日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.634405186709181
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.7兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.484301159054336
    },
    {
        "question": " 914万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.580796578449446
    },
    {
        "question": " 1930億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.564880545457821
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.58万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5027030775296946
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.591873718747727
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.59分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.333599780085204
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.94分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.6194687894864
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8312637321550986
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.1兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.556436344278932
    },
    {
        "question": " 8049万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.34946311481482
    },
    {
        "question": " 101秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22627746953790884
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.1京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.155715101236236
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.1兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.988068701552395
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.3兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.026669437566385
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.5万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8601987650831944
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2874873737860293
    },
    {
        "question": " 416万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.619237355259784
    },
    {
        "question": " 6099msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.785248292503887
    },
    {
        "question": " 922垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.466029856599663
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.26京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.576687395650334
    },
    {
        "question": " 673億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.271566320156997
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.7億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.106436475210298
    },
    {
        "question": " 370億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.568410354377167
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.4万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.6474481372122227
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.510911587585338
    },
    {
        "question": " 2991垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.539277974719358
    },
    {
        "question": " 203垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.750962683709476
    },
    {
        "question": " 5930京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.994885024614796
    },
    {
        "question": " 961京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.982641929457234
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.94兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.899765097156765
    },
    {
        "question": " 260億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.414230585462816
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.801904957727743
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.3億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.009482575783306
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.65億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.80381711386665
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.42日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6920694860216043
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.6万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.351522961831902
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.7億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3295571752575235
    },
    {
        "question": " 3407万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.152166110289052
    },
    {
        "question": " 6589万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.596972526045246
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.718066651955629
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.6万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1221484499661285
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.03兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.54279902385963
    },
    {
        "question": " 138万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3624406235768625
    },
    {
        "question": " 349分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.321064307902036
    },
    {
        "question": " 4476万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15207760647042434
    },
    {
        "question": " 743兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.934599192821413
    },
    {
        "question": " 1061万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4692303281182513
    },
    {
        "question": " 573秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9802129677977611
    },
    {
        "question": " 9447秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.975303295122096
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.717919406778977
    },
    {
        "question": " 8001億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.966617678141131
    },
    {
        "question": " 133億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5673054660058003
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.6兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.663340570654597
    },
    {
        "question": " 1163万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.065488515481266
    },
    {
        "question": " 38万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.579852527964796
    },
    {
        "question": " 3770msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.576285033475978
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.2垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.377293341746922
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.48兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4580404091650356
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.492505926920073
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.8兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.150420443880047
    },
    {
        "question": " 3896億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.590599372330897
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.85万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.4548151061049497
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.338557734471992
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.736383079239944
    },
    {
        "question": " 533垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.790368657329898
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.533450920102262
    },
    {
        "question": " 328兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.738016883803591
    },
    {
        "question": " 1618兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.208975422876297
    },
    {
        "question": " 494万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.694044094577696
    },
    {
        "question": " 527億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.722102065646563
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.594922414823132
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.5万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.808566667091869
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.1年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.477213316334453
    },
    {
        "question": " 1497日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6130470695896229
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.5日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7698841759214297
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.71兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.884509738955366
    },
    {
        "question": " 280億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.067648402276921
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.020107549779001
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.1時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.402144096878487
    },
    {
        "question": " 1056億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.30281387124683
    },
    {
        "question": " 955万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8217906225850307
    },
    {
        "question": " 3209分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.728163109478169
    },
    {
        "question": " 2571億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.91136391116792
    },
    {
        "question": " 744億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.935078446559543
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1597340106208198
    },
    {
        "question": " 2035万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.530493063952361
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6699892850093767
    },
    {
        "question": " 2247兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.415011302056439
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.75兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.385476977302327
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.257367167752557
    },
    {
        "question": " 9804億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.99142148964597
    },
    {
        "question": " 1964msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.293129250434891
    },
    {
        "question": " 147兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6692815953125908
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.6兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5202261827186936
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.789001201028094
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.1兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.856650154135815
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.3億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.262907825249086
    },
    {
        "question": " 37億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.568027975486476
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9718257918131195
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.7京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.742048697967345
    },
    {
        "question": " 134京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.571842830071016
    },
    {
        "question": " 118京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2929762839855155
    },
    {
        "question": " 37億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5679246749454903
    },
    {
        "question": " 466億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.66857113994673
    },
    {
        "question": " 3177億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.502069229416392
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.48万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.103569552123919
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.4年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.466178113868631
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.796278871330508
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5124445689717814
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4560980201465235
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.177110857574222
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.2兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.56250635128345
    },
    {
        "question": " 305億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.103901843156242
    },
    {
        "question": " 167時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.001647044158293
    },
    {
        "question": " 1274時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.661538266953192
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.629013673102834
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.79億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9595194551196413
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.98万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6183371319469475
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.293466119830133
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.7京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.894006844666386
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23483353039646104
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.3億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.109130035812097
    },
    {
        "question": " 582秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9869776278198517
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.79秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.68075688400529
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.8京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.945356288748346
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.08兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9138172356401935
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.79億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4345559146335702
    },
    {
        "question": " 4079億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.832395055053828
    },
    {
        "question": " 539億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.731940011298546
    },
    {
        "question": " 6556msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.816656898700372
    },
    {
        "question": " 9818msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.992030621976514
    },
    {
        "question": " 1137京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.556992563118937
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.7京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.311857713982062
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5398139847537804
    },
    {
        "question": " 1590億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4233723851549245
    },
    {
        "question": " 3741万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5729409470022615
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.086504744479168
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.11垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.410436161972946
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.074456762388753
    },
    {
        "question": " 2945兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9128145355482262
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5653053544264806
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.009380357712198
    },
    {
        "question": " 388兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.588792397698457
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.2695496510314825
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.5万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.124333240947617
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.5万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.820560410575954
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.893607465258725
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.69年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.485082745131844
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.15億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1496209905792565
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.62584896324885
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.87日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.995382842991985
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.72億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.628478115840537
    },
    {
        "question": " 282時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0699367272699079
    },
    {
        "question": " 258万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.189310452752931
    },
    {
        "question": " 538時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.287251343089366
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.8億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.110661079186397
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.854975975253463
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.4万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.121398026312756
    },
    {
        "question": " 9111分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.737702291432415
    },
    {
        "question": " 8274兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.41889744060702
    },
    {
        "question": " 11兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.102936421171584
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6457760994356765
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.4秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16810273756675098
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.267003805831482
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.066381728458705
    },
    {
        "question": " 388兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.090053578661667
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.3億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6684977114979582
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.928499384223854
    },
    {
        "question": " 8922億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.172293980919354
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.1億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.415940451096693
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6597110482691013
    },
    {
        "question": " 188兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.337312531264962
    },
    {
        "question": " 613億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2310273991574172
    },
    {
        "question": " 207億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.537558861103444
    },
    {
        "question": " 846兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.927507864853542
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.6億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.539007732840529
    },
    {
        "question": " 754usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.877587865852867
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.736e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.259785177272526
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.48垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.604764435330832
    },
    {
        "question": " 855京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3756037814215425
    },
    {
        "question": " 1730兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.459934178718199
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.9億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6523033508603648
    },
    {
        "question": " 9112億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.9596278885577725
    },
    {
        "question": " 261億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.416637159940398
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.8万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.28476366994433
    },
    {
        "question": " 2257年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.29601857515326
    },
    {
        "question": " 3454年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.258993135591655
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.615057884610323
    },
    {
        "question": " 6177万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2284985145663
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.7万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.551676460345872
    },
    {
        "question": " 212日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.263389277462057
    },
    {
        "question": " 1296億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.169953468620093
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.696605333592059
    },
    {
        "question": " 3209万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.28446537699097
    },
    {
        "question": " 2時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8567215022211454
    },
    {
        "question": " 322兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.787199768052954
    },
    {
        "question": " 547万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5797166398361657
    },
    {
        "question": " 152億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.40390119504895
    },
    {
        "question": " 1794万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.031852558691547
    },
    {
        "question": " 23億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.863701809476609
    },
    {
        "question": " 4560万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7224479713148964
    },
    {
        "question": " 246万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.834856675646067
    },
    {
        "question": " 8457秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.149085274525362
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.24秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.965798074481585
    },
    {
        "question": " 1397億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6464336911314661
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1002236942723331
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.663347015190868
    },
    {
        "question": " 1160億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.286281615394208
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.45万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9752362896087727
    },
    {
        "question": " 2407msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.381443173669807
    },
    {
        "question": " 1292京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.612423305808817
    },
    {
        "question": " 323兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.572868223154877
    },
    {
        "question": " 1799京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.698843514554008
    },
    {
        "question": " 1338億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.348323246288434
    },
    {
        "question": " 667万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8244501096736578
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.82億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.8336872731823295
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.8usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.50229140373739
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.1京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11431111932560523
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.276026371506812
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.472689772678212
    },
    {
        "question": " 3971兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.820755557909533
    },
    {
        "question": " 405億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.606975056329073
    },
    {
        "question": " 4269万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6303144312441076
    },
    {
        "question": " 3675億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.565268576545582
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.1年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.295587295195656
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.95億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2795467099580735
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.9日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.212082034701015
    },
    {
        "question": " 125万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.25621174909693
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.1万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7212257750603766
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8858894957639123
    },
    {
        "question": " 3784時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.356074326317085
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.758303261302073
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.5兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8294640195163385
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.46億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.491011195880885
    },
    {
        "question": " 4725分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8962624539123984
    },
    {
        "question": " 2859万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.234431694996527
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.979195043938958
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.107756019346626
    },
    {
        "question": " 1773万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6924249223635544
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3376447433017784
    },
    {
        "question": " 1149京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.561576134778857
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.4億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7828253557618734
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4818572140587616
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.608051883027597
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.055601004217368
    },
    {
        "question": " 64msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.805898788211213
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.78垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.332345118483159
    },
    {
        "question": " 3568兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.615871141329788
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6562434673827973
    },
    {
        "question": " 10兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.222177726189079
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.97億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.695923273363113
    },
    {
        "question": " 175億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.243915595535745
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.999e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.802001576602672
    },
    {
        "question": " 5716兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8205723644715466
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.9京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.199016595785836
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.1京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.114467425319605
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.64京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.561433559578623
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.3兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.366960053067636
    },
    {
        "question": " 1918万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.282930975799629
    },
    {
        "question": " 2704万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.994340132349235
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.120479795782213
    },
    {
        "question": " 229万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.798330134384691
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.753040975703163
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.6万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.925878730721488
    },
    {
        "question": " 106日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.961982375252962
    },
    {
        "question": " 67万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8837837527354662
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.47万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.013145892764404
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8687065882635112
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.925152459052457
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.2兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.584177879888918
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.171099461299129
    },
    {
        "question": " 43万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.855554387972504
    },
    {
        "question": " 1539分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.965319100652602
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.37京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.231497033878595
    },
    {
        "question": " 2568億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.473070756664164
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.990624783585152
    },
    {
        "question": " 1536秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4082946087193804
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.46万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.8725436911153315
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.3秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.385514372696612
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.84京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.954349816735446
    },
    {
        "question": " 2689兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.493030912507008
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.7億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6910074553854257
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.3万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9232529187576
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.52兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.742254185735957
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.2万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.945301577933154
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.4msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.719555077860644
    },
    {
        "question": " 1917京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.783910767796393
    },
    {
        "question": " 313京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5585034405207026
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.97京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.219908351268903
    },
    {
        "question": " 106兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.248656161282174
    },
    {
        "question": " 593兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.773336385035996
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.21億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.6245279929551
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.24usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.627504592550838
    },
    {
        "question": " 15垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.678126392674659
    },
    {
        "question": " 5813兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8279014195063592
    },
    {
        "question": " 1724京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6801985836863755
    },
    {
        "question": " 455京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8796346905698575
    },
    {
        "question": " 176兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.244576773513465
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.08兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.783825158977386
    },
    {
        "question": " 3593nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.5555175380219357
    },
    {
        "question": " 2653年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.986011056359832
    },
    {
        "question": " 107万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.973727195457345
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.2年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.58529066263237
    },
    {
        "question": " 104年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.515225839175484
    },
    {
        "question": " 2468万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.830008676099393
    },
    {
        "question": " 836万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.302471839847867
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.4日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.805558348158108
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.6日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.739618369286874
    },
    {
        "question": " 425万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.685872154865768
    },
    {
        "question": " 135万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.74860164773788
    },
    {
        "question": " 349時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.098915411211561
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4043017108263554
    },
    {
        "question": " 1052万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8636459643704555
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.2億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.98650382022993
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.855708639737117
    },
    {
        "question": " 212分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.1041673641357335
    },
    {
        "question": " 2401億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.881622913983275
    },
    {
        "question": " 329万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5808883803317841
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.016988739005487
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.692966178557144
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.37万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.971696162851822
    },
    {
        "question": " 16秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.204277404909608
    },
    {
        "question": " 417兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.120853318812477
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.63京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.047205505324195
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.602778059770424
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.34965501115222897
    },
    {
        "question": " 499億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.697998641400857
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.44msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.808767066226202
    },
    {
        "question": " 369兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.068780591946813
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.18京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.026529527249954
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.628840322359867
    },
    {
        "question": " 5547兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.965881063347771
    },
    {
        "question": " 268兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.42791786426845
    },
    {
        "question": " 5918万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.772198622957432
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.69万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.671453180211256
    },
    {
        "question": " 525京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2215435596164426
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1558754064193972
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.9京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9468925528082694
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.42垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.8676075710126
    },
    {
        "question": " 197兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.294538085795385
    },
    {
        "question": " 6192億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.791802259467827
    },
    {
        "question": " 1889nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.27632677510836534
    },
    {
        "question": " 114万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.617728722153391
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.065491035735237
    },
    {
        "question": " 2398日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8174785781655791
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.46兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.867596273370024
    },
    {
        "question": " 500時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3184561581274468
    },
    {
        "question": " 1311時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.673981782449076
    },
    {
        "question": " 3483兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.821312741215019
    },
    {
        "question": " 2400分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.221871537755568
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.9億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.739393440675987
    },
    {
        "question": " 16万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.981792822212097
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.6分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.6016496665736994
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.52008047638667
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.1億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.608776501268417
    },
    {
        "question": " 710億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.295048972770216
    },
    {
        "question": " 905秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.17827720361661
    },
    {
        "question": " 1186秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.074099881101733
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.4秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.468778988668325
    },
    {
        "question": " 1706兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.733288476274959
    },
    {
        "question": " 302兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.544008162120686
    },
    {
        "question": " 1817兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.703091487033936
    },
    {
        "question": " 163億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.433586522391078
    },
    {
        "question": " 1865万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.270593731565294
    },
    {
        "question": " 269msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.429093789397638
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.7垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.490885487154925
    },
    {
        "question": " 455京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.721167301955627
    },
    {
        "question": " 3532億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.991737762098853
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.7億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1007748237425874
    },
    {
        "question": " 9992兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.999659212539164
    },
    {
        "question": " 1967万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.293813999413568
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.2万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.325670154893762
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.864e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.77161336474504
    },
    {
        "question": " 63京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8630754649220678
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.5京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.195411473056403
    },
    {
        "question": " 419兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.844467011892574
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.98兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9020901562439905
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.6億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.526639597250859
    },
    {
        "question": " 1385nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.14146976525043486
    },
    {
        "question": " 1832万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.82512375290041
    },
    {
        "question": " 389年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.532288809281535
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.021298259628642
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.4万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2728901617880823
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.5万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.943083058720517
    },
    {
        "question": " 287万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.615892916846779
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.101157584186145
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.8万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.290135902443705
    },
    {
        "question": " 937時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.749872354455718
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.67時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.494445720078964
    },
    {
        "question": " 7284億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.141715307412535
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.898827313451292
    },
    {
        "question": " 601億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.000820585614381
    },
    {
        "question": " 824万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.693840152169475
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.7分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.073633179278906
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.249823321581907
    },
    {
        "question": " 3094兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.99171046648354
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.174921559568432
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.964330562594796
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2299211980510845
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3892604378763567
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.7京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2472483515046076
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.218255863306219
    },
    {
        "question": " 585億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.211116155242086
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.3万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9231769508784882
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.28兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.862326258690679
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.4msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.5842108495113445
    },
    {
        "question": " 8736msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.941303103826012
    },
    {
        "question": " 5855京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.268737108105038
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.74垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.739400381944503
    },
    {
        "question": " 847兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.371428168861323
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.52億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8773173457550598
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.193379542390143
    },
    {
        "question": " 164億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.214638586211624
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.2万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.904397237171773
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.2垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.258305780971121
    },
    {
        "question": " 204兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3730675567285868
    },
    {
        "question": " 160京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.649044998293821
    },
    {
        "question": " 6270億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0191459507970624
    },
    {
        "question": " 174億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2410100503019283
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.093993473548197
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.501970790857913
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.804439397736551
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.32年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3080270934647995
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.5億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.32125724918859
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.477648558243978
    },
    {
        "question": " 696日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.001135938853484
    },
    {
        "question": " 874日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.878073138959475
    },
    {
        "question": " 1545万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.246310056781719
    },
    {
        "question": " 6023時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3996095390717223
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.78万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.540086121635886
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.632978411315568
    },
    {
        "question": " 1631万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4917113164378415
    },
    {
        "question": " 459億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.503909251238108
    },
    {
        "question": " 2217億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.567562542004671
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.78万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.669218955271928
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.5分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.506873957277525
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.89億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0906826273155268
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.1億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.909050500930609
    },
    {
        "question": " 1176億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.514072008540015
    },
    {
        "question": " 949秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1989063405589817
    },
    {
        "question": " 148万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.171025729319428
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.8兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1325291689267756
    },
    {
        "question": " 1375兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.201869037437483
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.5兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.163641845520468
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3726754988376495
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.112647128424179
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.1422712410250053
    },
    {
        "question": " 407msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.60935099615739
    },
    {
        "question": " 5590京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.248573860109624
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.6京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.912368973905686
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.754476039571104
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.229062681730574
    },
    {
        "question": " 6149兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.788808502880219
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.04万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.4822612552862546
    },
    {
        "question": " 509usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.706642462622112
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6512592817145717
    },
    {
        "question": " 32京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5687801975026723
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.708742691564221
    },
    {
        "question": " 509兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.928406729355368
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.6京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.7290346483037
    },
    {
        "question": " 8905億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.949637342264635
    },
    {
        "question": " 1613万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.207680638990681
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.202153378051109
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.39年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.028534339760704
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.6億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.227517330515436
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.39829503292261
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.8万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.746950389527674
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.94日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.710387465033292
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.2万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8717252329158418
    },
    {
        "question": " 251億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.018925781276332
    },
    {
        "question": " 10時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.558408937969038
    },
    {
        "question": " 989億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.274413014892966
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.09兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.626284273639204
    },
    {
        "question": " 221分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5670505795725755
    },
    {
        "question": " 2723万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.21322138594804
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.9億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3637052517208765
    },
    {
        "question": " 366兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.62698029532248
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.633052255774263
    },
    {
        "question": " 237万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.596972373236243
    },
    {
        "question": " 127秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.1030798618696185
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.4兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.922488970929047
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.286542210321034
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.5兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.775405820203377
    },
    {
        "question": " 1497億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.396971844544045
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.1万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4928115946497575
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.132089702890019
    },
    {
        "question": " 8199msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.913752101453493
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.4兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4984210605231887
    },
    {
        "question": " 1098兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.103939715248304
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5349355890053094
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.6兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.111595741315476
    },
    {
        "question": " 355万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5506803076250644
    },
    {
        "question": " 526億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.720671410085141
    },
    {
        "question": " 2238京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.850992118017296
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0987295554846206
    },
    {
        "question": " 135京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.572753457858179
    },
    {
        "question": " 889京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.170843329380844
    },
    {
        "question": " 229兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.359513974290524
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.21兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.964418846822401
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.6万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.649321223964296
    },
    {
        "question": " 218年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.901243529464435
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.975060951375198
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.799667850140366
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.27兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.952546249673462
    },
    {
        "question": " 2394万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.759265845786913
    },
    {
        "question": " 762日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.040293692118384
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.19兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.849510081955223
    },
    {
        "question": " 752万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.49578662608924
    },
    {
        "question": " 16万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.981609619641397
    },
    {
        "question": " 796時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.45712969212549
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.1億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5128480331590364
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.94万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.741687814678543
    },
    {
        "question": " 4213分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8463944977755442
    },
    {
        "question": " 443兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.14727919352323
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.83億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.747218620342243
    },
    {
        "question": " 7100万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.294969367138459
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.04億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.069387497009449
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.83垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.953464425081373
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.68兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.492229621222834
    },
    {
        "question": " 4279兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.075054576173093
    },
    {
        "question": " 9052万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1785943329568376
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.58兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.879486177190705
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.06258194015115
    },
    {
        "question": " 2203垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.844311805648957
    },
    {
        "question": " 7017兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.909649721069082
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.76京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.018734358028855
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.2京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.014377346714724
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.91兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.463465136326043
    },
    {
        "question": " 17億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.2300222958086495
    },
    {
        "question": " 113万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.052729339536388
    },
    {
        "question": " 643京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.309094496907548
    },
    {
        "question": " 974京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.05198771391132
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.8兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1499499825068826
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.383290526224789
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.2兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.615402038877355
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.5億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3330549798832445
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.8億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.928480269366396
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.972390139598644
    },
    {
        "question": " 6658日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2610715092234182
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.04兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.540507439856158
    },
    {
        "question": " 298万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0935729393994595
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.22万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.903554066944077
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.842330090374316
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.437569755671127
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.69兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.597061817551134
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.7億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.831179539862893
    },
    {
        "question": " 2037分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.087140644994742
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.023760628355478
    },
    {
        "question": " 457億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1611467945507066
    },
    {
        "question": " 7010億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.909241842973239
    },
    {
        "question": " 2704億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.875744719348061
    },
    {
        "question": " 3573億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.77490692586241
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.75秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.438555530384689
    },
    {
        "question": " 7643秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.883256030199755
    },
    {
        "question": " 6765億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3314878384488438
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.361008875417889
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.67767827662493
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.309448891618793
    },
    {
        "question": " 828億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.91787828802185
    },
    {
        "question": " 7万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.8448872240604
    },
    {
        "question": " 4780兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.180604478592263
    },
    {
        "question": " 1986京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.361582063935613
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.75503546972427
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.5億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6291078864914443
    },
    {
        "question": " 464万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6661230073181745
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.1万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.996057850860411
    },
    {
        "question": " 864万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.936464034284448
    },
    {
        "question": " 3966垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.099512542050385
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.5京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6484383920709607
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.576574664421472
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.267148634569786
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.5京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.744065029973443
    },
    {
        "question": " 138万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.13984782573230436
    },
    {
        "question": " 3207億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.506139868905837
    },
    {
        "question": " 264年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.984376826738471
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.4万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.599965876627696
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6964519185251636
    },
    {
        "question": " 7724日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.268046387827284
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.257597193844681
    },
    {
        "question": " 250万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4553351227993456
    },
    {
        "question": " 1358万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.752666867105668
    },
    {
        "question": " 8万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.681265004648509
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.7439071029827335
    },
    {
        "question": " 322億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.787600164966354
    },
    {
        "question": " 5989分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6189891518242285
    },
    {
        "question": " 1169万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2895708530476675
    },
    {
        "question": " 296分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.249367239641256
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.792867794771621
    },
    {
        "question": " 1304億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.178791280896974
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.1万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9369291279572431
    },
    {
        "question": " 404秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8277689899573737
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.2万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.725664814219726
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.97秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.472195076972248
    },
    {
        "question": " 1448兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.661991759011959
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.7兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.61650612031595
    },
    {
        "question": " 8625億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.379480246882558
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.28億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7372896868769354
    },
    {
        "question": " 8399msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9242221189493682
    },
    {
        "question": " 363万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.559318417058954
    },
    {
        "question": " 2261兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.855571504014344
    },
    {
        "question": " 8536億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9947304626785869
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.02京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.748914983633524
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.328448074590606
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.419778317839016
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.86万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5866896371370354
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.9京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1906331451677443
    },
    {
        "question": " 381垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.64407033697471
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.641357700453501
    },
    {
        "question": " 7951兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.122279201584892
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.4兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.437259292181911
    },
    {
        "question": " 2161兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.334575132753264
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.224171131069632
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7975873819036376
    },
    {
        "question": " 5704日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.19384675219118
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.43246346733272
    },
    {
        "question": " 827日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.075999582070243
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.8日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.313223735993684
    },
    {
        "question": " 344億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.593856957522922
    },
    {
        "question": " 117億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.68684674363787
    },
    {
        "question": " 1920時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.839554951764889
    },
    {
        "question": " 273兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.714802786616152
    },
    {
        "question": " 8344億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.763006356572275
    },
    {
        "question": " 1261分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.322677553239584
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.4万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.01980119727533
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.8兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.386735258280842
    },
    {
        "question": " 4018万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6675309612975138
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.14億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.297468250090316
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.310683924740168
    },
    {
        "question": " 795秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.900376403809588
    },
    {
        "question": " 3184兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.004216619056222
    },
    {
        "question": " 523億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7818265276898813
    },
    {
        "question": " 5213兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.16082764672045
    },
    {
        "question": " 255兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.628517116549363
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1762295670218914
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.4msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.421742532302259
    },
    {
        "question": " 527垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.22281070967591
    },
    {
        "question": " 4677億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7334555885810068
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.32兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2442540938839413
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.9兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.752215965667689
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.263725486234578
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.088915215930092
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.101674706082116
    },
    {
        "question": " 25京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8985228440735338
    },
    {
        "question": " 2319京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.428867562089961
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.8兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2418066674104566
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.3京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6888826869138365
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.9兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.953853655914542
    },
    {
        "question": " 136兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.134377613388674
    },
    {
        "question": " 1568万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.195380533091964
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.46万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.372604966427642
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.961329967122703
    },
    {
        "question": " 225年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.073544788976799
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.5年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.742437164829687
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.6万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.435950858036266
    },
    {
        "question": " 623日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.174740213298914
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2096556638980966
    },
    {
        "question": " 661万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.877493773703078
    },
    {
        "question": " 577億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.380914142742492
    },
    {
        "question": " 122時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.864193685365188
    },
    {
        "question": " 174万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.79620941846281
    },
    {
        "question": " 1246億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.375019246584154
    },
    {
        "question": " 263万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.261760075918345
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.8分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19844575106473417
    },
    {
        "question": " 108分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.810842579136411
    },
    {
        "question": " 5311億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.226339042506409
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.4億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7392169676127
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.85億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.029046291085532
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.340310913240276
    },
    {
        "question": " 2064秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.314659753582638
    },
    {
        "question": " 346京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.040473440739294
    },
    {
        "question": " 1883兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.338241583602832
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.62兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.002713282925445
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.37220895907942
    },
    {
        "question": " 4223msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6256291612703335
    },
    {
        "question": " 4745兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1774329489504995
    },
    {
        "question": " 166兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.283453802609121
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.6億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12168773659820942
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.31856368982249
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.9億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5038763836095486
    },
    {
        "question": " 2582億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.411875056876308
    },
    {
        "question": " 5057京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.205112480469766
    },
    {
        "question": " 3079兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5518980728935505
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.3京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.965918833799527
    },
    {
        "question": " 5875京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.990873825181223
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.034439411138612
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.327708305854351
    },
    {
        "question": " 9118万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.959916370320448
    },
    {
        "question": " 185年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.829366425254543
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.8万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.640073469918443
    },
    {
        "question": " 212万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.765025243756863
    },
    {
        "question": " 2600万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.795205451750727
    },
    {
        "question": " 550万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.898635766060787
    },
    {
        "question": " 1454万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.220102186336921
    },
    {
        "question": " 900時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.574250944663238
    },
    {
        "question": " 393万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.372269030715215
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.7万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.097122964660166
    },
    {
        "question": " 4967兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.975480171212066
    },
    {
        "question": " 8717分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7819982847338225
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.1分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07960982758123736
    },
    {
        "question": " 123万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.86961239534985
    },
    {
        "question": " 246分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.169827940013953
    },
    {
        "question": " 832兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.421135964906727
    },
    {
        "question": " 7150万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.917812443893859
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.30799319351922
    },
    {
        "question": " 543億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.956640870615608
    },
    {
        "question": " 1515秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.180471369617196
    },
    {
        "question": " 2233億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8500754119812948
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.1兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.555880127108751
    },
    {
        "question": " 931兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.412423876172712
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.55898633655655
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.6億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.789589733136329
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.5万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.351411641517617
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.93951408114178
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.9兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7867804833670142
    },
    {
        "question": " 652兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.257729911197848
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.2兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.937813454011262
    },
    {
        "question": " 265億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.422721134003296
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.11万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.9597038513604192
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.119747303882304
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.458e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.891708775088576
    },
    {
        "question": " 192兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3463969914853182
    },
    {
        "question": " 101垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.446756634175449
    },
    {
        "question": " 2066京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.536882093627826
    },
    {
        "question": " 681京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.833370756165845
    },
    {
        "question": " 3786兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.578136447619045
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.69兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.671481212439662
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.5万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.191173712998648
    },
    {
        "question": " 4197年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.343546711218462
    },
    {
        "question": " 136億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.57021277585607
    },
    {
        "question": " 3819万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.962162367025973
    },
    {
        "question": " 1213万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1414236778878815
    },
    {
        "question": " 1494万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.794149065925059
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9694774636026269
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.19時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.347826272825079
    },
    {
        "question": " 315時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.05479814026249
    },
    {
        "question": " 40兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.881209838559108
    },
    {
        "question": " 2197分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18356609950666014
    },
    {
        "question": " 378万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.799781123280839
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.83分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.770879169103954
    },
    {
        "question": " 264分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.199051259308934
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.95億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9716502296116836
    },
    {
        "question": " 14万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2094656815959428
    },
    {
        "question": " 139万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.586170712015069
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.6秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2023880902757702
    },
    {
        "question": " 111万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.043768496651323
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.84兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3953274955628867
    },
    {
        "question": " 948兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.040218175048287
    },
    {
        "question": " 475兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.120313186107545
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.298897290447383
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.158906118909374
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.057332960474488
    },
    {
        "question": " 3489msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.542668985842624
    },
    {
        "question": " 1413兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6514130927622472
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.41京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.70836066603471
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.545687373365268
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5821951506433298
    },
    {
        "question": " 1022万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0094383539595064
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.099153336359327
    },
    {
        "question": " 132usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.121780641912003
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.9垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.143707999736603
    },
    {
        "question": " 253垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.465954099065577
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.37垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.173699626472091
    },
    {
        "question": " 889京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.170565425054097
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.8京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.318994946022363
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.6兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.775521784576296
    },
    {
        "question": " 103億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.013309244478423
    },
    {
        "question": " 2138万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.892293518809932
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.09805341309828
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.805271820763005
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.48億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.249570132501741
    },
    {
        "question": " 172日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.615389361967286
    },
    {
        "question": " 483万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.842007528372418
    },
    {
        "question": " 75日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.811280529193551
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.4万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7601036762983724
    },
    {
        "question": " 8249時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.536185744286923
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.38万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.750169739302382
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.58時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.43591294140702
    },
    {
        "question": " 7272億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.14103344143179
    },
    {
        "question": " 5992万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.619201549974709
    },
    {
        "question": " 2213億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.566740148348599
    },
    {
        "question": " 1896万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.056085655731636
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.3億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.18521474518395
    },
    {
        "question": " 4772万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.74217763351308
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.48兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.83823115811211
    },
    {
        "question": " 186秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4904176921126435
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.7万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.576033414210105
    },
    {
        "question": " 9674秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.985599774112861
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.793646016180631
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.095988964243784
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.637822523737801
    },
    {
        "question": " 392兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.814773098020595
    },
    {
        "question": " 6909msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8394085914764138
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.08msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.6110774588228987
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.561225663877249
    },
    {
        "question": " 126京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.164440155647763
    },
    {
        "question": " 111兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.487836323235392
    },
    {
        "question": " 2843億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.675622087247523
    },
    {
        "question": " 4496兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.652796922395751
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.3億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.4819272207236125
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.55京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3789686819393978
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.20156765130257
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.530881880464718
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4797495814814345
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.4京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.46887431060171
    },
    {
        "question": " 43兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.633680962252182
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.95兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.900443136866441
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.6年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.498838334746433
    },
    {
        "question": " 116年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.563379413082382
    },
    {
        "question": " 277万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8805055620678286
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.4万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.119260702315243
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.48億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.931230311907195
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.896618490920223
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0689225728228715
    },
    {
        "question": " 125時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.654525345047656
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.41億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.661102432453112
    },
    {
        "question": " 3260万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.354858263452882
    },
    {
        "question": " 380万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.801867843466516
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.03兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.202374914943753
    },
    {
        "question": " 1677万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.288053796088403
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.5万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1803700530963077
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.5億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.880316055053615
    },
    {
        "question": " 63万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.799602796725857
    },
    {
        "question": " 247秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.392349116905974
    },
    {
        "question": " 5878億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2704395984972439
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.324759379552889
    },
    {
        "question": " 54兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.17582583597375
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2463993322114788
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.21億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.624047613315996
    },
    {
        "question": " 556万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.744940420821923
    },
    {
        "question": " 737msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.86752041279123
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.91京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.192362397452264
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2737290723047163
    },
    {
        "question": " 396京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.041797926518644
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.89京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.99213966256373
    },
    {
        "question": " 5158兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.71244445252185
    },
    {
        "question": " 4145億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.617526938067432
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.313e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.470296985095594
    },
    {
        "question": " 904垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.019700140213102
    },
    {
        "question": " 5374京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.173984710538362
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.68京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.650678800866341
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.17兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.500658993320458
    },
    {
        "question": " 1195万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.0772095516543734
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.276898191440523
    },
    {
        "question": " 243年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.884961360204171
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6723126792296805
    },
    {
        "question": " 1510日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5591531031090256
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.068954467746096
    },
    {
        "question": " 867万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.995570724721733
    },
    {
        "question": " 4781時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.299326161436449
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8275395090822117
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.3万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.202971560811475
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.05兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1274316538216524
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9925034470428216
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.362433533337727
    },
    {
        "question": " 675分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.607544717719286
    },
    {
        "question": " 1115兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.548403692537758
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.091586844981008
    },
    {
        "question": " 6231秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23826256558844516
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.05億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.924858799314089
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.120168630540467
    },
    {
        "question": " 581秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.764087363034827
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.53京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.480481372854026
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.148864388849639
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.56億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9957142730973088
    },
    {
        "question": " 193億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.507237587349922
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.158520750769142
    },
    {
        "question": " 330垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.019484822929138
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3181232230297446
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.792971186169654
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.22兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.186731057697297
    },
    {
        "question": " 2717万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4340930594038048
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.023329262438653
    },
    {
        "question": " 6859京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3374865184896176
    },
    {
        "question": " 6827垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.897732721986062
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6798503941195237
    },
    {
        "question": " 1992兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.52110037582207
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.3兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.656539169938464
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.345332080821911
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.4万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.4682544969677958
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.3万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.08103334943707
    },
    {
        "question": " 6526年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7571580099146065
    },
    {
        "question": " 1869年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.992324258558128
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.5777455940776
    },
    {
        "question": " 4037日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.986270014643377
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.6日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.87110160381513
    },
    {
        "question": " 446万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.706993654215818
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7982146192769077
    },
    {
        "question": " 2280万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.136113071521262
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.4万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.2673068911959
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4382811143718097
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.09593052768704
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.456762515312896
    },
    {
        "question": " 319分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.281928953586405
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.879106960217649
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.51兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.31489630341063
    },
    {
        "question": " 408億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.673708793756575
    },
    {
        "question": " 566万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1962230361150845
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.19億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.724971489032302
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.4万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.76612665063128
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.886311467246075
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.5億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9358151369235332
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.2兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.079125510810188
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.6万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7220754552799824
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.58億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.746528144987641
    },
    {
        "question": " 25万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.397664004046216
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.1msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.6540022209141965
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.1兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16529818354899417
    },
    {
        "question": " 238京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.440009885059729
    },
    {
        "question": " 3488億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9863384779907312
    },
    {
        "question": " 9047億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.178374429407005
    },
    {
        "question": " 798万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9021881990903813
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.0048372053885546
    },
    {
        "question": " 300usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.476591615864819
    },
    {
        "question": " 3910京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0934131711134016
    },
    {
        "question": " 851兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9935231603448058
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.3垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.81175463722416
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.428486758542831
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.03京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.904675103089943
    },
    {
        "question": " 491万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.6911865175087684
    },
    {
        "question": " 41億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.612623525534712
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.5万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.265995821878262
    },
    {
        "question": " 1020年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.729448291599788
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.08万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7552785343796695
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.559230453458257
    },
    {
        "question": " 1826日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.419934474122135
    },
    {
        "question": " 863日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.872352913371628
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.9611829200248785
    },
    {
        "question": " 366万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.621427949730284
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.4億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.421885422972169
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.29時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.073116438787604
    },
    {
        "question": " 334億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.80338948607168
    },
    {
        "question": " 2863分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2984965535158324
    },
    {
        "question": " 2857万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.67773291091622
    },
    {
        "question": " 963分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.761759429251034
    },
    {
        "question": " 173分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.016335493513717
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.634970973939392
    },
    {
        "question": " 637万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8678662184934613
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.662561018459767
    },
    {
        "question": " 1629億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.433819392214582
    },
    {
        "question": " 1899秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.278507167919124
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.843495672315123
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.70663354155624
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.82億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.055737961052745
    },
    {
        "question": " 531億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.168449389226286
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.1万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1617264078555112
    },
    {
        "question": " 464億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.666410766835034
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.3万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.594333211577075
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7019307884454875
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2353698182826045
    },
    {
        "question": " 4974兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.140390279164707
    },
    {
        "question": " 3488億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7644311649314877
    },
    {
        "question": " 4590億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.661765416675405
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.8億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.754520521736955
    },
    {
        "question": " 163usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.213119267821051
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.5垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1954145008811645
    },
    {
        "question": " 5784垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.825710438570814
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.3兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9526555452340268
    },
    {
        "question": " 147京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.388079555790696
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.54京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.815509565638646
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.28兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.3586626152711005
    },
    {
        "question": " 5676nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.7540150453442718
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.8年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.656545417440963
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.3万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.918475874423969
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.16万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.999719973025379
    },
    {
        "question": " 944日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.911396730487378
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.04万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7598035439741069
    },
    {
        "question": " 1113万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6664373880785135
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.886523543108295
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.17時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.176935508667976
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.9時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.046544499134473
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.9兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.111114693640802
    },
    {
        "question": " 231億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.204629173742551
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.5万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.116723122067839
    },
    {
        "question": " 4354分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.417027911921451
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.104664684355354
    },
    {
        "question": " 154分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.966433128258862
    },
    {
        "question": " 3347億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.025804306523556
    },
    {
        "question": " 8699万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0029519134258873
    },
    {
        "question": " 3029億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.925053757077167
    },
    {
        "question": " 1243万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.316434106044243
    },
    {
        "question": " 912秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.959795282963702
    },
    {
        "question": " 2176京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.838902040608659
    },
    {
        "question": " 383億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6465552183630994
    },
    {
        "question": " 476億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.121559784640633
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.04億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.82782209971539
    },
    {
        "question": " 8437億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.926197464210878
    },
    {
        "question": " 224msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.349291469983488
    },
    {
        "question": " 637msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.803999832949344
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.6垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.052805364263099
    },
    {
        "question": " 1587京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.264100772500052
    },
    {
        "question": " 104京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.461745162115026
    },
    {
        "question": " 751兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.097320553912367
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.22760357666278
    },
    {
        "question": " 417万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6197563382263933
    },
    {
        "question": " 5584usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.746920943271599
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.384e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.878423753358393
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.39763862317695
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.7垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.366502694197646
    },
    {
        "question": " 3兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6983213736819225
    },
    {
        "question": " 650京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.812887537312298
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.190013428611147
    },
    {
        "question": " 102万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.0083177265276873
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.04万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.871424573164978
    },
    {
        "question": " 477年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.620743223364678
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.46年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.110828703072098
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.78226704233409
    },
    {
        "question": " 627万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.235103508984778
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.84日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.834089319788501
    },
    {
        "question": " 230万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.519423033742529
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.193588251786434
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.24万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.407583374119872
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.6万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.348866253977148
    },
    {
        "question": " 300時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.255702823252677
    },
    {
        "question": " 121時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.638565053230806
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.94兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.053133337996127
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.17737389118845
    },
    {
        "question": " 122万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.307221142902837
    },
    {
        "question": " 517分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.491385363020475
    },
    {
        "question": " 3125億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9960945150009666
    },
    {
        "question": " 214億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.39295198168227
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.09兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.402429868084885
    },
    {
        "question": " 101万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.227103115471622
    },
    {
        "question": " 6418秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.807412885336337
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.639957678590527
    },
    {
        "question": " 3754億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6380324963632136
    },
    {
        "question": " 6101兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.229081171471904
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.3億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.837933740708653
    },
    {
        "question": " 18万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.255114706001752
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.388201288187098
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.79京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.444989888633941
    },
    {
        "question": " 713京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.916387743757448
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.78京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.334652644465727
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.5億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.082179446064454
    },
    {
        "question": " 5502万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.740540406591814
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.433913680015193
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.443e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.660413274827059
    },
    {
        "question": " 1189兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1385724752667448
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8427876152405807
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.345041589468307
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.190373092581355
    },
    {
        "question": " 1400億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.146038185756655
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.286136566343287
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.069943513172144
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.47年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.371433870293249
    },
    {
        "question": " 296億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.90893748877982
    },
    {
        "question": " 907万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.337739978371394
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.947259352874507
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.168380560049401
    },
    {
        "question": " 1018億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.065296846790153
    },
    {
        "question": " 1364億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.754513205803057
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.3万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.641366878398336
    },
    {
        "question": " 661時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3766827993002915
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.88時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.325529654575944
    },
    {
        "question": " 340兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.811020576460642
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2006389735621426
    },
    {
        "question": " 469万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.892808196174378
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.937721525564325
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.3京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.869163589223115
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.3万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5591166191105368
    },
    {
        "question": " 298万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9181194133897073
    },
    {
        "question": " 2535万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.625884392211466
    },
    {
        "question": " 337万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.527350904662498
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.57京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.911054340299279
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.18京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.68438137982026
    },
    {
        "question": " 8324億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.36400835205344
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.286581133634023
    },
    {
        "question": " 124万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.093233585226006
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.002381164603216
    },
    {
        "question": " 5088京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.207737245979778
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.254646890858599
    },
    {
        "question": " 320兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.949065580767878
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.3京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.964962006086806
    },
    {
        "question": " 5205万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7164037081556327
    },
    {
        "question": " 2951usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.4699143102731451
    },
    {
        "question": " 9996usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.99982760558325
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.618032383170835
    },
    {
        "question": " 7135垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.91691924719259
    },
    {
        "question": " 4502京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.097100929518881
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.1京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.125700437182
    },
    {
        "question": " 6759億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8298569897833445
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.91兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.464567057486463
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.9万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.529686294092045
    },
    {
        "question": " 1295万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.674549250486923
    },
    {
        "question": " 768年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.82813327394236
    },
    {
        "question": " 181年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.978855437505863
    },
    {
        "question": " 1590億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.639007828574357
    },
    {
        "question": " 127日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4847477988545883
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4203377821128256
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.8日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.567930741623883
    },
    {
        "question": " 9368時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.029168176609808416
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.75万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1940602777320883
    },
    {
        "question": " 252万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.179909550958918
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.826839931598148
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.3時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.291159968419
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6675594789129082
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9285291762453083
    },
    {
        "question": " 29万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.684088041103122
    },
    {
        "question": " 209万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.09766230168478
    },
    {
        "question": " 8228億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.416520170436068
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.096494638890624
    },
    {
        "question": " 1913億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.725520192315699
    },
    {
        "question": " 2555秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6293169836394072
    },
    {
        "question": " 2569秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.409793092015084
    },
    {
        "question": " 1590秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.201320219713802
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.437449034119961
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.69142330659828
    },
    {
        "question": " 439億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7058018857964794
    },
    {
        "question": " 3772兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.02031514290899
    },
    {
        "question": " 6082億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.00586103456574
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.136932663552187
    },
    {
        "question": " 121msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.08329026485425
    },
    {
        "question": " 8379兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4243795252724087
    },
    {
        "question": " 3415兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.596911523329698
    },
    {
        "question": " 312億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.938105098764801
    },
    {
        "question": " 5192兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.937175171511139
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.9兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.77762380688184
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.5億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.9372521463687296
    },
    {
        "question": " 2936usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.467827636360678
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.319e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.621345186798505
    },
    {
        "question": " 4709垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.73639985011356
    },
    {
        "question": " 4555京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.102158678014055
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.88兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.059338765388464
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.3億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5478124401486317
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.2億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.5703776682982102
    },
    {
        "question": " 1289nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.1103385319864969
    },
    {
        "question": " 634万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.364072150933628
    },
    {
        "question": " 110年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.981916088824361
    },
    {
        "question": " 357万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.990582810841785
    },
    {
        "question": " 195万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.449434614641333
    },
    {
        "question": " 2612日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.353465479243091
    },
    {
        "question": " 385億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.642617645737089
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8807976364622103
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.320436157976127
    },
    {
        "question": " 10万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.556936060215296
    },
    {
        "question": " 1791兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.532516193607002
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.7万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2348160429316657
    },
    {
        "question": " 108分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.25371323040360716
    },
    {
        "question": " 154分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9663721791516613
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.9分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.295103601168064
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.650950514308718
    },
    {
        "question": " 1062万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.089743858355929
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.727950973382008
    },
    {
        "question": " 2715億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.655666948673844
    },
    {
        "question": " 2861億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9577795246821341
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3183249609530292
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.7億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.269995158342205
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.1億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8244897180331066
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.7万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2939621474359093
    },
    {
        "question": " 128msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.1083183844812785
    },
    {
        "question": " 888msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.948247439379323
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.6京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1789366568962425
    },
    {
        "question": " 3278億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5790681233241157
    },
    {
        "question": " 2939京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.911848921090758
    },
    {
        "question": " 798兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.12400312686788
    },
    {
        "question": " 173万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2382537573528487
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.1万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.9915602428146
    },
    {
        "question": " 2051usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.311916355347382
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.218e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.847251380509225
    },
    {
        "question": " 961垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.046416652744613
    },
    {
        "question": " 6534兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2588835447066176
    },
    {
        "question": " 367京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7864949487333845
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.2京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.570353186167525
    },
    {
        "question": " 1156万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.0630698525750637
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.261324947223964
    },
    {
        "question": " 358万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.116372061258778
    },
    {
        "question": " 133年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.067435942755366
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.69年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.324175873118062
    },
    {
        "question": " 1540億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.625196144717854
    },
    {
        "question": " 123日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4713348122216017
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.3日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.998883711808179
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.243970549616328
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.749496964167709
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.81時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4605382993049076
    },
    {
        "question": " 1876時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.829622803288343
    },
    {
        "question": " 79兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.177050061955114
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.32万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6420248858637376
    },
    {
        "question": " 506万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.926352748212813
    },
    {
        "question": " 3702万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.346619068795993
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.85万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.233441289591301
    },
    {
        "question": " 153分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.96271387781991
    },
    {
        "question": " 9746万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49002390614296454
    },
    {
        "question": " 191万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3451512214615946
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.787957210634759
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.03万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9233632645505425
    },
    {
        "question": " 1657秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.2193188427655315
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.18151827441337
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.2京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.137004687503062
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.91兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.059386421962648
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.5兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.866250606529229
    },
    {
        "question": " 217兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.557490951034367
    },
    {
        "question": " 196万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2916534996933033
    },
    {
        "question": " 277msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.442815939797146
    },
    {
        "question": " 185msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.266123527289986
    },
    {
        "question": " 960兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.483498058189957
    },
    {
        "question": " 2342億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43309287600280966
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6249745045009973
    },
    {
        "question": " 1180兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.293556862045339
    },
    {
        "question": " 2195兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.34135619903693
    },
    {
        "question": " 1271億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.104308128216012
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.9垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.080386431627092
    },
    {
        "question": " 137兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20099585977705337
    },
    {
        "question": " 721兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3015575340898997
    },
    {
        "question": " 9769兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.211699524410784
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.23992230775211
    },
    {
        "question": " 1786億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.251991775356758
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.38万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.5294249033130758
    },
    {
        "question": " 401年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.545453824754538
    },
    {
        "question": " 5152年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.432661433067583
    },
    {
        "question": " 1310万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.555126335637319
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5402244374701946
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.1万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.929797710704936
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.92万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.628418020842789
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.3兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.713251984113239
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.6万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.600395582478947
    },
    {
        "question": " 3662万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.341834551920861
    },
    {
        "question": " 227時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.913227442452714
    },
    {
        "question": " 7598億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.160029766563788
    },
    {
        "question": " 2253億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.194368820871157
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.243187442100093
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.11分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.270634354897804
    },
    {
        "question": " 5145億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.212544388079943
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.5万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7214978423097573
    },
    {
        "question": " 1968万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7376329201219316
    },
    {
        "question": " 332億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.74293737817599
    },
    {
        "question": " 500万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.698775409220925
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.54兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.432450360240722
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.7億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7771552067399587
    },
    {
        "question": " 8542万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3752770598573172
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.7万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5774476479761415
    },
    {
        "question": " 1773億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.248605374516062
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.153146188777846
    },
    {
        "question": " 412msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.61478418673958
    },
    {
        "question": " 203京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.809582398894388
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.123401270757446
    },
    {
        "question": " 2616兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.861383706063887
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49231716627943456
    },
    {
        "question": " 144兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.157664293481657
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.468698283031227
    },
    {
        "question": " 684usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.8351075033492075
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.764e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.443880859364311
    },
    {
        "question": " 889京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.012195098159537
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6373369406229052
    },
    {
        "question": " 161兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4291524990018307
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.26007781871681
    },
    {
        "question": " 2177兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.33790248866717
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.411162170544603
    },
    {
        "question": " 1660年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.782290298781944
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.47年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.112665095375136
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.32兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.959163909806632
    },
    {
        "question": " 4629万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.045662521201407
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.63万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.718696210960144
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.27万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.798031134452787
    },
    {
        "question": " 572億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.815185162985974
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.5億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.355881730363928
    },
    {
        "question": " 458万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.439432405945766
    },
    {
        "question": " 523時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.27510551731363
    },
    {
        "question": " 4156億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.898037437265443
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0590920939207171
    },
    {
        "question": " 140分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3669391095708552
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.252135938877967
    },
    {
        "question": " 106分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.804492398710865
    },
    {
        "question": " 402億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1051026202090934
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.76兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6383157235167385
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.98万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4427839481220395
    },
    {
        "question": " 534億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.949036680419592
    },
    {
        "question": " 260万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.415283011243083
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.32京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.365464253865309
    },
    {
        "question": " 2302兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.425526444083685
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.716086898496076
    },
    {
        "question": " 11万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2638754742017291
    },
    {
        "question": " 2496億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.397197102758023
    },
    {
        "question": " 945垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.476489780638692
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.09兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3844835610743578
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.6京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.304387797459889
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6598465281238042
    },
    {
        "question": " 3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.476916504629129
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.6億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.3346279878418335
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.277565214661932
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.209e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.583608506924303
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.87垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.057799762926119
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.74京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.272184822817716
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.456488948684305
    },
    {
        "question": " 501兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.699753164544576
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.82億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.6831302284973244
    },
    {
        "question": " 2545億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.405613055448546
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.98万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.259330475782734
    },
    {
        "question": " 1227年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.03148539872161
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.2年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.883473465517692
    },
    {
        "question": " 2626億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.857048956318382
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.1万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.02431703884816
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.6万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.715231767347191
    },
    {
        "question": " 107億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.087552617250954
    },
    {
        "question": " 275時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0587860426052842
    },
    {
        "question": " 1937万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.065285313301404
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.3時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.066074910136727
    },
    {
        "question": " 10兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2801306409451785
    },
    {
        "question": " 4298万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.474875733675806
    },
    {
        "question": " 602万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.00109047818321
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.7分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5339223262769464
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.46万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.16820833424359
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.9京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.191238535979027
    },
    {
        "question": " 8251万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.980012928851994
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.23兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.161986426176455
    },
    {
        "question": " 2685万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.650868330491402
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.886313086706295
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.585585056218792
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.7億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6155847588293315
    },
    {
        "question": " 385兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.02909557512744
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.4兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.869617176276252
    },
    {
        "question": " 1562msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19361535547487652
    },
    {
        "question": " 1504msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.177118946871665
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6285730998921717
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.353172969314
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.38京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0852621524479495
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.635247316483228
    },
    {
        "question": " 1435万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.156879144014431
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.34万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5243663000669994
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.28垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.468634621714473
    },
    {
        "question": " 5447京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7996901429025485
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.901304072718776
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.343937123076325
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.7京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.729937309853172
    },
    {
        "question": " 1854兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.268052064647092
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.92兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.283832975060006
    },
    {
        "question": " 1249年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.039052995154794
    },
    {
        "question": " 960億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.420038677704783
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.309653994099154
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1158191694376518
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.992670655453898
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.5万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.372784463153694
    },
    {
        "question": " 466億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.947764972971901
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.6万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2828743287893785
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.389561554867756
    },
    {
        "question": " 7210分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.636075002278545
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.64分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.338757299503808
    },
    {
        "question": " 6654億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.324307181040176
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.2兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.909534026649323
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.71兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.117009167758543
    },
    {
        "question": " 798万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.124054570281737
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.16秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.499214942484894
    },
    {
        "question": " 2294億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8617377837487006
    },
    {
        "question": " 120億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.14137942915821
    },
    {
        "question": " 306億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9296544139764844
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.696102497155186
    },
    {
        "question": " 5877億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.769154920253644
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.20606250690795
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.066827210050079
    },
    {
        "question": " 163兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7133567310906752
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.25兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6918328942358851
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.702064769536434
    },
    {
        "question": " 2314億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5861702269752485
    },
    {
        "question": " 6640兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.822189998307548
    },
    {
        "question": " 6033万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.780544455787599
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.571e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.69727306119096
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.5垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.97986340782031
    },
    {
        "question": " 68兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.276377559812818
    },
    {
        "question": " 355兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7720066023184327
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.79京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.578570546269559
    },
    {
        "question": " 842兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.92533601962538
    },
    {
        "question": " 4240nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.6273708171357639
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.060260830877926
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.539988807843001
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.02日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9846859874804479
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.5日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.564053148309336
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.1兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.843515926039782
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.009702234350639
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.5万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.233448345599635
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.4時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.088278817088229
    },
    {
        "question": " 1455万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4421564613147442
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.82万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.524696833104443
    },
    {
        "question": " 22万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.563671651763011
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.802227063271259
    },
    {
        "question": " 30億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9786398425063034
    },
    {
        "question": " 256億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.472458491666124
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.580729151390792
    },
    {
        "question": " 1350億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.35227267515015
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.3秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.701796577148361
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9097699585183867
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.35億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5890033700487718
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.2億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.066961568372583
    },
    {
        "question": " 35兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.766043811443112
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.29万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6324525700582693
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.73万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.8280597560960254
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.240985827570828
    },
    {
        "question": " 2607兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9172603959167056
    },
    {
        "question": " 106京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.089807589153061
    },
    {
        "question": " 317兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.94525230936506
    },
    {
        "question": " 480兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.902950585999198
    },
    {
        "question": " 309万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.48994343495751935
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.260049831278735
    },
    {
        "question": " 3329usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.522311641691079
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5320531969826785
    },
    {
        "question": " 154京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.251259715943368
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.4兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2098265653139828
    },
    {
        "question": " 3垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.699519198607963
    },
    {
        "question": " 650兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.812697363375348
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.2億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.401751297073241
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.5億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.667597771779009
    },
    {
        "question": " 111万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.608443627797145
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.8年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.148624557782117
    },
    {
        "question": " 3495日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9811679908638371
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.9万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.801271648197126
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.040977036046137
    },
    {
        "question": " 86億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.992140220040999
    },
    {
        "question": " 295億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.089072205955539
    },
    {
        "question": " 10時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.780007691251005
    },
    {
        "question": " 1278時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.662897583524438
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.23時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.5213360926884825
    },
    {
        "question": " 5030億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.980950108772486
    },
    {
        "question": " 1168億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.909231967962443
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.92億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0616558646383965
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.939855179069873
    },
    {
        "question": " 195分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.067606107756256
    },
    {
        "question": " 18京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.757341623844903
    },
    {
        "question": " 1852億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.331207949448066
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.618117226408382
    },
    {
        "question": " 2168秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.557825451172976
    },
    {
        "question": " 298秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.4741582571568195
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.119768470022125
    },
    {
        "question": " 3951京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.097866369515144
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.9億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0125236380184464
    },
    {
        "question": " 1836万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7076542635674765
    },
    {
        "question": " 199億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.519763723900095
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.11万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3237819501861559
    },
    {
        "question": " 962msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.983204746220373
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.618872469723877
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.87京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.900466332811334
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.16兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.233482621523577
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.281289947174633
    },
    {
        "question": " 348億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.54191295085357
    },
    {
        "question": " 6737usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.8284940774545857
    },
    {
        "question": " 811京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4100193754738495
    },
    {
        "question": " 1360京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.197136007669961
    },
    {
        "question": " 3075兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9314817061793774
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.1京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.114452532933201
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.32京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.366315263557124
    },
    {
        "question": " 500万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.6986466075884734
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.6万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.574939425151438
    },
    {
        "question": " 852万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.492986294109153
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.72万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0077405277141303
    },
    {
        "question": " 746日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.252688582736573
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.55日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.342570851012175
    },
    {
        "question": " 3975万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.656824624560838
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.059837355222166
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.42万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.648517022836082
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.686838028173561
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.5時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.34486489443232
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.534009352644864
    },
    {
        "question": " 538億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5724971810553585
    },
    {
        "question": " 5456万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9587115068268135
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.3分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.14039679245547
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.845927989113248
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.6万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0009286930448769
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.61億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.263664326646498
    },
    {
        "question": " 157秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.41896223488078865
    },
    {
        "question": " 938億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47322880245706966
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.29京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.786581073384363
    },
    {
        "question": " 14兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.590342580295266
    },
    {
        "question": " 211兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.545850142714842
    },
    {
        "question": " 137億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.138247472753124
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.027974944383116
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.5京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.956299199448541
    },
    {
        "question": " 8281兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.981556903591027
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.7兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.084404839282642
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.67兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.891259088517437
    },
    {
        "question": " 1338万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.126355847024505
    },
    {
        "question": " 3239万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.5103631078367155
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.004e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.404487995914572
    },
    {
        "question": " 9630兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.047105139074202
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.620848102775586
    },
    {
        "question": " 8385兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.145370047627743
    },
    {
        "question": " 761億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8816515404978518
    },
    {
        "question": " 2251万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.3523328918380728
    },
    {
        "question": " 6089nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.7845427725061471
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.46年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4352767356997416
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.074283723279022
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.67年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.063447479682743
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.459968082466351
    },
    {
        "question": " 303日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8617841062074945
    },
    {
        "question": " 19万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.437549414485643
    },
    {
        "question": " 578日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.698503222856515
    },
    {
        "question": " 317万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.559049748269447
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7221249058013237
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7771618502077176
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.581315834591992
    },
    {
        "question": " 134兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.406720945345551
    },
    {
        "question": " 2070分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1576796789692092
    },
    {
        "question": " 511万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.930063522063294
    },
    {
        "question": " 106万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.80441790288315
    },
    {
        "question": " 173分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.015767168217301
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.163255216610397
    },
    {
        "question": " 4020億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.10546832720414
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.72億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6339538167161702
    },
    {
        "question": " 13億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.556415065599385
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.7億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.15964716768198
    },
    {
        "question": " 1秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.000897928548226
    },
    {
        "question": " 1874億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7738907538786755
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.65兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.625416877203747
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.9億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.26265119525313
    },
    {
        "question": " 2207万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.565744224281868
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.189159888345001
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.9msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.64241728119363
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.83垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.266830375014842
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.9兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.869097929693968
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.528162768389036
    },
    {
        "question": " 7682万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10733502565065223
    },
    {
        "question": " 3146万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4978016975069963
    },
    {
        "question": " 375億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.574299966408844
    },
    {
        "question": " 1387垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.643331738156636
    },
    {
        "question": " 967京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.04892746942617
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5184667290071765
    },
    {
        "question": " 5872京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.990599693586022
    },
    {
        "question": " 101京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.005459980109695
    },
    {
        "question": " 215万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.3318703695445513
    },
    {
        "question": " 5480億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.73880105406699
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.080250246990574
    },
    {
        "question": " 2633億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.858079343297858
    },
    {
        "question": " 22万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.723576561868297
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.75日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.597947698755841
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.334507814764348
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.776784282120354
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.824123640679331
    },
    {
        "question": " 637時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.36072098672625
    },
    {
        "question": " 123兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.370874408675508
    },
    {
        "question": " 379億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4207951697431405
    },
    {
        "question": " 182億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.482189801331133
    },
    {
        "question": " 9383分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.750477850256058
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.842799343173224
    },
    {
        "question": " 283億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9525031342379684
    },
    {
        "question": " 549万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8031180562548976
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.1万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2507737530371994
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.6万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.076554195447148
    },
    {
        "question": " 2684秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.428843802125115
    },
    {
        "question": " 5471京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.239250289401523
    },
    {
        "question": " 2829億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5151528689657496
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.603423060471352
    },
    {
        "question": " 1491億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.395333534484154
    },
    {
        "question": " 1143億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.058047223615636
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.61msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.935192506119005
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.737961687616874
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.2京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.884130790364792
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.5京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.297786683068649
    },
    {
        "question": " 483兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.905855515451526
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.321302899729899
    },
    {
        "question": " 8643億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.93668724117523
    },
    {
        "question": " 1093京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.539776727394835
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.3京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9789046350123236
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.7垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.691854956222821
    },
    {
        "question": " 421京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.84660186546004
    },
    {
        "question": " 322兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.507730641792897
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.6兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.848683127791894
    },
    {
        "question": " 1929nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.2853459614288001
    },
    {
        "question": " 1762万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.683609749723027
    },
    {
        "question": " 2325日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.746712530725921
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.81日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.922368367064424
    },
    {
        "question": " 679億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.889563401489603
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.2時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15330866699077128
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.1万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.23856425355685
    },
    {
        "question": " 415万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8973979977555224
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.176868604905067
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.92万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5061224151065167
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9923639429946665
    },
    {
        "question": " 3652分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.340705397432243
    },
    {
        "question": " 4030万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10654283256442798
    },
    {
        "question": " 383万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6462158793469694
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.8万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.305725170552754
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5182262173127468
    },
    {
        "question": " 7549秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.877888854267404
    },
    {
        "question": " 498京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.19884428458609
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.53億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.805913523363172
    },
    {
        "question": " 263億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8641410158339715
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.4万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.965074949008784
    },
    {
        "question": " 503億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.701249168165471
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.019391456286359
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.51京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.242677275684962
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.484236727435999
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.786797674358269
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.3億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9720284395095211
    },
    {
        "question": " 12兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.079730616435484
    },
    {
        "question": " 1666万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.22174001853893
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.6京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.120014821427543
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.86垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.831437998102391
    },
    {
        "question": " 165兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.660106861428149
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.9兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9114421698096837
    },
    {
        "question": " 218京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.338632600536943
    },
    {
        "question": " 272万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.4348101045269981
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.5億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.51160025855427
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.740766110909727
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.951828618261763
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.659336231215809
    },
    {
        "question": " 747万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.253702166033857
    },
    {
        "question": " 117日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.225891914332993
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.7日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.899078029386994
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.8億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.485508949039531
    },
    {
        "question": " 558時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3666349232403119
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.27時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5003099542685714
    },
    {
        "question": " 724兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.139175958136708
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.039523345830418
    },
    {
        "question": " 314分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7193319039261747
    },
    {
        "question": " 296分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.248954968680842
    },
    {
        "question": " 4292億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.133899051289006
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.3万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6236671020295914
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.31万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3630778288229295
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.497916368618316
    },
    {
        "question": " 141秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.150196677205621
    },
    {
        "question": " 339兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.03118981308933
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.391478200326585
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.47兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.836810740640502
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.544601074745306
    },
    {
        "question": " 3899万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.590904642918846
    },
    {
        "question": " 9661msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.985032696838383
    },
    {
        "question": " 4154msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.618499346429012
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.579319151379116
    },
    {
        "question": " 8090京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.971455706533861
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.8兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.009490104812316
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.87兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.909618763136725
    },
    {
        "question": " 3828万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5829414758390192
    },
    {
        "question": " 1450万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.161496758000791
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.2万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.504936152262208
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.852e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.268468012129038
    },
    {
        "question": " 2289垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.423163700729306
    },
    {
        "question": " 239兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.822382253740632
    },
    {
        "question": " 800億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1251428294190493
    },
    {
        "question": " 5955兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.774852524367602
    },
    {
        "question": " 7430万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.8709669884690683
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.018450689264421
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.6万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9515257442269527
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.9万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.069757666745067
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.91万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.932764468266688
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.445611341364817
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.922522913640098
    },
    {
        "question": " 2147時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.110010244296724
    },
    {
        "question": " 1598時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.759866371005034
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.9万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.21836115488821028
    },
    {
        "question": " 3226分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.35028349662099334
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.5万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.024408204371034
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.84分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2321078242478007
    },
    {
        "question": " 690兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.34002093898646
    },
    {
        "question": " 387万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6509520480374962
    },
    {
        "question": " 1313億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.561959347173732
    },
    {
        "question": " 3752億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.796147766285825
    },
    {
        "question": " 216秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.334687180477442
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.264646936980405
    },
    {
        "question": " 9511兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4794388512367735
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.32京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.789326295639961
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.766890953053576
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.6兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.916905659860596
    },
    {
        "question": " 3112億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.493103595339438
    },
    {
        "question": " 1051msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.021637479429938
    },
    {
        "question": " 230兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8620427626845528
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.3京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.042521415701872
    },
    {
        "question": " 192兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.727044958878389
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.4兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.865189900036327
    },
    {
        "question": " 954億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.97965121189028
    },
    {
        "question": " 271万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.4328790307486834
    },
    {
        "question": " 523万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.718771422690223
    },
    {
        "question": " 3470垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.041526702286184
    },
    {
        "question": " 712京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.916092974538552
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.5兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4097801518495123
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4082796235317963
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.1兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.644856976048029
    },
    {
        "question": " 674万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.8288641491041726
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.1213630686713367
    },
    {
        "question": " 1029万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.574799966321464
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.2年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.326381368850221
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.503818433144136
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.1日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8135367384650434
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.382222639871443
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.978152110956053
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.326894954205423
    },
    {
        "question": " 175時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8638462602638819
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.3万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.924364064156919
    },
    {
        "question": " 422兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.904181729168183
    },
    {
        "question": " 561万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.590337237352946
    },
    {
        "question": " 4604億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.885018071356795
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0917794154132476
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.934018688924233
    },
    {
        "question": " 2496兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.898381663334329
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.294093694211738
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.524984444378886
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.43682936353195
    },
    {
        "question": " 977兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.491244756588973
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.68億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49181324089261014
    },
    {
        "question": " 601万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22255454386160833
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.46億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6123221593664634
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.313259085377635
    },
    {
        "question": " 100msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.0017463137829665
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.9兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49650207836624993
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.304977132638181
    },
    {
        "question": " 981京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.435372562912596
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2498962498960235
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.75兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.438560093712265
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.31兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.519900054902344
    },
    {
        "question": " 1946usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.289179373067286
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.4垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.832564226656205
    },
    {
        "question": " 2526垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.465928652320777
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.61垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.107700646274719
    },
    {
        "question": " 29京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.68431268599961
    },
    {
        "question": " 128京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.106151040938421
    },
    {
        "question": " 1461兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.164706083160883
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.20973748977109
    },
    {
        "question": " 1447万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.722782460913882
    },
    {
        "question": " 135年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.07266665268884
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.13年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.681280756520119
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.44億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.246669350010481
    },
    {
        "question": " 1317日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.499706742034323
    },
    {
        "question": " 277日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.60034174988707
    },
    {
        "question": " 140日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.082904085289413
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.493290360927751
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.94億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.908456227811461
    },
    {
        "question": " 633万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.579385213275767
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.0312021570988
    },
    {
        "question": " 2199万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6214871978040146
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.4万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.766080877128584
    },
    {
        "question": " 8513万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1519461968027
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.791310822855442
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.978452685432575
    },
    {
        "question": " 1418億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6527352690864214
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2201763984696266
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.1億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.825796193898986
    },
    {
        "question": " 5746秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.981189591420065
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.949960630553066
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.3京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.515857447152673
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.09億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.933393240486565
    },
    {
        "question": " 5623万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9718390185400745
    },
    {
        "question": " 136万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1333447519396973
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.14万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.787814978339776
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.531866065053271
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.44兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6005290753669188
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.92京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.727668023987451
    },
    {
        "question": " 7868億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.11771501376725
    },
    {
        "question": " 113万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.051251245876995366
    },
    {
        "question": " 820億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.914072713209443
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.805e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.757653304101682
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.4垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.799278772837891
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4918093939543533
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.9京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.684075100620141
    },
    {
        "question": " 454億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.65730388031044
    },
    {
        "question": " 1138万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.0560080516775638
    },
    {
        "question": " 7589nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.8801762933464585
    },
    {
        "question": " 61万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.347338030333647
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.8年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.570637354496981
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.33年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.300368826307862
    },
    {
        "question": " 4082日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0485835872254134
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.2万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.145023837988296
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.9万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.153566387490763
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.64日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.68774055583112
    },
    {
        "question": " 1413億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.207623272888274
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.3万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.981845744856646
    },
    {
        "question": " 3403時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.310059209251544
    },
    {
        "question": " 384時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.140880795208947
    },
    {
        "question": " 1223億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.366640432644594
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.51億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5824166604336325
    },
    {
        "question": " 8048分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1275527006461523
    },
    {
        "question": " 531万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.503040237547788
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.55分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.43618106069831
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.1兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.272796552886744
    },
    {
        "question": " 2024万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.369693601236842
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.3万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7914012370190135
    },
    {
        "question": " 238億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.598047479068235
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.34万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.637353599603605
    },
    {
        "question": " 178兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.751725940789583
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.074109474308005
    },
    {
        "question": " 218億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.782780479997696
    },
    {
        "question": " 181万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.479355912174376
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.84万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4535688934707136
    },
    {
        "question": " 887msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.947918389378372
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.9垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9912965486166385
    },
    {
        "question": " 487兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.751163303062727
    },
    {
        "question": " 1987億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7419286498378361
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.2億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5673454308119716
    },
    {
        "question": " 2254兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.35297207348586
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.7億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.410236278398688
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.72垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.328299513140187
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.7京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6163670231510947
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.547761920755697
    },
    {
        "question": " 1995京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.521701427966358
    },
    {
        "question": " 1025兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.010553930263635
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.86兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.5862253484286635
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.0427033087686122
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.08年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.348706432851635
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5438198305273754
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.3万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.073071660403216
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.978563883496995
    },
    {
        "question": " 436億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.696501405376489
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.905721596451065
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.912939674740246
    },
    {
        "question": " 4653億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.947073978036865
    },
    {
        "question": " 311億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.335000860222131
    },
    {
        "question": " 1028万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.233839206068241
    },
    {
        "question": " 163分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9903580681558504
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.1京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.917046729084413
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.302283976921053
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8066725734482683
    },
    {
        "question": " 1046万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.241515311085564
    },
    {
        "question": " 28秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.447676410742223
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.011024538822793
    },
    {
        "question": " 634兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.303530095705935
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.116352353643467
    },
    {
        "question": " 2013兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.747476903453958
    },
    {
        "question": " 1661億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.44231629106357
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.3兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.91883200035143
    },
    {
        "question": " 117万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.068902875724781
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.1424671890279665
    },
    {
        "question": " 2097京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8228623803131105
    },
    {
        "question": " 4354京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.702416819555404
    },
    {
        "question": " 1421京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.596400056453584
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.53兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.625357009507638
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0666581708020804
    },
    {
        "question": " 8793億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.944117921802079
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.96usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.8426144446261468
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.559594489023362
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.316172186857804
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.575219324884763
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.7兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6952649875257206
    },
    {
        "question": " 5748億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7595076403534957
    },
    {
        "question": " 1776億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.249540433363245
    },
    {
        "question": " 881億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.944771202033522
    },
    {
        "question": " 384年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1462148749604175
    },
    {
        "question": " 10万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.942400538617822
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.2年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.613769503840287
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.965229542199417
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.9万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.090417151207805
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.58日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2597081458845802
    },
    {
        "question": " 1739万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2977095103672758
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9919476309687387
    },
    {
        "question": " 2181万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.116736139729392
    },
    {
        "question": " 100万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.556986369608772
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.9兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.07131795588611
    },
    {
        "question": " 3745万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.415104696191147
    },
    {
        "question": " 1894分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4992401082321372
    },
    {
        "question": " 5601万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.52642064716799
    },
    {
        "question": " 147分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.945531251749248
    },
    {
        "question": " 396兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0993182353738336
    },
    {
        "question": " 124億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.157408112432521
    },
    {
        "question": " 1382万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5841441885013827
    },
    {
        "question": " 160秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.42637169244524986
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.8秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.805155315878823
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.78763095895781
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.19兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.567189338783199
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.56859801582141
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.44235280384709585
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.4万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6375169348147844
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.860465796147848
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.1京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.921533289107609
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.460332713759438
    },
    {
        "question": " 3370億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.749533425429159
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4194263503838886
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.291026154054497
    },
    {
        "question": " 253京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9049528612153044
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.92京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0139007805813245
    },
    {
        "question": " 6178兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2345338378886157
    },
    {
        "question": " 3839兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.806105797408804
    },
    {
        "question": " 390億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5909898800520605
    },
    {
        "question": " 2174億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.337227819267621
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.02万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.4805448543141053
    },
    {
        "question": " 276万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.003728181978106
    },
    {
        "question": " 3697年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.510396201398035
    },
    {
        "question": " 9494万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4151484722214995
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.46万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.770989369349245
    },
    {
        "question": " 1028日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.170457079832538
    },
    {
        "question": " 530万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.781837555174458
    },
    {
        "question": " 1061億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.645543448295047
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9194337062787126
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.53時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.298694237885284
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.3時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.471706531275636
    },
    {
        "question": " 176兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.525245470402611
    },
    {
        "question": " 6858億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.677858615009548
    },
    {
        "question": " 138万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.36086659770495
    },
    {
        "question": " 3619万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.336721367034313
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.72分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.718687105206756
    },
    {
        "question": " 164兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7167982440149725
    },
    {
        "question": " 77万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9502458713249218
    },
    {
        "question": " 7011億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.289476125137211
    },
    {
        "question": " 1343万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.349911151445949
    },
    {
        "question": " 343億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.036632429408551825
    },
    {
        "question": " 8417兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.988668056272824
    },
    {
        "question": " 123億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5339223021573796
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5532918986882955
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.1億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.54553990972401
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.3msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.655976315125509
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5765696704013283
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.284772879074235
    },
    {
        "question": " 292兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.909420482465511
    },
    {
        "question": " 356億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.773580380910964
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.165715327618977
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.62兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.559144173924208
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.20015187786353
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.96垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.09900452469976
    },
    {
        "question": " 135兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19325991574407286
    },
    {
        "question": " 240兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8239239153591946
    },
    {
        "question": " 369京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7883513519647
    },
    {
        "question": " 2402億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3805397637858796
    },
    {
        "question": " 6095億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.784939057247386
    },
    {
        "question": " 1721nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.23571827955374935
    },
    {
        "question": " 1471万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.729983094234377
    },
    {
        "question": " 487年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.630285253826013
    },
    {
        "question": " 297年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.972145214781506
    },
    {
        "question": " 1841億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.702828104747999
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.59日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2602971992958176
    },
    {
        "question": " 319億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.560976307104546
    },
    {
        "question": " 129億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.729339707600982
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.69時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.532976015520121
    },
    {
        "question": " 754時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.433658368058763
    },
    {
        "question": " 1115兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.326757453729108
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.7万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1135878086607827
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.360301245116133
    },
    {
        "question": " 2897分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.240067384257177
    },
    {
        "question": " 4486分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.42998144992908
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.787665301144834
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1869714039160857
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.3万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.145248325397829
    },
    {
        "question": " 149秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3955584620888164
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.2秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.969618326314896
    },
    {
        "question": " 3522秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.546809198180522
    },
    {
        "question": " 7401億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3704928649874715
    },
    {
        "question": " 9760億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.052970551193268
    },
    {
        "question": " 1794万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6974656020342829
    },
    {
        "question": " 8546億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.15362361331196
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.2億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.893204737541392
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.20129224954697
    },
    {
        "question": " 438垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.142465015833864
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.9兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1751734725770677
    },
    {
        "question": " 5306億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1684513224121016
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.594285885580507
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4509534052338005
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.009689094902888
    },
    {
        "question": " 4京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10313362752455979
    },
    {
        "question": " 5480兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8022676362389034
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.34兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.36475908420314007
    },
    {
        "question": " 1533兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.407451566571096
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3869803019357221
    },
    {
        "question": " 3649兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.56221422786247
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.5億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.916459038904248
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.068772851273797
    },
    {
        "question": " 5947億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.211997015604073
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6478212585185403
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.494841780506293
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.49万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.478855776207332
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.51万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6030930767701614
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.7時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12137466204662384
    },
    {
        "question": " 148時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.726055184993793
    },
    {
        "question": " 854億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.210958609589862
    },
    {
        "question": " 849億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.770475855011
    },
    {
        "question": " 5770億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.983017465557037
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.2分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6878033083457415
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.06分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.482638013223934
    },
    {
        "question": " 3825兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.083863193196324
    },
    {
        "question": " 360万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6193654929119827
    },
    {
        "question": " 283億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.895548483822758
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.6秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16929056175113755
    },
    {
        "question": " 4236秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.6269749427915405
    },
    {
        "question": " 178秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.249285661153252
    },
    {
        "question": " 301京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9796997773256315
    },
    {
        "question": " 403兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.668549124730142
    },
    {
        "question": " 131兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.559707521282614
    },
    {
        "question": " 216兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.556765043235666
    },
    {
        "question": " 714万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8539507057834896
    },
    {
        "question": " 9341msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.970388519949356
    },
    {
        "question": " 5077msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.705566473280165
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.514737723575356
    },
    {
        "question": " 1506京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.241435078521706
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.49兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.183248986434648
    },
    {
        "question": " 13兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.336563424799335
    },
    {
        "question": " 953兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.979072280859326
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.53万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6556431578544206
    },
    {
        "question": " 99京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4967332172588954
    },
    {
        "question": " 2808京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.511832411289188
    },
    {
        "question": " 2018京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.748549476765909
    },
    {
        "question": " 111兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2672518106268345
    },
    {
        "question": " 5387億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7313591661414813
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.7億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.952950840652493
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.8万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.5999373795367795
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.27年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.297729226124208
    },
    {
        "question": " 100億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.439039793053177
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.558615425984719
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.39日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9637231519114735
    },
    {
        "question": " 242日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.320289145555594
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.201717371583788
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.5兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.480326773689667
    },
    {
        "question": " 232万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.98534020082425
    },
    {
        "question": " 102万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.784679366152652
    },
    {
        "question": " 833億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2001473480323295
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.51兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.583195117779946
    },
    {
        "question": " 3039万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.704564163005657
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.027603964001468
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.27分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.134451696285004
    },
    {
        "question": " 3656億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.064194460236553
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.411767284462769
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.2億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.431433601560467
    },
    {
        "question": " 1518万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.403222568945102
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.79兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0802188375333053
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.61億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7270121584591016
    },
    {
        "question": " 4827万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1274167467250007
    },
    {
        "question": " 3259万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7348754362638763
    },
    {
        "question": " 1787msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2521736111473005
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.080745585679531
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.92msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.593167810138027
    },
    {
        "question": " 288京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.960802859982264
    },
    {
        "question": " 80京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.966781256138215
    },
    {
        "question": " 163京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.656275646445529
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.41億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9554310854056125
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.084498403297186
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.092772161086652
    },
    {
        "question": " 39垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.091798302574978
    },
    {
        "question": " 281京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.511846406991815
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.12京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3530992834028845
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.1京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.217803965674831
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.9億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8565153886244825
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.089235168614453
    },
    {
        "question": " 352万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.5465039311437794
    },
    {
        "question": " 278年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.007073417318184
    },
    {
        "question": " 5508年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.46162004936921
    },
    {
        "question": " 156万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.631134517030704
    },
    {
        "question": " 109日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4193637589834425
    },
    {
        "question": " 107日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.967258590465187
    },
    {
        "question": " 1081億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0915063152916655
    },
    {
        "question": " 817万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5321186828965905
    },
    {
        "question": " 421万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.402639514751119
    },
    {
        "question": " 3844時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.141074860358038
    },
    {
        "question": " 585時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.32372178488523
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5431025588000478
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.926847553342109
    },
    {
        "question": " 356万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7738463260892425
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.003238576122568
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.9分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.509392703655279
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.2兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.828149401125654
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.9億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.173201495544669
    },
    {
        "question": " 101億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.446104929881247
    },
    {
        "question": " 126秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.32238627480063675
    },
    {
        "question": " 942秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.973906596361465
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.4京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7418183690740445
    },
    {
        "question": " 225億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.415810485216147
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.9兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0352806244008335
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.1億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.502010121376339
    },
    {
        "question": " 9604万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.982473726872701
    },
    {
        "question": " 839msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.92382676222716
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.310907227335121
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.63京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3224934539060955
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.2兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7791381054859312
    },
    {
        "question": " 1570兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.639516238089173
    },
    {
        "question": " 102兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.231878481334052
    },
    {
        "question": " 4920億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.691967650302909
    },
    {
        "question": " 1255usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.09878748822636951
    },
    {
        "question": " 4030京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1065060882618747
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4713204281928
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.45垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.09168956850776
    },
    {
        "question": " 3593億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.777367462864248
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.4京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.815692598545935
    },
    {
        "question": " 7049億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.848124034411909
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.004123396237327
    },
    {
        "question": " 1618年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.929695208514344
    },
    {
        "question": " 72万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2949786513488366
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.09万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.230558541036889
    },
    {
        "question": " 599日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.935880061711439
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.8日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.854540765198516
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12873932349642958
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.4億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.08765881473011
    },
    {
        "question": " 185万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.046303317942359
    },
    {
        "question": " 2536万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6835374741036102
    },
    {
        "question": " 1905分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12147809827897427
    },
    {
        "question": " 636億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.025364372432508
    },
    {
        "question": " 530分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.50205455426195
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.81095810108095
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.3兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.01994080729205
    },
    {
        "question": " 302億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.543486667456781
    },
    {
        "question": " 7712万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.330870236900085
    },
    {
        "question": " 313秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7168302875019561
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.32900238841397
    },
    {
        "question": " 2333秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.36800208086203
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.4兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3783392151370717
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.2京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.65703142486581
    },
    {
        "question": " 2836万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8964820436638632
    },
    {
        "question": " 2247万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.573430778471286
    },
    {
        "question": " 2659msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.42474627463463754
    },
    {
        "question": " 2709msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.432814796270003
    },
    {
        "question": " 403京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.106632576701858
    },
    {
        "question": " 1701京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.294120769474258
    },
    {
        "question": " 826京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.360603618706886
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.444769870265224
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.9億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9953427645585315
    },
    {
        "question": " 189万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.2771946737278035
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6072942381819075
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.92京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6570377765758666
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.37垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.24751241985558
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.43京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.868254029662493
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.030160161174998
    },
    {
        "question": " 3280万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5158529577789737
    },
    {
        "question": " 6951nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.8420621882402202
    },
    {
        "question": " 338万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.091282832169316
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.31億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.301701450227103
    },
    {
        "question": " 470日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.830564895523427
    },
    {
        "question": " 4377万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.698685781627604
    },
    {
        "question": " 134億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.74680565670282
    },
    {
        "question": " 261万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.194046949775338
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.854304944490864
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.47967400992751
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.894445631138959
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.23万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.730680555774124
    },
    {
        "question": " 274万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.215751510093275
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.791052505640357
    },
    {
        "question": " 403兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1059901985659675
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.304720417692649
    },
    {
        "question": " 109万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.481905387461598
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.31万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.946581123671732
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.7秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.79723034061418
    },
    {
        "question": " 1405京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.649019151692931
    },
    {
        "question": " 2125兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.390867876159507
    },
    {
        "question": " 1236万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5356131346537674
    },
    {
        "question": " 166億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.442207708785166
    },
    {
        "question": " 9682msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.985950909931187
    },
    {
        "question": " 4511msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.654298938490728
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.05msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.703019574525689
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.9垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.61094529351859
    },
    {
        "question": " 2439億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4507233448709236
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.783443289482151
    },
    {
        "question": " 406兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.830048891331344
    },
    {
        "question": " 764億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8832033149919205
    },
    {
        "question": " 706億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.848899760054078
    },
    {
        "question": " 365万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.56226495634995
    },
    {
        "question": " 4958京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1964788094305128
    },
    {
        "question": " 417兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6838971518795012
    },
    {
        "question": " 1173兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5130460825281165
    },
    {
        "question": " 1062億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24804169657067443
    },
    {
        "question": " 24兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3794005902026525
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.5億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.8720814015162563
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.417437240560172
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.51万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.872568301758802
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.71年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.290463905394401
    },
    {
        "question": " 1576億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.635238365321397
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.22日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7266240384325293
    },
    {
        "question": " 6895日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.99689646942228
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.93万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5236660419030303
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.18億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.476034792460182
    },
    {
        "question": " 4708万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.451024418771096
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.71918748978917
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.5万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2062478743246854
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.8億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.330586760716445
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5073350761869406
    },
    {
        "question": " 99分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7740000054054756
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.845841514613667
    },
    {
        "question": " 756億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.379803325095879
    },
    {
        "question": " 3582億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.617625414728646
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5351844682514075
    },
    {
        "question": " 161億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.429974178135472
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.79秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.578764961749371
    },
    {
        "question": " 1873億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7738052641147275
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.412333618895046
    },
    {
        "question": " 348億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9856480699208454
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.69339759483847
    },
    {
        "question": " 2204億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.34320477176012
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.2msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.833632449143246
    },
    {
        "question": " 7192京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.358045900323627
    },
    {
        "question": " 771京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9504879868723
    },
    {
        "question": " 6191億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.235436348536739
    },
    {
        "question": " 464億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8884250735960904
    },
    {
        "question": " 114兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.057382838558695
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.62億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.821153413924857
    },
    {
        "question": " 952京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4798950949587297
    },
    {
        "question": " 136垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.196299225463083
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.3兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8628429726802622
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.6兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1543148763224025
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.3京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.684200124657275
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.284265027783064
    },
    {
        "question": " 271万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.433556808550551
    },
    {
        "question": " 1033年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.576397971823606
    },
    {
        "question": " 1033万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.451859841940841
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.24万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.007745280196869
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.28101367432337
    },
    {
        "question": " 46億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.719858212984258
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.97万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.396011436412072
    },
    {
        "question": " 1978時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.852484358706747
    },
    {
        "question": " 205万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5901227391028752
    },
    {
        "question": " 5208億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.558286242091496
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.41億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.754514116369689
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.35分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.148366704350412
    },
    {
        "question": " 7460億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.373958178354296
    },
    {
        "question": " 1610億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.270316321372204
    },
    {
        "question": " 793万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.343203336194022
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.6万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8609832781850226
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.21万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.6243623593240395
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.97京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.796598957355364
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.8京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.401697869634063
    },
    {
        "question": " 597兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.21971061811442
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4589543741293911
    },
    {
        "question": " 1505msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17750398315925398
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.49msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.7394103667704637
    },
    {
        "question": " 5921兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2735963432282236
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.12京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6780859416389085
    },
    {
        "question": " 59億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.214599465544284
    },
    {
        "question": " 4298億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.85507256366048
    },
    {
        "question": " 254億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.404300383008667
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.55兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.550623308327953
    },
    {
        "question": " 190usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.277613371721218
    },
    {
        "question": " 983垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.493737822486114
    },
    {
        "question": " 2524垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.465630702263232
    },
    {
        "question": " 2293兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8041057184526688
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.24525630114629
    },
    {
        "question": " 121京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.083882437830223
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.64兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.984088557324588
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.68万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.670034349090086
    },
    {
        "question": " 825年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.478654825262153
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.7万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.38435441876299
    },
    {
        "question": " 745年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.592764489515819
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.55032869029467
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.4万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.858755136622876
    },
    {
        "question": " 1357万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.512782172090922
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.9日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9136675341137135
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.52日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.591201871774487
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.29万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6904529874407894
    },
    {
        "question": " 3306時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.139094101992204
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7864906738800956
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.99時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.1578138875236
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.385101149688654
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.1兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.333127502297696
    },
    {
        "question": " 4912分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9130672226030176
    },
    {
        "question": " 623分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.572681265619211
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5769120408981965
    },
    {
        "question": " 9487万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.040641237347941
    },
    {
        "question": " 723万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3028283205787314
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.582413587955905
    },
    {
        "question": " 144秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.158622632463919
    },
    {
        "question": " 7954秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.900564906023448
    },
    {
        "question": " 146京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.665975279186409
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.7兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6277743978325265
    },
    {
        "question": " 764億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.326678115210013
    },
    {
        "question": " 259億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.634358384642491
    },
    {
        "question": " 457万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6600815732217997
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.1万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.232577504124091
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.7msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.776294562525133
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.6京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.254288058318481
    },
    {
        "question": " 4647京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.730635411769413
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.35兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3098326484184994
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.51413318204841
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3451802022941823
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.36兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.80356159866806
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.76usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.4407164227960205
    },
    {
        "question": " 1054垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.524220026717751
    },
    {
        "question": " 5217兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7809574363188008
    },
    {
        "question": " 230兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.805853998956769
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.548585127946252
    },
    {
        "question": " 136兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.132248494594194
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.42億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.8072473364712036
    },
    {
        "question": " 230万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.3617678770214643
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.582718082078752
    },
    {
        "question": " 795年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.620768253631654
    },
    {
        "question": " 112億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.487088869098252
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.466185015105229
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.281038151964552
    },
    {
        "question": " 156億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.251114056251666
    },
    {
        "question": " 6797万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.452107545192275
    },
    {
        "question": " 7486万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.652396543741432
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.900248732698754
    },
    {
        "question": " 131兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.395416047903735
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.48億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.770201199358647
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.6万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.211087347101974
    },
    {
        "question": " 1627分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.989405007314721
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.57989877870048
    },
    {
        "question": " 157万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2590212131141254
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.783624816309548
    },
    {
        "question": " 377億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.798502360632343
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.02秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.700411380567139
    },
    {
        "question": " 462秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.664904570313716
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.1秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.491260336475436
    },
    {
        "question": " 546兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.238114940966375
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.095729820069643
    },
    {
        "question": " 142億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.597345733498888
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.26億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8517441942858435
    },
    {
        "question": " 313億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.495953116549493
    },
    {
        "question": " 812兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4107995196025203
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.3京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.581466147130838
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.5京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.111014636133838
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.2兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.548570764272517
    },
    {
        "question": " 175億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.243903242932214
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.285648300447949
    },
    {
        "question": " 1371usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.137179321244716
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.56垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.052509514437441
    },
    {
        "question": " 1305垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.178950533062388
    },
    {
        "question": " 6437京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.252364928947401
    },
    {
        "question": " 225兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.574602744520312
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.051585075107931644
    },
    {
        "question": " 653億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.815164265441992
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.11万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.4924507996221525
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.756926163562947
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.71年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.375259167692417
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.4万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7472622743189437
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.9日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.884320860228925
    },
    {
        "question": " 793日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.057595495902603
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.104647594957811
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3830016330136876
    },
    {
        "question": " 1175億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.689707349101374
    },
    {
        "question": " 65時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.591055303555659
    },
    {
        "question": " 195時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.84654790214698
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.5時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.026078515886866
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.7億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7051278285008973
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.055118815000395
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.634800007045241
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.9京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.80010011219795
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.27071509781192993
    },
    {
        "question": " 37万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0117331433865315
    },
    {
        "question": " 6450万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.031381054212524
    },
    {
        "question": " 157万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.194745456598776
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.75633552921056
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.122731250224932
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.4兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.96712614790416
    },
    {
        "question": " 120万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3001574259351112
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.44万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6473809778275528
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.4msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.496275373504096
    },
    {
        "question": " 209垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.822076010391179
    },
    {
        "question": " 970京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.050116626625025
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.643743544684729
    },
    {
        "question": " 1809兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.479305595375671
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.174348340539114
    },
    {
        "question": " 1813億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.258360056373878
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.052905188807101
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.7垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.943615770028816
    },
    {
        "question": " 434兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7013698564121595
    },
    {
        "question": " 6265兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.240607715258345
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.437249971318093
    },
    {
        "question": " 108億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0345047837029453
    },
    {
        "question": " 115兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.059944432537007
    },
    {
        "question": " 1417億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.151403727337826
    },
    {
        "question": " 2633年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.982821915102728
    },
    {
        "question": " 3年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1982065940829205
    },
    {
        "question": " 515万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.149827734151291
    },
    {
        "question": " 214日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7098687365143226
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.19日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.792967836807405
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.1億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.765337575801993
    },
    {
        "question": " 441時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2638484766635716
    },
    {
        "question": " 518時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.492429165792373
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.4兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.964079078727929
    },
    {
        "question": " 539億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.572926002717761
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3118720382632985
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.001285985681274
    },
    {
        "question": " 73分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.641586742487339
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.4分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.559035182493856
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.753116031995464
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.137059761108805
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.9兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.341062166454005
    },
    {
        "question": " 257万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.631143485974521
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5038948014547895
    },
    {
        "question": " 1219兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.149341956137912
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.593780508644914
    },
    {
        "question": " 802万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1261473521148053
    },
    {
        "question": " 579万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.762464140649464
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.060811450174273
    },
    {
        "question": " 156京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.693365480592924
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.6京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.883340637235931
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.87兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.031822393752006
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.537229540304397
    },
    {
        "question": " 123億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.090818691302347
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.229056627852568
    },
    {
        "question": " 24京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8820402560230378
    },
    {
        "question": " 6486京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8755054376108795
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.3京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.06000700420295
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.2京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.846805929823823
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.9兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8626605902090905
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.25億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.351560285614082
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.38万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.5295140298457222
    },
    {
        "question": " 212年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.887733452239208
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.85年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.397936656317554
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.2年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.08035808799194
    },
    {
        "question": " 36万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.993882595829569
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.65日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9427038512569217
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.438869410087786
    },
    {
        "question": " 216万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.392501970172669
    },
    {
        "question": " 862億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.55527157149692
    },
    {
        "question": " 169時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.78455819684617
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.527661526517107
    },
    {
        "question": " 465億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.509376623524213
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.5万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9890790210088225
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.7万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.772385936259355
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.8兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.23175993288534
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.5兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.660377022114446
    },
    {
        "question": " 8570秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3766936987000846
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.41906222424456
    },
    {
        "question": " 1948秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.289677981216003
    },
    {
        "question": " 5605秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.748562976757826
    },
    {
        "question": " 577京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.26221572524192
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.500414131908204
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.1兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0567392104600355
    },
    {
        "question": " 976億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.211384929047876
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.6億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.854717086378619
    },
    {
        "question": " 8770msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.942980363438375
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.95msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.951645038256541
    },
    {
        "question": " 87京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.440815910395688
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.3京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.697102648155471
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.21京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0683599164313
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.534754893414437
    },
    {
        "question": " 1680億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.225411912108085
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.15万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.910914314118074
    },
    {
        "question": " 283万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.451261590911837
    },
    {
        "question": " 685京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3371694962251754
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.9京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6750287231262946
    },
    {
        "question": " 176兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6891437916134266
    },
    {
        "question": " 5255京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.942453359112697
    },
    {
        "question": " 3439兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.536492562562984
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.6億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.551755256293264
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.190449219903367
    },
    {
        "question": " 937万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.534156389528135
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.9年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.741038813078349
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.5年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.476584034621421
    },
    {
        "question": " 2477日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8315598490710552
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.99日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2828490733060813
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.77万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.148143665554565
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.02億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6613040075297105
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.2万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.465839743882702
    },
    {
        "question": " 420時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.401601591165315
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.55時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.434339686735727
    },
    {
        "question": " 286万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7364200247031893
    },
    {
        "question": " 2551万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.24839791169221
    },
    {
        "question": " 4096分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8342619486346645
    },
    {
        "question": " 789万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.675434565997648
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.062251797459357
    },
    {
        "question": " 2074兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.818017305558563
    },
    {
        "question": " 388億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.652633164368752
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.661903518363967
    },
    {
        "question": " 139万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.363518951017746
    },
    {
        "question": " 358秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.553425221743465
    },
    {
        "question": " 546秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.736827039450283
    },
    {
        "question": " 924兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.46687364676161
    },
    {
        "question": " 210億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3859725680111508
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.39兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.82179166006487
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.21兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.846323571394094
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.11億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.95945441721109
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.840504905142792
    },
    {
        "question": " 523msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.718794529748692
    },
    {
        "question": " 6880兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3388106103651807
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.6兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.682871433220013
    },
    {
        "question": " 6902億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.282659722270898
    },
    {
        "question": " 717億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0773641965976326
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.4兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3494469257186985
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.01億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.954706951852799
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.1万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.432680094901922
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.157e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.119949008100194
    },
    {
        "question": " 854垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.99473055932863
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.63垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.194567820581845
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.22京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.568469978268008
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.7兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.696055147160436
    },
    {
        "question": " 485億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.685484257645834
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.92万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.4649755573207068
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.8年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.630525433280428
    },
    {
        "question": " 197億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.732724106262817
    },
    {
        "question": " 4468日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.030295614173217
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.8億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.771722492635803
    },
    {
        "question": " 261時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.035910435218379
    },
    {
        "question": " 500兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.978432625374335
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.94万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1298258751681967
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.25万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.138559709973615
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.51分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.323604612263331
    },
    {
        "question": " 464億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.167470012224997
    },
    {
        "question": " 100万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0650887345949156
    },
    {
        "question": " 147億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.611519371591719
    },
    {
        "question": " 501億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.922102730849684
    },
    {
        "question": " 583秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.765655139249468
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.1京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.114342418620056
    },
    {
        "question": " 5400兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.795886928981655
    },
    {
        "question": " 179兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6958792500670565
    },
    {
        "question": " 863万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1578877797189087
    },
    {
        "question": " 6116msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.786480697259504
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.7992050985197734
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.08msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.849809069283355
    },
    {
        "question": " 9971京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.499938492235328
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.3兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.623190789580004
    },
    {
        "question": " 1252億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5411638451478837
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.93兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.172548883099522
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.54313676188945
    },
    {
        "question": " 1025万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.0108541646701745
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.95垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.401449577433211
    },
    {
        "question": " 223垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.412299281721866
    },
    {
        "question": " 474兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1194111499777515
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4828791115955475
    },
    {
        "question": " 144億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1575087071017232
    },
    {
        "question": " 9798万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.9911188789973433
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.63万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.6655151932911016
    },
    {
        "question": " 313億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.933773236155618
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.24日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8900851847246336
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.41日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8030588517131116
    },
    {
        "question": " 2631日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.356627666120541
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.92億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5229269498582525
    },
    {
        "question": " 896万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.571974951963005
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.7億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.706019627639494
    },
    {
        "question": " 2289分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2012953361652814
    },
    {
        "question": " 201億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.524622206664985
    },
    {
        "question": " 43分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4115342951841257
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.8京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.819196762222813
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18053107629294574
    },
    {
        "question": " 385億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.029633109293673
    },
    {
        "question": " 864億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.158131170158178
    },
    {
        "question": " 983秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.992434322657738
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.82秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.893435760609478
    },
    {
        "question": " 9661兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.486209964130634
    },
    {
        "question": " 7796兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.955355310929412
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.555609192579102
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.4兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.056915258844716
    },
    {
        "question": " 2203msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3430099360678285
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.77万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.761332866158881
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.259839639904185
    },
    {
        "question": " 110京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.54379292805549
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.35垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.929675504949868
    },
    {
        "question": " 113兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4964881448524
    },
    {
        "question": " 15京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.39796525142317
    },
    {
        "question": " 138億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.140786288847544
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.1万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.4933789243950963
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.8万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.738944091350287
    },
    {
        "question": " 622京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.294730946494652
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.65京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4863031795052812
    },
    {
        "question": " 26垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.859100181539123
    },
    {
        "question": " 1119兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.270516028209688
    },
    {
        "question": " 100京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.002165279664764
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.71兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.432274933078338
    },
    {
        "question": " 2482万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.39471725891665
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.4年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.157872366185194
    },
    {
        "question": " 493年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.413506847055384
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.6年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.166874009533085
    },
    {
        "question": " 309万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.927768835381377
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.42712899163569
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.7日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.711236537630038
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.33日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.663046652012401
    },
    {
        "question": " 516万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7699238677170435
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.03万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.524630745839893
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.21万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.692612170550881
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.539381245250798
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.56時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.107469182076898
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.5兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.74869759170988
    },
    {
        "question": " 15万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0165886693470645
    },
    {
        "question": " 120万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.300819928716208
    },
    {
        "question": " 247分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.169989383960386
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.88京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.960027393350082
    },
    {
        "question": " 692万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9037356927756444
    },
    {
        "question": " 104万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.460482249744821
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.270743709953341
    },
    {
        "question": " 232万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.366044246176115
    },
    {
        "question": " 658秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.81809195028394
    },
    {
        "question": " 2958兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9721659762282036
    },
    {
        "question": " 669億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8888545789448736
    },
    {
        "question": " 810兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.352449430771692
    },
    {
        "question": " 3528万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7693957853772355
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.32億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.635092555448848
    },
    {
        "question": " 35兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04472902510624377
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.4京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.929001644570092
    },
    {
        "question": " 111億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4897205857012854
    },
    {
        "question": " 1767兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.469197029406137
    },
    {
        "question": " 645万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8092611722737653
    },
    {
        "question": " 1987usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.2981772316072384
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.435300908332332
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.024e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.105890540866335
    },
    {
        "question": " 5254垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.784028009499627
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.51京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.097904019336433
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.428759145661812
    },
    {
        "question": " 228億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3570586980635502
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.06兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.485769478069265
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.53億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.402498252830105
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.6万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.895815017104265
    },
    {
        "question": " 881年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.665563340366177
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.5万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3747817235892685
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.602757753382763
    },
    {
        "question": " 2665日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.584124405923003
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.94036522006191
    },
    {
        "question": " 154万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2441163048523127
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.44万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3552956892501373
    },
    {
        "question": " 3743万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.351328951941444
    },
    {
        "question": " 8048万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1850579089516007
    },
    {
        "question": " 2575億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.252453087820014
    },
    {
        "question": " 5203分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9380778032271706
    },
    {
        "question": " 416分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.397734169113525
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.22万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.403364916066048
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.2分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.123923294632753
    },
    {
        "question": " 705億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3493772059749705
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.7兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.975871454750017
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.71094370416296
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.08万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0059918072360423
    },
    {
        "question": " 215京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8337182323481045
    },
    {
        "question": " 317兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.565127107713588
    },
    {
        "question": " 4913兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.135078187551848
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.77兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.112232150320562
    },
    {
        "question": " 134万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.126745800538627
    },
    {
        "question": " 479msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.680315834032946
    },
    {
        "question": " 3566兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0534317818918355
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.193141108768242
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.35京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.246814046452049
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.1兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.545736252663868
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.072739023124926
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.3億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.625897199455318
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.403e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.233808122481861
    },
    {
        "question": " 1975兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.358973885606578
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.7兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3557847822568092
    },
    {
        "question": " 169兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4508796147311283
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.5兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9889837245647914
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.3兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.36798876576089
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.3億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.674424975232178
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.906182721585166
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.600530418738543
    },
    {
        "question": " 879万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3815425031245265
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.938071737949557
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.8億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6574218268835
    },
    {
        "question": " 446億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.269090399555953
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.4万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.288307760757803
    },
    {
        "question": " 13万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.668759086543638
    },
    {
        "question": " 419万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9013793939976356
    },
    {
        "question": " 357億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.394661576815086
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.465203533046476
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.786735737723719
    },
    {
        "question": " 1103分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.820702925711859
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.006507718894913
    },
    {
        "question": " 9871万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49556668703070184
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.4兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.600634387952269
    },
    {
        "question": " 2875億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.902298168838817
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.5億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.116918585646037
    },
    {
        "question": " 1028秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.011962708993588
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.363680390004166
    },
    {
        "question": " 890京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.45038011352803
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.9億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7350299796211577
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.31億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.363074792656924
    },
    {
        "question": " 831億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.141425160351048
    },
    {
        "question": " 1952億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.29045883547972
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.78京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.263353405596919
    },
    {
        "question": " 253京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.466459627736485
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.12兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2959325797704775
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.77億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9003660086648435
    },
    {
        "question": " 1906億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.280218093910407
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.17万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.9623315323163348
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.06京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10978748071555522
    },
    {
        "question": " 156垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.257447749239628
    },
    {
        "question": " 3535京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.992139252333592
    },
    {
        "question": " 2454億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6116405756225629
    },
    {
        "question": " 62億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.792422866611544
    },
    {
        "question": " 215億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.33325762351312
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.3595276769132187
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.54年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9677310718351957
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.222566502313827
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.81年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.169412774685891
    },
    {
        "question": " 261億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.853511101640656
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.59日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3619770388655006
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.1万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.004359878434508
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.54万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4618523327052826
    },
    {
        "question": " 1878時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8934105190247474
    },
    {
        "question": " 31万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.26942624343653
    },
    {
        "question": " 1586兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.479780413606193
    },
    {
        "question": " 1249万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.938287123381221
    },
    {
        "question": " 371万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.79158327249333
    },
    {
        "question": " 238分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.154066505905249
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.4分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.2316316514201855
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.2分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.723851624921249
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.92億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9663555682707736
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.8億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.381453717585803
    },
    {
        "question": " 16万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6474008812552987
    },
    {
        "question": " 676億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.051846024562687
    },
    {
        "question": " 1393秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.143841500204265
    },
    {
        "question": " 1226秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.088538983547275
    },
    {
        "question": " 1320兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.621777628083059
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.38億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9314338914025222
    },
    {
        "question": " 641兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.25036818291686
    },
    {
        "question": " 880億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.16653218760619
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.032147031916365
    },
    {
        "question": " 196msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.292414188638856
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.4兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.01221010756606522
    },
    {
        "question": " 5213億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7805695466499263
    },
    {
        "question": " 274億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8820614649529457
    },
    {
        "question": " 200億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5232209005228845
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2015096876206264
    },
    {
        "question": " 7431億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.871021230366052
    },
    {
        "question": " 1594usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.202542760668276
    },
    {
        "question": " 5938垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.274862700993998
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.3垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.765193399512649
    },
    {
        "question": " 4877兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1318239132046966
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.02兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5268473074838351
    },
    {
        "question": " 688兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.837537988102995
    },
    {
        "question": " 6730万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.8279873575747985
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.1万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.7931251189853135
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.2年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.788908687663791
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.71263082056388
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.631151220955126
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.5万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.732459215858574
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.5日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0589723795167245
    },
    {
        "question": " 1977日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.232476582007322
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.31億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.782605133548418
    },
    {
        "question": " 393時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.213740562816037
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.620115868423584
    },
    {
        "question": " 1560億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.472573870984442
    },
    {
        "question": " 54億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.573903559746012
    },
    {
        "question": " 243万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.606698007690063
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.78分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7218261874192162
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8546602562252514
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.9兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.362032784678677
    },
    {
        "question": " 133億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.567572149063218
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.5秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12241559964161763
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.72秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.940723030947912
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.4京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.348840065598845
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.32億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0329481408627461
    },
    {
        "question": " 1640万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6585829983533831
    },
    {
        "question": " 981億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.213686072011418
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.69万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8857187660661923
    },
    {
        "question": " 104兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5190122767431515
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.9兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.855013111126896
    },
    {
        "question": " 1980兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.740347541941362
    },
    {
        "question": " 1142億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2796640144777167
    },
    {
        "question": " 981億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.991495299786002
    },
    {
        "question": " 394億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.595395118275089
    },
    {
        "question": " 3129usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.495379442258225
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.7垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.477613198732759
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.8垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.895045829354796
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.628267438071392
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.8京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.495452823684543
    },
    {
        "question": " 365兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.562305831940631
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.29億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.7233554340335275
    },
    {
        "question": " 6352億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.802912096555216
    },
    {
        "question": " 1645年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.778541744587869
    },
    {
        "question": " 5098万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.14512817753787
    },
    {
        "question": " 317日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.88128189368547
    },
    {
        "question": " 743万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9285681656403586
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.3億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.168133861532286
    },
    {
        "question": " 174時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.019691644849889
    },
    {
        "question": " 392万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.872842426280257
    },
    {
        "question": " 1851億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.108939821969223
    },
    {
        "question": " 4030万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.827119468545145
    },
    {
        "question": " 1064万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.805188309596396
    },
    {
        "question": " 4258万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13045432940004154
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.7兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.970231243621544
    },
    {
        "question": " 551万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.184738399760587
    },
    {
        "question": " 5579万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.968397694347152
    },
    {
        "question": " 669秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.825234984207053
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.31秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.968768874203606
    },
    {
        "question": " 5666億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2544825491776501
    },
    {
        "question": " 126億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.163809482003789
    },
    {
        "question": " 741万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31326316884204397
    },
    {
        "question": " 150兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.398435311899952
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.8億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.967475840573921
    },
    {
        "question": " 4306京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.135322991397948
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.163917426061495
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.5億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4370330605602579
    },
    {
        "question": " 8634万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1580788990226345
    },
    {
        "question": " 139億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1433172415851836
    },
    {
        "question": " 937万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.9715519060187052
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.7万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.713369901230944
    },
    {
        "question": " 322京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.009608660138821
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1654424332463655
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.41京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9761403834297804
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.99垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.697572764587969
    },
    {
        "question": " 4兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6017224152619622
    },
    {
        "question": " 175億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.243956789775095
    },
    {
        "question": " 5457nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.7369920807918284
    },
    {
        "question": " 8352年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.864273205450073
    },
    {
        "question": " 206万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7510930333719275
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.3万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.765274442618161
    },
    {
        "question": " 227日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.514744177080243
    },
    {
        "question": " 669億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8826517120800546
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.9時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2622070340587823
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.88万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.615740369325932
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.024796809052901
    },
    {
        "question": " 769時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.442067767282445
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.941720635433809
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.996877122659244
    },
    {
        "question": " 134万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.348891004920965
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.841848376323522
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.799178218282417
    },
    {
        "question": " 341兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.596178811625052
    },
    {
        "question": " 1753億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6875254110125635
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.81万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9858401063739937
    },
    {
        "question": " 1911兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.78238770117647
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.097374334656037
    },
    {
        "question": " 190兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.723299956467901
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.8兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.421522544871138
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.142414046520603
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.1垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.192219750814807
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2673551852253728
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4613684557145175
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.406108900894623
    },
    {
        "question": " 265兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.423129388180065
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.17億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.789944182566556
    },
    {
        "question": " 277usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.442664870010676
    },
    {
        "question": " 3413垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.034322768557436
    },
    {
        "question": " 993兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0604097526421363
    },
    {
        "question": " 1949兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7334533647535886
    },
    {
        "question": " 330兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7399585746337447
    },
    {
        "question": " 348億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5416505180972995
    },
    {
        "question": " 3272万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5148070196463337
    },
    {
        "question": " 692億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.840057132017081
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.5年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2568705785777015
    },
    {
        "question": " 507日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14281675142366557
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.51万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.812420228352906
    },
    {
        "question": " 265億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.480728549750646
    },
    {
        "question": " 1296時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7324979794884565
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6720267626109484
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.8024979764472215
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.97兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7522916732956
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.04億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.324020086155972
    },
    {
        "question": " 690万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.060388573765464
    },
    {
        "question": " 6119分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.564820056777805
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6703607655889954
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.69兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.49258109158475
    },
    {
        "question": " 160億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6475339880394815
    },
    {
        "question": " 2611秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.638646196268957
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.332872833091788
    },
    {
        "question": " 5247京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.221131121891508
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.1兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.698221282552394
    },
    {
        "question": " 198億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.74101975858712
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.1兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.091536600603176
    },
    {
        "question": " 1188万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0747442181987505
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.228761128395544
    },
    {
        "question": " 233兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8683299725587834
    },
    {
        "question": " 1667兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.285341600304639
    },
    {
        "question": " 232兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.808510768347849
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3619829423762542
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.84億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5843145328837966
    },
    {
        "question": " 2980億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.474224735182933
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.196658230653265
    },
    {
        "question": " 7057垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.349812213108478
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.17垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9756210199713164
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.627256694233967
    },
    {
        "question": " 327京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.735871246942782
    },
    {
        "question": " 690億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8386095720811513
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.1億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.71707534546984
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.183182665707796
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.54万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4935250117267
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.1年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.226878100681976
    },
    {
        "question": " 213年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.82644524179156
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.26億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.066610155241781
    },
    {
        "question": " 111万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4247645248519785
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.3日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.804876678766336
    },
    {
        "question": " 8414万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.982481900507003
    },
    {
        "question": " 1884万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.894829644162493
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.697531382957127
    },
    {
        "question": " 6928万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.119958306053673
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.83万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6759699702922337
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.74万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0505156504724553
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.5万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.090165338029103
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.988367761565426
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5470507321230511
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.2億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.688321849228777
    },
    {
        "question": " 3769億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.019899526894234
    },
    {
        "question": " 535億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.950294901289293
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.3京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.137561228483856
    },
    {
        "question": " 952兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.042193494836997
    },
    {
        "question": " 4765万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1217719687781502
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.530104073879897
    },
    {
        "question": " 3824億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.582544875775733
    },
    {
        "question": " 6857msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.836146199166149
    },
    {
        "question": " 1267msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.102727152435646
    },
    {
        "question": " 4004兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1037158517908106
    },
    {
        "question": " 3263京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.57706415490809
    },
    {
        "question": " 7048兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.291758941724312
    },
    {
        "question": " 1070兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.251390158939186
    },
    {
        "question": " 1146万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0592089237952418
    },
    {
        "question": " 917億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.962151012900315
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.81usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.448619331418137
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.351e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.631954859715452
    },
    {
        "question": " 263垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.48365585798338
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5311166534237834
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.396312490409315
    },
    {
        "question": " 9808兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.991567101988241
    },
    {
        "question": " 79兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.897534339253327
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.8億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.849987577456914
    },
    {
        "question": " 1427年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.716829946154079
    },
    {
        "question": " 3510年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.487831712847186
    },
    {
        "question": " 131年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.61509582473354
    },
    {
        "question": " 186億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.706972643260224
    },
    {
        "question": " 106万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.404040820558415
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.56日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.817685095112262
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.939082380369275
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.02万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9040710906222182
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.7時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5475348337668406
    },
    {
        "question": " 984時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.771316574100625
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.53時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.212773834105468
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.9万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11757761009807188
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.6万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.594388858008072
    },
    {
        "question": " 26万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6361590992103032
    },
    {
        "question": " 755万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.65620829597519
    },
    {
        "question": " 18兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.756673083745493
    },
    {
        "question": " 332億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.584866778439915
    },
    {
        "question": " 7471秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.317103893447197
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.5秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17861630249430216
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.91万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.690950345470395
    },
    {
        "question": " 4241秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.627457618860731
    },
    {
        "question": " 8358兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.423326270132453
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.1兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.856670668746875
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.69京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.874255169940119
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.2万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8370611859292154
    },
    {
        "question": " 6799msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8324497145033394
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.93万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.69283511299646
    },
    {
        "question": " 741msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.869807839103599
    },
    {
        "question": " 8386京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4247740543638585
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.47兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4570418746743996
    },
    {
        "question": " 412京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.058796743635604
    },
    {
        "question": " 559億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.969118454627735
    },
    {
        "question": " 471億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.672793829693833
    },
    {
        "question": " 538万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7310731424633015
    },
    {
        "question": " 1192垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.57740988004244
    },
    {
        "question": " 48京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7446818894840694
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.613555628918603
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.672187314291758
    },
    {
        "question": " 2813億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4491868894869393
    },
    {
        "question": " 211万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.32458214658869333
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.66億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.752830156610069
    },
    {
        "question": " 2572万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.972545540265266
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.55万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.686865462264267
    },
    {
        "question": " 538年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.451574251561619
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.637542368265622
    },
    {
        "question": " 277万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8797657239165586
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.8日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1709604760866474
    },
    {
        "question": " 149万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.332446684220477
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.15万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7692249174784083
    },
    {
        "question": " 436万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.259126578909074
    },
    {
        "question": " 7929万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.677371767652566
    },
    {
        "question": " 105時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.577058409028312
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.8億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.636533021579158
    },
    {
        "question": " 5469万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5795669482683685
    },
    {
        "question": " 12億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3006801401757135
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.1分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.432403978562053
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.659953742457503
    },
    {
        "question": " 8847万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0103115046060047
    },
    {
        "question": " 550億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1838767121354286
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.3億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.569449721739774
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7711584450026905
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.51兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.877087098931975
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.1億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0363503171601947
    },
    {
        "question": " 3747億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.79555459913985
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.016780629700499
    },
    {
        "question": " 484msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.684435686836089
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.8msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.8797521501067935
    },
    {
        "question": " 539兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2325763564986436
    },
    {
        "question": " 276兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5038361574447716
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.73173586131234
    },
    {
        "question": " 5274兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.94400896518395
    },
    {
        "question": " 654億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.815763009094304
    },
    {
        "question": " 2520万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.4013735270301755
    },
    {
        "question": " 122京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5882720398790762
    },
    {
        "question": " 1354兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1950722877150277
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.9垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.221041000621595
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.72京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.049427107002283
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.2京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.593402432328464
    },
    {
        "question": " 1568億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.195447700554306
    },
    {
        "question": " 747万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.8734169835523002
    },
    {
        "question": " 106万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.587393122102394
    },
    {
        "question": " 1212日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5213518582285726
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.7日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.184074715307925
    },
    {
        "question": " 110日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.19926098767375
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.29日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.735087046437133
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.380375749921553
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.946559182377278
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.036622828021316
    },
    {
        "question": " 4914万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9708143760031693
    },
    {
        "question": " 2528分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24446632981408145
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.94万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.173048821645632
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.2分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5275148974942017
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.151451028778544
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.5兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0267261470119395
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18177746182193588
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.3万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0596894385225726
    },
    {
        "question": " 2026億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.528574922868867
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.21万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.7169739850527925
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.31514541119915
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.714899847364515
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.86億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8311916379659956
    },
    {
        "question": " 68兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.276033171285757
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.4億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.602344447905581
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1402064461749861
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.4万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.693973050938006
    },
    {
        "question": " 4423兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1468831629813137
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3917311496568128
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.01京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.347548489758728
    },
    {
        "question": " 253億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6258272257587856
    },
    {
        "question": " 53億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7239707952962195
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.9億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.963121983642222
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.2万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.558270315481654
    },
    {
        "question": " 360京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0579206940497086
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.5垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.05241570729618
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.84069844254264
    },
    {
        "question": " 366京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.785365180554479
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.019645770421254
    },
    {
        "question": " 406万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.6085775568680252
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.8億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.791332710570338
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.72年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5027812884949494
    },
    {
        "question": " 146年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.10736338852119
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.67億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.107380702050751
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.73万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.321124509066628
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.06日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.422231324130989
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.4億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.299114787259982
    },
    {
        "question": " 197万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.915241877333203
    },
    {
        "question": " 931万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.747317810295822
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7034936166538
    },
    {
        "question": " 53億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.00393895888457
    },
    {
        "question": " 100億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.841639545942494
    },
    {
        "question": " 439万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.864614978863319
    },
    {
        "question": " 2721万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.212894377339678
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.298948318846046
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.607819401728867
    },
    {
        "question": " 826万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9804764017295584
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.7万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7994235282747706
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.29万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.020751637315544
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.8秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.890838972171143
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.729606688726459
    },
    {
        "question": " 2582京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.913233337245313
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.157244317029212
    },
    {
        "question": " 494兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.137298618168126
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.302151236686765
    },
    {
        "question": " 1590億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.201420378334813
    },
    {
        "question": " 166京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.720943445107978
    },
    {
        "question": " 7425兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.934224527223372
    },
    {
        "question": " 133京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.568157647697697
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2276036790795541
    },
    {
        "question": " 3061万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4858778955771634
    },
    {
        "question": " 2255億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.353099759769826
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.7万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.472978052824645
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6249139071843928
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.52垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.993951489847764
    },
    {
        "question": " 6京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.221989036157216
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.4兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.075384281176219
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.034206941996844
    },
    {
        "question": " 224億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.349978057662316
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.107288972754161
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.46年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1017708522883733
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7677492653950395
    },
    {
        "question": " 923万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.402917205598428
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.183458098790073
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.12765096244576
    },
    {
        "question": " 3180万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.122205856689958
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.4万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.405702359565634
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.137867743489034
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.9兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.931963218622845
    },
    {
        "question": " 1083億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.876340073722492
    },
    {
        "question": " 126億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.322754115623907
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.8万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.154978400191576
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.97万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.250180031303374
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.3億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0232436552118505
    },
    {
        "question": " 169万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2901386017754057
    },
    {
        "question": " 7372万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.311280543545274
    },
    {
        "question": " 1535秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.40796587379439
    },
    {
        "question": " 8428秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.92571586065378
    },
    {
        "question": " 279兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.947217337094917
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.115735709136052
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4802963061995345
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.2億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7686644179238815
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2781828538709572
    },
    {
        "question": " 85msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.929569374748235
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.2130656172413214
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.1京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0207044356546
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.14734295716269
    },
    {
        "question": " 10京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.444773232913118
    },
    {
        "question": " 8209億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.136162886988094
    },
    {
        "question": " 1109億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.044958056091148
    },
    {
        "question": " 448億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.651033261329241
    },
    {
        "question": " 1878usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.273731693065534
    },
    {
        "question": " 148京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6703761976167641
    },
    {
        "question": " 5193垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.778912696785515
    },
    {
        "question": " 637兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.247974360703383
    },
    {
        "question": " 1110億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.26714027919933936
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.3京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.780258055184802
    },
    {
        "question": " 444兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.647533044111956
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.4003157220482698
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.02年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0417727315338707
    },
    {
        "question": " 1639億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.65228713741891
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.61843630309892
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.3億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.983188308698459
    },
    {
        "question": " 142万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.772802233084731
    },
    {
        "question": " 6678時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.602819973297613
    },
    {
        "question": " 810時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.464539499216919
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5344520009034497
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.8万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.28617465248401
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.328130162330333
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0577612725472614
    },
    {
        "question": " 130兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.614847962438776
    },
    {
        "question": " 115兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.122908089283877
    },
    {
        "question": " 3957万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.041055050468243
    },
    {
        "question": " 8172万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.134176581389045
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.82秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.893260309103843
    },
    {
        "question": " 3278秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.515588751844193
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7620547006123966
    },
    {
        "question": " 7582兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.94327014418447
    },
    {
        "question": " 1083兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.478360024305934
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.8億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.882657067765843
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0815634673540508
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.0092745087168
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.060687294867105
    },
    {
        "question": " 105兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5212688950838618
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.215217072465173
    },
    {
        "question": " 719京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.300555976702835
    },
    {
        "question": " 6310億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.021910856080152
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5094251599853195
    },
    {
        "question": " 5907億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.771358727182912
    },
    {
        "question": " 544万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.7355077520711
    },
    {
        "question": " 532垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.227489507510102
    },
    {
        "question": " 2569京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.473293215800579
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.548640738879548
    },
    {
        "question": " 2247億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5734214936930271
    },
    {
        "question": " 198京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.297498452830746
    },
    {
        "question": " 799兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.902789577153413
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.89万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.6892300537966354
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.3万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.32771664983204
    },
    {
        "question": " 1201年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.022067706968061
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.807301033682401
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.8日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.094686032681595
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.598246767106268
    },
    {
        "question": " 181万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.315941745861161
    },
    {
        "question": " 973億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.6080693208881
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.044624504292325
    },
    {
        "question": " 1553時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.747488923707391
    },
    {
        "question": " 350時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.100187793964965
    },
    {
        "question": " 227万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6352085536921981
    },
    {
        "question": " 7138分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6952489527209549
    },
    {
        "question": " 9104万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.181095512237698
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.09分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.686076406510993
    },
    {
        "question": " 483分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.4621471347458135
    },
    {
        "question": " 335億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0262954649847886
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17972729385205666
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.12兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.9371977399965
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.65万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9741046892247622
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.3万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.888166242454544
    },
    {
        "question": " 214秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.330072992331987
    },
    {
        "question": " 5157京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.213628269409336
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.1億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.463123736545049
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.48億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2551657608172215
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3667856003873267
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.3万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.814700588542517
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.24msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.795425663188141
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.145159540195252
    },
    {
        "question": " 3349京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.026120323951733
    },
    {
        "question": " 1360億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1968876406058362
    },
    {
        "question": " 1750億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6868443004476141
    },
    {
        "question": " 3111兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.714797217246318
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.49兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.73985992894964
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.25万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.720500439508551
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.053e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.813518434451337
    },
    {
        "question": " 865兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0006735730222793
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.76垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.884494642387832
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3259380605507936
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.27京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.51495456881881
    },
    {
        "question": " 150万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.1767235526522204
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.86兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.836150600827287
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.169340589563292
    },
    {
        "question": " 1102億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.479892302184819
    },
    {
        "question": " 79日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.833943535218946
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.9日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.526713399100302
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.277203173103566
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.6億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.194668049222129
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.834699053218712
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.51時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.297572231378419
    },
    {
        "question": " 8993億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.233237747692797
    },
    {
        "question": " 1958分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13341041452104796
    },
    {
        "question": " 224万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.571407847442291
    },
    {
        "question": " 119分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.853647404989351
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.06811645972742
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.932931280889582
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.51兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.479171331976607
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.7万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9069884539415418
    },
    {
        "question": " 2262万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7981172475953295
    },
    {
        "question": " 579秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9845655418217658
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.6京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.815882509034575
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.35兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.588191025452403
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.659826060816912
    },
    {
        "question": " 1436億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.379142327936508
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.44億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.388168825551583
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.79万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.83171531497301
    },
    {
        "question": " 871msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.94022465346392
    },
    {
        "question": " 8783兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.444834670739838
    },
    {
        "question": " 2889兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.524235779101104
    },
    {
        "question": " 6550億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.259933317574715
    },
    {
        "question": " 2018億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5267775114481594
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.388637810431179
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.96億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.695120933226093
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.4usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.841065805965396
    },
    {
        "question": " 138垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.640477204933746
    },
    {
        "question": " 504京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.766265570372999
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.99垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.221247909654503
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.6兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.796793960590227
    },
    {
        "question": " 123億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0895221916080688
    },
    {
        "question": " 34億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.5312807560117774
    },
    {
        "question": " 7299億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.863274536036254
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.583573202565903
    },
    {
        "question": " 786年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.837688670326859
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.6億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.100605670270673
    },
    {
        "question": " 3888日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9699009983000995
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.8日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.758267163413505
    },
    {
        "question": " 46万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.720102905843679
    },
    {
        "question": " 129万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.731052354202557
    },
    {
        "question": " 3360時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.304506527828503
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.52時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.370534748579702
    },
    {
        "question": " 2111兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.60385908957528
    },
    {
        "question": " 8454分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7687379254367166
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.321027410302143
    },
    {
        "question": " 8109万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.687111970117659
    },
    {
        "question": " 420分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.401865203680206
    },
    {
        "question": " 1116億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5487442957389046
    },
    {
        "question": " 1010万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0679335049487135
    },
    {
        "question": " 460万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1067204922613003
    },
    {
        "question": " 239万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.59949270357892
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.58秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.746592635102066
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.6秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.760304768316882
    },
    {
        "question": " 2兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8027796913204064
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.57億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8092963280026633
    },
    {
        "question": " 204兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.754256655100375
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.4億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.67497633376908
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.92億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.772278007149044
    },
    {
        "question": " 3694京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.068643725185331
    },
    {
        "question": " 347兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6043654023531757
    },
    {
        "question": " 405兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.051631763676445
    },
    {
        "question": " 88兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.166338074476693
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1782289310033685
    },
    {
        "question": " 121万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.0844146583760668
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.179e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.839479920639868
    },
    {
        "question": " 125兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1614437046411188
    },
    {
        "question": " 195兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7340443445305964
    },
    {
        "question": " 3867億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8092473354228036
    },
    {
        "question": " 245兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.388663072285295
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.4兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.422236139363362
    },
    {
        "question": " 177億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.248088023876873
    },
    {
        "question": " 1101万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.604014247424557
    },
    {
        "question": " 858億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.371331249729595
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.8万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.068353399010942
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.1日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.521797038033685
    },
    {
        "question": " 5035億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.759521391844665
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.7億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.995132490901089
    },
    {
        "question": " 1333時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.902881636496144
    },
    {
        "question": " 817億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.191560629564414
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.2億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.412729038465238
    },
    {
        "question": " 279億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.667019941473074
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9964823587617984
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.94分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.677766335324977
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.8分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.29456367656492
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.67京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.170921053098008
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.94兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.837508960156033
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.660033847972439
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.3万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5884987941718496
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.7秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.730119089201487
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.93兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0960369368556275
    },
    {
        "question": " 2239億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4136450066748236
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6528748487952905
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.1兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.904124935005727
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.439232950395045
    },
    {
        "question": " 1516垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.681929791150797
    },
    {
        "question": " 3765億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.639235888349482
    },
    {
        "question": " 597億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2194180795079679
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.3兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.584266140825654
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.06億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.906596865237651
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.3547331769502347
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.5万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.788831966479325
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.686281401358141
    },
    {
        "question": " 649垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.875681045712382
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.08京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2939229943459045
    },
    {
        "question": " 2847億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6761896246297161
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.7兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9944763992875165
    },
    {
        "question": " 1574億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.196872568829884
    },
    {
        "question": " 2079億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.317805425107078
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.8年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.25091924757353
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.53年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3459585019444225
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8111766640055382
    },
    {
        "question": " 7929万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.279415754626415
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.966473583479875
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.6億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.930343245933973
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.6万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2879586943013095
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.805461228988602
    },
    {
        "question": " 2079万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5972473892848715
    },
    {
        "question": " 648億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.653315311632357
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3412298543027186
    },
    {
        "question": " 425分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.406193330365394
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.1分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.178606085217591
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.9兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.224886207603712
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.9兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.593360541657677
    },
    {
        "question": " 2973万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9169307366812367
    },
    {
        "question": " 1993秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5213744026262965
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.9万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.71503458744325
    },
    {
        "question": " 692京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.341405197999753
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14171905816609542
    },
    {
        "question": " 2165兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.779223852538667
    },
    {
        "question": " 2530万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6248886645844127
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.7万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.650292916832245
    },
    {
        "question": " 2500msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.3979120490550105
    },
    {
        "question": " 249msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.396788370218417
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.2兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.359775071426337
    },
    {
        "question": " 770兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9500118355774436
    },
    {
        "question": " 281兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.892140411441517
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.6兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.143828674986308
    },
    {
        "question": " 6476億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8113125228968885
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.009493261951484
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.277294475609695
    },
    {
        "question": " 1277京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6074611447536578
    },
    {
        "question": " 206垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.377827446445545
    },
    {
        "question": " 919兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4069181386271876
    },
    {
        "question": " 1178兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2928454527450635
    },
    {
        "question": " 2180兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.338474042666783
    },
    {
        "question": " 3761兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.575291536341052
    },
    {
        "question": " 3071万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.487321760056061
    },
    {
        "question": " 5621年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.692339294138692
    },
    {
        "question": " 6956年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.562997451065321
    },
    {
        "question": " 9621日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4209360917198766
    },
    {
        "question": " 100万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.381049471828334
    },
    {
        "question": " 24万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.537955567385357
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.7日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.463831908828407
    },
    {
        "question": " 245億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.446199982216041
    },
    {
        "question": " 91時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5788038961719921
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.916525565248944
    },
    {
        "question": " 716時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.411246479307314
    },
    {
        "question": " 1209億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.361769668650988
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.08兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.159667651019847
    },
    {
        "question": " 4480億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.873150033232045
    },
    {
        "question": " 244分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.165558896508129
    },
    {
        "question": " 1231分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.868347262630016
    },
    {
        "question": " 221兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.846076391523525
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.353152678976294
    },
    {
        "question": " 4508万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.097688444702693
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.528913570013913
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.071968573282872
    },
    {
        "question": " 841秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.924949268155231
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.34820206952746
    },
    {
        "question": " 95兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4790055277160103
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.3兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.425884600998459
    },
    {
        "question": " 4710億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.116742455446089
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.1億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.079756152421608
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.307035457522439
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.1270887635232345
    },
    {
        "question": " 486兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1876391179195178
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.9兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0222020116833104
    },
    {
        "question": " 2915兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.908279913671742
    },
    {
        "question": " 926億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1886731604891816
    },
    {
        "question": " 14兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1461124756647285
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.86万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5867674915487984
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.679e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.171360295530855
    },
    {
        "question": " 869兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0026351279617962
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.2垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.749501410851662
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.22京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.729319121211967
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.3京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.262546072126627
    },
    {
        "question": " 191万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.2818707580901958
    },
    {
        "question": " 216億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.334176862192232
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.69万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.317324035164533
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.123091592240174
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.2年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.067185992531892
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.5年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.740811091332771
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.448486267530412
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.791489103208491
    },
    {
        "question": " 269万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.486591366019286
    },
    {
        "question": " 3929万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.214108740056485
    },
    {
        "question": " 1751万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.021508866702225
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.9億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.208440350543454
    },
    {
        "question": " 336億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.368506836238029
    },
    {
        "question": " 3316億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.742480780078049
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.788999803165665
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.8分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.1718371120898645
    },
    {
        "question": " 849兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.429859772938893
    },
    {
        "question": " 2932億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.530703609575825
    },
    {
        "question": " 7208億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.301504990374118
    },
    {
        "question": " 4839億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.906620937505838
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.2秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.507920066761551
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.45秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.647944933326144
    },
    {
        "question": " 4468京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.151283172964607
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.324800948909222
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.476883648628448
    },
    {
        "question": " 269兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.651681991818425
    },
    {
        "question": " 4091億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.61184066182606
    },
    {
        "question": " 109万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.037226527404451
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.2msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.914054533718232
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.7兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.48216893536623173
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.500356747047874
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.78京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.02171898328796
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.13億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7172499723453807
    },
    {
        "question": " 52億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7157154144327142
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.54兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.656929777161197
    },
    {
        "question": " 727usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.861374054099885
    },
    {
        "question": " 2594垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.915195119903731
    },
    {
        "question": " 1082京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.097850102521405
    },
    {
        "question": " 3089京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.933506125679222
    },
    {
        "question": " 241京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.603719999349382
    },
    {
        "question": " 1022億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.009618467152726
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.322785112892772
    },
    {
        "question": " 919億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.963261543355084
    },
    {
        "question": " 139年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.704540800560553
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.39万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.673900803349314
    },
    {
        "question": " 736万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.304688030160298
    },
    {
        "question": " 1361日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.513899636683908
    },
    {
        "question": " 426日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.787790334005503
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.361477203395829
    },
    {
        "question": " 203億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.927937095840742
    },
    {
        "question": " 109時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.815637401729713
    },
    {
        "question": " 1221時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6430409811113025
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.1億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.149178611219978
    },
    {
        "question": " 1567分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03671161801939049
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.1万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9293849942800843
    },
    {
        "question": " 4794分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.458853636064065
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.3分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.394235517576993
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.22京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.294952129119531
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.234552017532625
    },
    {
        "question": " 896億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.395770372350291
    },
    {
        "question": " 74億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.090928751219014
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.2万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.434663431292167
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.426248196600412
    },
    {
        "question": " 4234兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.127988354212069
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.453134120017772
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.58億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3233942358182436
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.5万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.211054029013694
    },
    {
        "question": " 2595msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4140611536028782
    },
    {
        "question": " 1790msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.252796879778
    },
    {
        "question": " 429京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.133180833216555
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.68京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.817802428063975
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.540525938250866
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3706359864931106
    },
    {
        "question": " 5619万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7496507863883337
    },
    {
        "question": " 1710万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.232938899830486
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.284850476061571
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5664306794481195
    },
    {
        "question": " 3912兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6559214054937788
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.02京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9231038864055168
    },
    {
        "question": " 752兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.09805147008636
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.7京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.473079314883833
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.5億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.351861409743594
    },
    {
        "question": " 465億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.667659119942423
    },
    {
        "question": " 1137年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9982058652088055
    },
    {
        "question": " 837万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.360600576111185
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.84日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.924805757976114
    },
    {
        "question": " 1291日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.047365873612192
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.9日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.548392763253963
    },
    {
        "question": " 9360億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.028775936874736
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.7億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.498630504582167
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.83万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.724138359818478
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.4時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.52931258059826
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.758536250793612
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.122202740426339
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.42億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.755262138633968
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.823795004584921
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.55分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.52218624399707
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.940070214358407
    },
    {
        "question": " 1753億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.307186823223145
    },
    {
        "question": " 258万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.854641920084
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5122607720591015
    },
    {
        "question": " 2657秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.424345189103377
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.719961544943317
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.08億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3819177399982199
    },
    {
        "question": " 637兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.247641918342483
    },
    {
        "question": " 127億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.324861925548024
    },
    {
        "question": " 898万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9530487368701417
    },
    {
        "question": " 286万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.456626867113783
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.8京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7754533317948615
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.5京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.469373450469789
    },
    {
        "question": " 412兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.058186799320388
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4093042676376666
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.235968914038952
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.8万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.9946983990166776
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.9京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.162934557301023
    },
    {
        "question": " 3281垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.579535712921968
    },
    {
        "question": " 3485兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.985901612197601
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.8兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.560895941518236
    },
    {
        "question": " 3504兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.544536583823165
    },
    {
        "question": " 2741億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.437955077267932
    },
    {
        "question": " 1104億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.042773728612628
    },
    {
        "question": " 122万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.647389308180559
    },
    {
        "question": " 1024年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.952643760581109
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.7年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.341217221008077
    },
    {
        "question": " 103億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.448557182878108
    },
    {
        "question": " 5476万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.118634643572484
    },
    {
        "question": " 1414日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.086992469918663
    },
    {
        "question": " 119万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1316425101961256
    },
    {
        "question": " 385億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.20474280216154
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.56時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.595199903997234
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.81時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.320494367871283
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.00306584260126
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.1兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.012191975431351
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.7万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3937635804833404
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.2分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12579454575972093
    },
    {
        "question": " 970万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.764917967714418
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.988474778789924
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.94億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4011892391578018
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.5兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.682000250596161
    },
    {
        "question": " 1346億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.572783599409067
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.12万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8364393524117784
    },
    {
        "question": " 153秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.183715888450685
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.315529686608352
    },
    {
        "question": " 366億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06476136617223571
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.61京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.883911916590794
    },
    {
        "question": " 3313万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9639488519489958
    },
    {
        "question": " 247兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.614058099341243
    },
    {
        "question": " 1528msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18420733801735145
    },
    {
        "question": " 241万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.382025196124227
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.790775203467672
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.39京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.441353385263969
    },
    {
        "question": " 1656兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.662807670346066
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.6兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.851116165624406
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.92兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.89854791655971
    },
    {
        "question": " 60万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.777926528644843
    },
    {
        "question": " 3usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.4777402560102177
    },
    {
        "question": " 8207垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.415360706096566
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.07410302911604
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.4京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.17916758514917
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.57垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.967984527003567
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.5億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24272396537690755
    },
    {
        "question": " 237億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.37467859471645
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.573037026830288
    },
    {
        "question": " 508年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.268294779745305
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.6年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.803168435618918
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.2万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8884258085416317
    },
    {
        "question": " 7221日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.238783426433264
    },
    {
        "question": " 5724日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.916060062175554
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.87億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8944047479748445
    },
    {
        "question": " 838万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.542861775044811
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.9万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.156280859800049
    },
    {
        "question": " 48時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.23774389323454
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.79時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.134627737704816
    },
    {
        "question": " 1084億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.314183538207519
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.973180849503079
    },
    {
        "question": " 117万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.28924264548188
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.88万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.237496164760441
    },
    {
        "question": " 108分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.810081864880403
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9144982953796066
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.148358068943303
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.698903916896581
    },
    {
        "question": " 2763万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.663183804617345
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.4万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.523273982130164
    },
    {
        "question": " 1590秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.201332122844876
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.5京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.379217579274679
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.5兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.905541460627103
    },
    {
        "question": " 459万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10586163244883262
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.5兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.783905982710749
    },
    {
        "question": " 659億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.819112748168835
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.27msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.5144975634757647
    },
    {
        "question": " 6693msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.82561700508327
    },
    {
        "question": " 3888京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0909532788794065
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.92垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.346590855058366
    },
    {
        "question": " 2487兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.839357861311052
    },
    {
        "question": " 346億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.761467678132181
    },
    {
        "question": " 57億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.755956258893737
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.116097015536541
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.26万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.720604431660504
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.713e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.734930179205351
    },
    {
        "question": " 2106京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.386870790809261
    },
    {
        "question": " 422兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.06931590394269
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.8京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.633012527051058
    },
    {
        "question": " 301兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.478092738253198
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.66億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.9374979107139563
    },
    {
        "question": " 2964万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.471837211768005
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.24万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.908020161288247
    },
    {
        "question": " 281億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.886171393360217
    },
    {
        "question": " 1276万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.486072498094718
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.2日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.402185855901399
    },
    {
        "question": " 741億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.92742060673482
    },
    {
        "question": " 8641万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.556385580254457
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.64時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.378165902610679
    },
    {
        "question": " 393時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.150273562562298
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.285036897123669
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.016532787419988
    },
    {
        "question": " 7856万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.117065478816115
    },
    {
        "question": " 1092分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.816411729243603
    },
    {
        "question": " 212兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.827961636793453
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16793467886160096
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.630477760059895
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.38万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.194019003800901
    },
    {
        "question": " 1579億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6996319697386766
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.8億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5797879780272461
    },
    {
        "question": " 5146兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.155151461400013
    },
    {
        "question": " 537億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.951627986820766
    },
    {
        "question": " 2790億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.445609599651482
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.45万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.809234592401218
    },
    {
        "question": " 2189msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.340207698217787
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.8京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.255270444328793
    },
    {
        "question": " 603兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.843847519127589
    },
    {
        "question": " 134兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.569542266458337
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.9億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6833187992922238
    },
    {
        "question": " 145万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16276961441139437
    },
    {
        "question": " 3876万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.588437692163709
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.65京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1687854688008028
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.51垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.939067661760831
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5360335012547655
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.51京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.875862325110144
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.7京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.271723508802069
    },
    {
        "question": " 230兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.361911553974432
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.272785341264815
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.648237533100224
    },
    {
        "question": " 276年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.382895798467768
    },
    {
        "question": " 6446億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.247009220602946
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.7日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9486790907359208
    },
    {
        "question": " 600日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.714780813741221
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.5万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8673708822633184
    },
    {
        "question": " 756万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.498203690297633
    },
    {
        "question": " 19時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0576360396111335
    },
    {
        "question": " 121時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.638458731033001
    },
    {
        "question": " 596兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.05437496704526
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.7万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1125124222227267
    },
    {
        "question": " 16万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4254678685939655
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.81万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.359271437862935
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.52万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.179933813232859
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.884293280303451
    },
    {
        "question": " 344兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.037314656112165
    },
    {
        "question": " 120億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.144065701878359
    },
    {
        "question": " 2091万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7640643732492105
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.33億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.588517906980127
    },
    {
        "question": " 1414秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.150380296293348
    },
    {
        "question": " 122秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.084949134850469
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.562542775888632
    },
    {
        "question": " 817億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.975901282925899
    },
    {
        "question": " 123兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.535207436659153
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.93074212868443
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.58万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5540132338356005
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.23msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.6258634067003994
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.4msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.452904215416663
    },
    {
        "question": " 213垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.828955067322273
    },
    {
        "question": " 917億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.025635438597432225
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.591242671028087
    },
    {
        "question": " 122兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.30823244829291
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.311160608971507
    },
    {
        "question": " 45億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.65281759748682
    },
    {
        "question": " 3346usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.524544098917505
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.695569244662755
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.6垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.416935004894874
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.7垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.692333082929837
    },
    {
        "question": " 191兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.502833863291678
    },
    {
        "question": " 1710兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.23305862847154
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.1559433302672524
    },
    {
        "question": " 5792万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.762850124504606
    },
    {
        "question": " 39年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.153440764290954
    },
    {
        "question": " 580年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7057763936394235
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.3年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.567623165560589
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.17億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.350005138601482
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.07万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.866944969139394
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.54万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9020041523158895
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.4日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2458402701485385
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.274526307601755
    },
    {
        "question": " 1955万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.910902242931795
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.81252910964314
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.44204128934169
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.1万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4766252739115013
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.9万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6348235279754304
    },
    {
        "question": " 3832万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.36157766869685
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.6億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.362106194714312
    },
    {
        "question": " 466億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.731908727248931
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.489430848341391
    },
    {
        "question": " 2362万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.595165654010483
    },
    {
        "question": " 34秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.531533240869152
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.3秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.467368867218207
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.568153924517065
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.78億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8254474919230259
    },
    {
        "question": " 52兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1594018793379055
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.6億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.058105843335273
    },
    {
        "question": " 1254億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.098402280221016
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.04万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.7811957941436205
    },
    {
        "question": " 447兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1512930585880377
    },
    {
        "question": " 397京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.662794116927064
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.1億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17718239770739497
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.4兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.77033033995326
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.2兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.857166942211527
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.44兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.38733342422945
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.00321429218709
    },
    {
        "question": " 1049垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.522153754431922
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.1垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.707663589069482
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.46京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.181250017488919
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.4兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.973335999266382
    },
    {
        "question": " 156兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1920407547912575
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.17244590319737
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.55万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.7442576420640976
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.5万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.709901025862328
    },
    {
        "question": " 2739億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.875248220423268
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.9日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8263508817304315
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.1万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.557581423299222
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.42日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.910693877272315
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.3億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.013413908565787
    },
    {
        "question": " 9801万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.611068736176348
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.631697028285904
    },
    {
        "question": " 120万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.359151252549581
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.906477548431285
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.38万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.862857188580384
    },
    {
        "question": " 3295分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.295987148012381
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.703174139749408
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.233578397032745
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.1万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8771938004666433
    },
    {
        "question": " 4936億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.91525564216333
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.32万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.364823343543524
    },
    {
        "question": " 689秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.83830321533471
    },
    {
        "question": " 2832京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.953299810548968
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1347675987187622
    },
    {
        "question": " 2852億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.898780093383963
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.408360898280557
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.5億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.511238117939836
    },
    {
        "question": " 1939msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.2876363177920265
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.63京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0613128789925668
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.7京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.69396968897761
    },
    {
        "question": " 135億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.574191198677132
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.275031331912896
    },
    {
        "question": " 2319億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.365263617553653
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.3725385448993788
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.1usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.382773260502804
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.337e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.62740382490577
    },
    {
        "question": " 522垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.781082053815414
    },
    {
        "question": " 215兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7756058133163988
    },
    {
        "question": " 115京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.280945900206856
    },
    {
        "question": " 4848兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.685601636950846
    },
    {
        "question": " 214億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.3296381929851355
    },
    {
        "question": " 8623万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.935681808000152
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.6万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.192162492215832
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.09年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.554233448928517
    },
    {
        "question": " 1216年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.805572980272018
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.689632435411347
    },
    {
        "question": " 281日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.828669171444754
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.004036219191638
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.988634400060741
    },
    {
        "question": " 11億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.09741978661287
    },
    {
        "question": " 2303億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.98217781459205
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.34時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5801908261780584
    },
    {
        "question": " 205兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.591759876357871
    },
    {
        "question": " 273億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.277505197899429
    },
    {
        "question": " 105億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.241421678593198
    },
    {
        "question": " 55分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5183509426893234
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.09039470033523
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.559595502280711
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.01兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7634715926924605
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5912873099686715
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.2億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.971446045000896
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.8秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.610192253708596
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.56兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4339081146517714
    },
    {
        "question": " 967億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0490760201965372
    },
    {
        "question": " 693兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.284120556606883
    },
    {
        "question": " 468億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.892104098614048
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.3億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.960376511314918
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.2万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.80099119458969
    },
    {
        "question": " 832垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.421189747117296
    },
    {
        "question": " 176京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.308796720430989
    },
    {
        "question": " 586億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.211759346933028
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.4億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1376196257681346
    },
    {
        "question": " 5894万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7704357992136965
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.0966426150454966
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.228777949111298
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.537e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.15793898872565
    },
    {
        "question": " 168垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.28782655024224
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.2垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.270860397229564
    },
    {
        "question": " 324兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.732211809180719
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.449193534285599
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.029513753724467
    },
    {
        "question": " 141万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.1506164261147553
    },
    {
        "question": " 5887年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.712428951050738
    },
    {
        "question": " 127年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.60247969994992
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.4億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.748071125452265
    },
    {
        "question": " 100日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.38134594990235
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.299898037180279
    },
    {
        "question": " 70日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.781317793958719
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.6兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.411737059724597
    },
    {
        "question": " 1701億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.850469669223857
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.95万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.620014740975008
    },
    {
        "question": " 4304時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.19012820213054
    },
    {
        "question": " 431時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.191064685109499
    },
    {
        "question": " 1011億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2841041919880505
    },
    {
        "question": " 2029億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.148833303617145
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.9万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.180456981652418
    },
    {
        "question": " 9360分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.749443981134808
    },
    {
        "question": " 180億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.756433879256578
    },
    {
        "question": " 4474万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7141609648317955
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.66億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.869145115293135
    },
    {
        "question": " 2692億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.651894762703476
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.2万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.654730778607256
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.5垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.899769457497925
    },
    {
        "question": " 636億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8666471720479003
    },
    {
        "question": " 1968兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.737654941924536
    },
    {
        "question": " 239億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6009012949598
    },
    {
        "question": " 3310msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5198388220992511
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.5msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.628852770946702
    },
    {
        "question": " 332msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.521053861739574
    },
    {
        "question": " 3301京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.019788331510396
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.334320161123092
    },
    {
        "question": " 273兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.879325978084208
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.390174906869907
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.32752341262215
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.193203598109957
    },
    {
        "question": " 7204usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.857586083251499
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.222e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.588128972582133
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.6兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06165498825166593
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8520190449137255
    },
    {
        "question": " 3035京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.703962860466365
    },
    {
        "question": " 424億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6268788568334769
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.13兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.495178827359251
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.7億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.884547941964896
    },
    {
        "question": " 191万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.843196298858336
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.035479331199717
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.442794102366628
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.1万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8437350775121555
    },
    {
        "question": " 2324日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.524644671468564
    },
    {
        "question": " 464日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.603463174426079
    },
    {
        "question": " 1012万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.062672256552336
    },
    {
        "question": " 1402時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7666323809408035
    },
    {
        "question": " 3809時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.13709879284595
    },
    {
        "question": " 6431万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0876130529157475
    },
    {
        "question": " 422万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.466716042365091
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.5億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.733950801280565
    },
    {
        "question": " 1614分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.986164498567385
    },
    {
        "question": " 7468分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.651330873350952
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.592814563360253
    },
    {
        "question": " 196万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3549328105804104
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9861119711817832
    },
    {
        "question": " 434万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.859009454227328
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.172687646057128
    },
    {
        "question": " 3474億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0420657189205729
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.3兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.530858610579168
    },
    {
        "question": " 928億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.411474843939689
    },
    {
        "question": " 3211億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7284544256409795
    },
    {
        "question": " 1142msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05763736416680598
    },
    {
        "question": " 4051msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.607576093705907
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.156980125005109
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.2京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.916092284638159
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.9兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.920040294336158
    },
    {
        "question": " 47億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8939622241317067
    },
    {
        "question": " 331万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5200425969991151
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.5万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.916703137788492
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.4万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.828360244069911
    },
    {
        "question": " 101垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.504799598805834
    },
    {
        "question": " 2476京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.457303446916453
    },
    {
        "question": " 360京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.999852641029358
    },
    {
        "question": " 3164億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7220578094396335
    },
    {
        "question": " 418京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.621692823320922
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.215081419668865
    },
    {
        "question": " 7843nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.894509470178273
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.7年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.258827870780214
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.72年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.547929992305347
    },
    {
        "question": " 2756日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8779813319587215
    },
    {
        "question": " 7309日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.244076687900856
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.93兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.956540305449277
    },
    {
        "question": " 234万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.988948787394115
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9591036355891145
    },
    {
        "question": " 54万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.288934622368592
    },
    {
        "question": " 1375時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.694575955228846
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3863201876120463
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2377178650255116
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.1億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.503932692004499
    },
    {
        "question": " 348万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.31999123434672
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.4兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.741932537652339
    },
    {
        "question": " 1908万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3440821754819763
    },
    {
        "question": " 9561秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4242239432169803
    },
    {
        "question": " 4526億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.877603108779871
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.9秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.943859385012207
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.8秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.9676610542460145
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.4兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8815549092030703
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5474589181929357
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.98億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0438844562009217
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.6万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.138773349412413
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.64兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.751609548892867
    },
    {
        "question": " 1533msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.185661553304454
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.563038812671023
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.9垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.902605237402252
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.7兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7392348970686893
    },
    {
        "question": " 150兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.397171324465213
    },
    {
        "question": " 181億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.257676283443068
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.226716563839053
    },
    {
        "question": " 153usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.183455634729855
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.238e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.466754692299027
    },
    {
        "question": " 210垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.384760856814106
    },
    {
        "question": " 562京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.193494622401552
    },
    {
        "question": " 269京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.652131293764358
    },
    {
        "question": " 5063億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7044228862507835
    },
    {
        "question": " 104兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.019031442264936
    },
    {
        "question": " 166億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.220490965178348
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.21万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.526617418903508
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.4年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.653727289641564
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.987755925905661
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.7年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.118846333824784
    },
    {
        "question": " 16億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.642180697570686
    },
    {
        "question": " 669日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.205474386188797
    },
    {
        "question": " 497日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.632763140707971
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.51日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.482355796172568
    },
    {
        "question": " 303億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5389016076061495
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9282763045154816
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.52時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1802573304670805
    },
    {
        "question": " 3163兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.779425418833839
    },
    {
        "question": " 2167億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.177515623153997
    },
    {
        "question": " 492万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.913757091342644
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.1分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3818181428925156
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.8兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.375179866071068
    },
    {
        "question": " 198兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.360246439435326
    },
    {
        "question": " 518万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1576410897395113
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.413805865957146
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.1秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.663787898531692
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.160264501711237
    },
    {
        "question": " 2911億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9652253991310888
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18561732988098267
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.64兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.326647773658726
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.963610906158609
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2604923016820724
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.84万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.583981601832532
    },
    {
        "question": " 305垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.986138627275974
    },
    {
        "question": " 1478京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.23327638228659
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.7億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.233881912741013
    },
    {
        "question": " 1650兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.439418132665557
    },
    {
        "question": " 201兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.304156357515089
    },
    {
        "question": " 172万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.234718894824163
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.99usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.6977851274588946
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.412e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.651134880104092
    },
    {
        "question": " 1438兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2212874233141946
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.9垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.0866021573563
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.9京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.902002738084912
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.4京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.853991526524975
    },
    {
        "question": " 6716兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.827119939343556
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.79億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.990749325399688
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.744038520319993
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.25364564578591
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.949799667387788
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.81年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.080292071421614
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.906323495161379
    },
    {
        "question": " 342日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6922689842919585
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.096498432172833
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.003489925583642
    },
    {
        "question": " 6549億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.873677851546555
    },
    {
        "question": " 3289万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.136859715507513
    },
    {
        "question": " 160時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.759914428355794
    },
    {
        "question": " 3601億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.835826336576682
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.33億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.70690766660568
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.52万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.200423182299452
    },
    {
        "question": " 7745分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.667191294429379
    },
    {
        "question": " 1397分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.923413565064844
    },
    {
        "question": " 342億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.035207942095195
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.08億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.769458273596904
    },
    {
        "question": " 115万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5051324625905727
    },
    {
        "question": " 25億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.619411996533504
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.01714580021906
    },
    {
        "question": " 3083億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9901756029799469
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.5兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.807407782651857
    },
    {
        "question": " 344億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9805592478557514
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.8兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.150480699221786
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.74万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.675535656060947
    },
    {
        "question": " 607msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.782890725423908
    },
    {
        "question": " 207京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.816515404148257
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.2京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.983413587562406
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.9兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.411803871805295
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.68兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.976200770290905
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.386226213861692
    },
    {
        "question": " 19万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.2790087501966996
    },
    {
        "question": " 149usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.172243234960533
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.9垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.27210633837235
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.360670363757241
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.33垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.245135872141265
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.8京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.832732058230199
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.217892426587614
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.94兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.900048542839485
    },
    {
        "question": " 480億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.680853290951376
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.34万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.483293087750528
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.096124380467227
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.7年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.193505370721811
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.861983147076948
    },
    {
        "question": " 3807億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.018317648267299
    },
    {
        "question": " 417万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.999963976840386
    },
    {
        "question": " 128万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.165622774705848
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8065440075488475
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.825789543786641
    },
    {
        "question": " 4212万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9038402780746955
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.45万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8169219114881363
    },
    {
        "question": " 1027万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.233615225609084
    },
    {
        "question": " 13分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.891837404052308
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.668558686108197
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.75億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8231406880134857
    },
    {
        "question": " 360万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.999531516018241
    },
    {
        "question": " 9463万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.197900995509435
    },
    {
        "question": " 160秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.203611857188044
    },
    {
        "question": " 129秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.111756941625345
    },
    {
        "question": " 3923億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0948407622288259
    },
    {
        "question": " 431億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6984221236695594
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.815041506660165
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.1兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.894485502353547
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.2万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.40077527472644
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.290244199084727
    },
    {
        "question": " 1611兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7082435149558162
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2754969344550933
    },
    {
        "question": " 6786億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2753319793657143
    },
    {
        "question": " 5535億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9649466696907076
    },
    {
        "question": " 2419万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3836198749116735
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.87兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.687726536615033
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.131706779023531
    },
    {
        "question": " 7546京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.378911473257611
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.29907393801793
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.3兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.244967126602633
    },
    {
        "question": " 9536億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2012244858011734
    },
    {
        "question": " 89京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.949309090704071
    },
    {
        "question": " 370億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.567872180525793
    },
    {
        "question": " 627万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.7969964721954397
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.82万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.507595857842665
    },
    {
        "question": " 299億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.913150266629111
    },
    {
        "question": " 2867日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.615766077373696
    },
    {
        "question": " 285日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.390884927020268
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.6億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.033245218798964
    },
    {
        "question": " 2177万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.957750634309774
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.11219535117082
    },
    {
        "question": " 4119時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.171069036728173
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7161166042864107
    },
    {
        "question": " 9044万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.798018161235065
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.9億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.040677912961845
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.5万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.720261378316568
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.017073397083538
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.8京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.080807105359332
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.102454012106291
    },
    {
        "question": " 701億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.289224204645244
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.303676845637525
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.435427019986525
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.652495511956193
    },
    {
        "question": " 155兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.254991343380994
    },
    {
        "question": " 706万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.29253661391514196
    },
    {
        "question": " 121兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.305095054440844
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.14万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7882266108614375
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.6兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2767997174340542
    },
    {
        "question": " 9085億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0218294530354888
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.3京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.015588778737419
    },
    {
        "question": " 493億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9151349957362447
    },
    {
        "question": " 405億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.607549699010109
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.245999905365132
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8297749240229202
    },
    {
        "question": " 7033垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.910655877165901
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.465590903829068
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.372486103025228
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.209864763334108
    },
    {
        "question": " 1000兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.000135808409842
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.49億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.8125002035961835
    },
    {
        "question": " 1852年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.829982321202029
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.010948687752855
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.90831472753982
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.62590358999693
    },
    {
        "question": " 553万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.122547495552022
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.28億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.416315779678376
    },
    {
        "question": " 5102時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3275064386546687
    },
    {
        "question": " 9701万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.764963640721389
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5367747459052365
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.315469852317722
    },
    {
        "question": " 7017分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.067992544296806
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.82万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.461453981319362
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.7兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0663210840210535
    },
    {
        "question": " 1484億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2350724042232555
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.79億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2063823750173555
    },
    {
        "question": " 403秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8271537975339804
    },
    {
        "question": " 203秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.306802491541883
    },
    {
        "question": " 311秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.492659919747767
    },
    {
        "question": " 742億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3715016047100772
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3919246217201053
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.35京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.968574794873113
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.35億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7473033072496587
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.224694054632454
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.360303036798479
    },
    {
        "question": " 6979京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.344966875725787
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.384802941519023
    },
    {
        "question": " 5874兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.212647579636133
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.243933098378753
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.6億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.842499425086703
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.0206630405681136
    },
    {
        "question": " 466usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.668210839459239
    },
    {
        "question": " 3285垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.017747620094123
    },
    {
        "question": " 2999京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.540454437674401
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.2兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9521222576304456
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3645105559201232
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.1兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.558059617119995
    },
    {
        "question": " 145億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.162429860165949
    },
    {
        "question": " 2401nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.3804029446986068
    },
    {
        "question": " 1439年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.720291044864895
    },
    {
        "question": " 158億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.63539879594057
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.501515973524144
    },
    {
        "question": " 172日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.392842891295304
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.064785329484735
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.89兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.518792038788423
    },
    {
        "question": " 113億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.672167292325495
    },
    {
        "question": " 6140万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.566285550124988
    },
    {
        "question": " 112万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.605608957243797
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.66億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.21701201276324
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2887501706353
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.87万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.990845279575262
    },
    {
        "question": " 423分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.404962378231439
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.84万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.544281013113377
    },
    {
        "question": " 906億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4582697431810496
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.8兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.949063441302327
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.73億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.331943875914539
    },
    {
        "question": " 987億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.216111999546365
    },
    {
        "question": " 1018秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.007615468328505
    },
    {
        "question": " 2557秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.407717839039554
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.67兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3862140900374627
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3223995765010665
    },
    {
        "question": " 3667兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.008011125908789
    },
    {
        "question": " 636億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0252124274189445
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.11億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.959376042662984
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.030345809951778
    },
    {
        "question": " 232京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.867448721923145
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.6兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6611507805271497
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.542981081721829
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.794539890963691
    },
    {
        "question": " 111億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.045016396795624
    },
    {
        "question": " 1621万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.209832575911787
    },
    {
        "question": " 2473usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.393299420971709
    },
    {
        "question": " 3743垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.074442443469657
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.77京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5057719133221257
    },
    {
        "question": " 107京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.471970933567678
    },
    {
        "question": " 803京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.126377984967624
    },
    {
        "question": " 252京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.401743696304155
    },
    {
        "question": " 2039兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.30945489879854
    },
    {
        "question": " 854億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.931604566121021
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.6年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.49827773602347
    },
    {
        "question": " 1855年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.98895032307007
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.895655624541298
    },
    {
        "question": " 1081日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.414049246760101
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.45万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.806830224816151
    },
    {
        "question": " 188日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.210027978779613
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.2億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.538069439001153
    },
    {
        "question": " 1332億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.744183188454947
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.97万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.554114640011102
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.8時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.380799279480532
    },
    {
        "question": " 1746億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.521273206723904
    },
    {
        "question": " 6441億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.650578375421096
    },
    {
        "question": " 372万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.792007419835105
    },
    {
        "question": " 1989分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.076807151190204
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.58億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4825611342192846
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.300272978348606
    },
    {
        "question": " 1998万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7443874089248985
    },
    {
        "question": " 120秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3000848124661204
    },
    {
        "question": " 165万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.216237703430277
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.42702282324787
    },
    {
        "question": " 1792億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7545951706882281
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.35億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9850965161138048
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.695944909797148
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.82兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.055490562215391
    },
    {
        "question": " 6373万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.804364966537866
    },
    {
        "question": " 709万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.850376002019901
    },
    {
        "question": " 1056京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.524713549499621
    },
    {
        "question": " 6046兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8449512296982515
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.78723430239283
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.11京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.007711163843343
    },
    {
        "question": " 2514億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.400367690621733
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.127633746145088
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.716e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.935134629515401
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.370753289584834
    },
    {
        "question": " 2298京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8051366792764405
    },
    {
        "question": " 697京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.064913887041229
    },
    {
        "question": " 237京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.374482253020934
    },
    {
        "question": " 1004兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.001870102729562
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.5万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.4978621133559264
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7443321963118126
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.7年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.680237229342446
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.3年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.455669482122732
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.2億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.871527433711771
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.8日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9464869303499572
    },
    {
        "question": " 367日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.722532308951762
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.76万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.76671108688366
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5260761028537109
    },
    {
        "question": " 3746万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.193338388918509
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1034672357160575
    },
    {
        "question": " 8593時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.490435632398866
    },
    {
        "question": " 458時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.217113388308517
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.9万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09836511474890619
    },
    {
        "question": " 1667万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.063586687756042
    },
    {
        "question": " 191分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5032896935794251
    },
    {
        "question": " 5038万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.480437240288344
    },
    {
        "question": " 392分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.371305279780344
    },
    {
        "question": " 351億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.046027180949192
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.64億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8150862640976655
    },
    {
        "question": " 9115万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.403474086304612
    },
    {
        "question": " 6528秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.036628002441164
    },
    {
        "question": " 7877秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.896373161929169
    },
    {
        "question": " 1525秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.183393553697162
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.510127504243042
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.231739540409204
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.530860569624714
    },
    {
        "question": " 9862万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2158366341213283
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.6億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9520915441298206
    },
    {
        "question": " 9664京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4863381741391
    },
    {
        "question": " 6260億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8600638886185874
    },
    {
        "question": " 57兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.19942802962397
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2722921175447621
    },
    {
        "question": " 5089万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7066313416673495
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.127523281477098
    },
    {
        "question": " 450万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.6530772895566
    },
    {
        "question": " 8508垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.431006216321916
    },
    {
        "question": " 5038京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.765738597338929
    },
    {
        "question": " 22京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.786610606450533
    },
    {
        "question": " 4167兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.841694186601638
    },
    {
        "question": " 1612億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2074725075587
    },
    {
        "question": " 2067兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.315308400767856
    },
    {
        "question": " 53億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.723989342145464
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.13万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.729871812665648
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.9億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.222048997194607
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.792208516070485
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.01万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.937181592886367
    },
    {
        "question": " 2208日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.280512701530338
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.5日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.486869074545115
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07417276470148226
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.854371094098287
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.7時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.513983666720622
    },
    {
        "question": " 421兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.903131166557783
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.8兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.421501280683517
    },
    {
        "question": " 1083億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.256648540634195
    },
    {
        "question": " 403分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.383521953436225
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.837153535175634
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.03億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9831534135361297
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.1兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.998322121232182
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.493074004323374
    },
    {
        "question": " 760万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1025283467929805
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.27秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.966993865088618
    },
    {
        "question": " 2635兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.921972316689586
    },
    {
        "question": " 295兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.532749264706231
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4838964139476174
    },
    {
        "question": " 2221万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5684103898642174
    },
    {
        "question": " 2406億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.38124503460472
    },
    {
        "question": " 1737msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.239857957540433
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.6msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.513662665685521
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.27垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.015781293295721
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.7兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.936620243431254
    },
    {
        "question": " 1006京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.446343038348765
    },
    {
        "question": " 2002億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5232127456642637
    },
    {
        "question": " 2311兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.363855871803791
    },
    {
        "question": " 6493万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.812457777200947
    },
    {
        "question": " 17万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.230030472863877
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.739e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.74161055420667
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.316699154581131
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.7垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.38693306908153
    },
    {
        "question": " 821京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.136394441511408
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.034115989959332
    },
    {
        "question": " 123億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.0902326450613415
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.43万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.6459342867338844
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.1万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.270438517782798
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6287833704615338
    },
    {
        "question": " 7848日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.274953258890634
    },
    {
        "question": " 350日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7024370026227515
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.69兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.487708519683538
    },
    {
        "question": " 107時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6504560437358853
    },
    {
        "question": " 290万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.241090618967709
    },
    {
        "question": " 218時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.89509844169233
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.97億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.87829594451341
    },
    {
        "question": " 6095万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.626588445975691
    },
    {
        "question": " 436万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.861398825229467
    },
    {
        "question": " 6960万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.620782416882793
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.37分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.749861654594675
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.36億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2299773846850959
    },
    {
        "question": " 290億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.526269579980209
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.5万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.91292376212013
    },
    {
        "question": " 1809億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.479369326911668
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.07万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.487311350562522
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.166940120863821
    },
    {
        "question": " 143兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6564862390656137
    },
    {
        "question": " 394兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.659373294918559
    },
    {
        "question": " 31億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9355768881331112
    },
    {
        "question": " 282億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.671487991779465
    },
    {
        "question": " 6515msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8139120331130234
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.930949863817245
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.6兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2618700864467538
    },
    {
        "question": " 497兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.759442297621881
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.750846425842366
    },
    {
        "question": " 168億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.446731050341757
    },
    {
        "question": " 488万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6888120170316026
    },
    {
        "question": " 519億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.7151173144314775
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.39usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.53070751934769
    },
    {
        "question": " 23京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8620716232048387
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.5垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8800119813671525
    },
    {
        "question": " 9529京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4227410547041135
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.554679168576103
    },
    {
        "question": " 407兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.609891651527159
    },
    {
        "question": " 649万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.8119708120608027
    },
    {
        "question": " 8039億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.905211556197619
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.6年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.404932603826067
    },
    {
        "question": " 5740年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.701380075231965
    },
    {
        "question": " 6650年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.543486298878953
    },
    {
        "question": " 579億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.200592373912434
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8062448132386477
    },
    {
        "question": " 1609日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3648469374511105
    },
    {
        "question": " 432日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.571508307682131
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12983519830915613
    },
    {
        "question": " 3545時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1694177698008055
    },
    {
        "question": " 411時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.169629193334444
    },
    {
        "question": " 111万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3235854733560639
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0545693233827147
    },
    {
        "question": " 257億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.632491041437262
    },
    {
        "question": " 6744分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.60705091980969
    },
    {
        "question": " 1137分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.833883944826433
    },
    {
        "question": " 120分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.856108348406554
    },
    {
        "question": " 479兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.181429728177738
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.7万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7329890076360468
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.6万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2335844622384124
    },
    {
        "question": " 355億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.772137240681054
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.49秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.812174867480188
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.65京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.168756776637605
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.5京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.804074388333408
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.96億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.219173471290361
    },
    {
        "question": " 4299万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.855254095105609
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.75万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8895184202276338
    },
    {
        "question": " 6870msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.836934939587174
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.3msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.466796837687495
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.19垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.123669771902113
    },
    {
        "question": " 1840京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.32837954478781
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.5億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23971415175435218
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.3億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5888182450126564
    },
    {
        "question": " 6455万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8099291348254232
    },
    {
        "question": " 2081usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.31826226581088135
    },
    {
        "question": " 122万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.087615744349911
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.5e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.376260798753256
    },
    {
        "question": " 2982垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.538059332374385
    },
    {
        "question": " 8311京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.363369130957805
    },
    {
        "question": " 685億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05766358479661671
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.6京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.895432755979245
    },
    {
        "question": " 198兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.296419692599187
    },
    {
        "question": " 7101万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.851316082414696
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.49万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.104551588655377
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.4万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.920172777834539
    },
    {
        "question": " 6718万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.20742995495345
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.565778852514468
    },
    {
        "question": " 59日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7071728652852505
    },
    {
        "question": " 855億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9896409613891395
    },
    {
        "question": " 720万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.477159628304151
    },
    {
        "question": " 666万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.601780179925111
    },
    {
        "question": " 518時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.270838201101693
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.2億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.137752982060478
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.894121979396903
    },
    {
        "question": " 300分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.699361401476245
    },
    {
        "question": " 214兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.831177390679615
    },
    {
        "question": " 30億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.541127502234541
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.613858215147596
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4895296191348804
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.84秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.894283120174009
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.99垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.977459987587022
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.094129189794908
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.502532057256155
    },
    {
        "question": " 131兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.339958477805208
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.74万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.758890534480274
    },
    {
        "question": " 359万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.554570189889857
    },
    {
        "question": " 266兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9256288038938554
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1455784346166853
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4536400660560194
    },
    {
        "question": " 1467億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.388139304364275
    },
    {
        "question": " 5315万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7254900103406423
    },
    {
        "question": " 120億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.079911673750258
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.58万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.553658195582361
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.41垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.234769428314086
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.7京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.793093870364155
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.2兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2642555942918998
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.2京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.167125207190155
    },
    {
        "question": " 115兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0623061043516575
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.003171072152995
    },
    {
        "question": " 170万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.229474633162045
    },
    {
        "question": " 4877年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.250444616559211
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.9万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.64034281269869
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.15年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.338221747483295
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.703079120734046
    },
    {
        "question": " 2348万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.750887458352155
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.17万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.872166734325137
    },
    {
        "question": " 39億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.648706150926798
    },
    {
        "question": " 618億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.410807797378348
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.015350294995037
    },
    {
        "question": " 8548時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.488161271174483
    },
    {
        "question": " 515兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.991043402801258
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.092065212564044
    },
    {
        "question": " 551分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9628744491107133
    },
    {
        "question": " 8907分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.727886217107125
    },
    {
        "question": " 825億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4177262280721186
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.9万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.01237065262069
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.56億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.18900449313879
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.321394159711591
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.51067455040438
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.4兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.600629305489134
    },
    {
        "question": " 455億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.102085625823383
    },
    {
        "question": " 124億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3144660948663835
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.79億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.578288117358231
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.081312477692617
    },
    {
        "question": " 159msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.202283385581087
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8755901419821015
    },
    {
        "question": " 5859億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8312931055233963
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.474780257172914
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.413959679277127
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.5億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.809560324180088
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.031204215635002
    },
    {
        "question": " 254万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.404110746348094
    },
    {
        "question": " 5381垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.232097204300981
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.245575890339257
    },
    {
        "question": " 368京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.010104081358954
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.392022717738303
    },
    {
        "question": " 3348兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.524816148509993
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.387474791371614
    },
    {
        "question": " 1421nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.15250294277040166
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.7年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.463915194529151
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.1年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.475489349647162
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.19年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.839407849856905
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.4億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.787743311165785
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2865261721051544
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.84万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.390463632030473
    },
    {
        "question": " 266万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4825105296189043
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.5万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.305840269595337
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.785956383974947
    },
    {
        "question": " 124兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.37426855688596
    },
    {
        "question": " 778万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7328485370435605
    },
    {
        "question": " 342億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.755687608379269
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.34万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.580503353783693
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.1分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.527388384960686
    },
    {
        "question": " 4681億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1715456381574025
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.5万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5182088468721713
    },
    {
        "question": " 9344億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.414227135381475
    },
    {
        "question": " 166秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4428386679348273
    },
    {
        "question": " 718秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.856038665637206
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.15756177226405
    },
    {
        "question": " 3995兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.10271172807658
    },
    {
        "question": " 2400億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4436594300847103
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.4億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4233472885567795
    },
    {
        "question": " 448兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.872844812463573
    },
    {
        "question": " 7447万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.871959857137976
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.6msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.618761127828615
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.004657875805728
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.7京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9105367153880612
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.265824420408519
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.8兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.248545671270895
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.44828131326349
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.163113298441907
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.04億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.847640638155159
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.1万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.944783386888286
    },
    {
        "question": " 2788京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9464543069305438
    },
    {
        "question": " 2299兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4249527968081976
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5106972331959481
    },
    {
        "question": " 82京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.135650831985271
    },
    {
        "question": " 312億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4937068413668653
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.308532408979419
    },
    {
        "question": " 25億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.39754657477813
    },
    {
        "question": " 429年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.574476851148782
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.14万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0549638250526145
    },
    {
        "question": " 213万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.708579201050666
    },
    {
        "question": " 1日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1592867705061245
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.176025730350711
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.84兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.510907787724202
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.77万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0620160229047744
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9555160131117573
    },
    {
        "question": " 390万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8700405299889469
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.99万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.795310550419229
    },
    {
        "question": " 589万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.992020305178406
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2753707186229315
    },
    {
        "question": " 8106分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.686978185969803
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.657792714189119
    },
    {
        "question": " 2153億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.396470860455342
    },
    {
        "question": " 1054万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4664499180547814
    },
    {
        "question": " 122秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3068482060660971
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.4京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.032925560198422
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.349805216824349
    },
    {
        "question": " 5134兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.154116511955223
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.558753580550947
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.181767302343716
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.025971163360844
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.59msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.88000534360355
    },
    {
        "question": " 986兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.494877238630814
    },
    {
        "question": " 1599京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.26731277947236
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.4兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7936030704980714
    },
    {
        "question": " 491億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.912623191256708
    },
    {
        "question": " 8388億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.923654079451933
    },
    {
        "question": " 3854usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.5859311181252369
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.193628284439985
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.309e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.618174879692971
    },
    {
        "question": " 1764京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.310068561713982
    },
    {
        "question": " 8502京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3731991105266514
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.68京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.107402040735293
    },
    {
        "question": " 266億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.424426187473038
    },
    {
        "question": " 1154兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.062124911340664
    },
    {
        "question": " 115万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.0594682591744817
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.547967142058715
    },
    {
        "question": " 6990億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.28217493103147
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.64万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2021398143206765
    },
    {
        "question": " 1402日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3050164117483085
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.11兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.909360720167456
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7522367171709625
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.7時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.62132264847176
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.860506274197396
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.35兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.007890977905803
    },
    {
        "question": " 307億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.328945052775145
    },
    {
        "question": " 566億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.974440179207532
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.19分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.281565157678899
    },
    {
        "question": " 9167分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.740360596403859
    },
    {
        "question": " 3263億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0147640922270424
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.97兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.759756549581382
    },
    {
        "question": " 191万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.725635230875545
    },
    {
        "question": " 805秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1274472885129605
    },
    {
        "question": " 140万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.147675123554995
    },
    {
        "question": " 2931秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.466979757873865
    },
    {
        "question": " 9837億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.494070752974641
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.78億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9544431366511386
    },
    {
        "question": " 1708兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.676243260355173
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.609524150510106
    },
    {
        "question": " 498万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.696868772351766
    },
    {
        "question": " 342万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.53425943541569
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.4msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.637263244579765
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.656203732366977
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.406915629225232
    },
    {
        "question": " 198兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.740732403444342
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.3億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.218690278791061
    },
    {
        "question": " 151兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.17886603365062
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.1940532129629045
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.9万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.967921745606336
    },
    {
        "question": " 753京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3779213673578026
    },
    {
        "question": " 2168兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3996119039228805
    },
    {
        "question": " 16兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.648400124634031
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.02垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.826565095945059
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.9兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5914182311727014
    },
    {
        "question": " 123万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.08954538229366427
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.123006538805241
    },
    {
        "question": " 1106億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.481554496224295
    },
    {
        "question": " 4133万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.996495867094128
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.2万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.663185270113701
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.003819097862637
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1917555222040415
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.9億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.42555686341792
    },
    {
        "question": " 2553万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.185149283027464
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.86時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.013005513720181
    },
    {
        "question": " 1948万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5689389612536508
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.1億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.791626749735913
    },
    {
        "question": " 4155億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.840383385100408
    },
    {
        "question": " 6467万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.588847275967055
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.22分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.40386558202488
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.8京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.774574974698751
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.6万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4891041060894985
    },
    {
        "question": " 284万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.89758499667513
    },
    {
        "question": " 3824億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.804387454991762
    },
    {
        "question": " 1099億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5422075532126192
    },
    {
        "question": " 4964億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7593553285419157
    },
    {
        "question": " 122兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.53039589409479
    },
    {
        "question": " 3439万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.75834386186557
    },
    {
        "question": " 568万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7542736484701678
    },
    {
        "question": " 116msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.064057634829247
    },
    {
        "question": " 163垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.714563550909096
    },
    {
        "question": " 9023京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.018828675555362
    },
    {
        "question": " 394兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.039224820904904
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.69兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.789090869211518
    },
    {
        "question": " 9319兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.969378726554497
    },
    {
        "question": " 4047万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.607103404520737
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.647e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.717937783473579
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.5京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.052562373580195
    },
    {
        "question": " 1972京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7385740648842285
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.430620690395656
    },
    {
        "question": " 1806兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.256832279275068
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.0139669284538484
    },
    {
        "question": " 743億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.871223089455235
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.3年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.555045633998215
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.33兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.960003524571633
    },
    {
        "question": " 165日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.596954954554649
    },
    {
        "question": " 264万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.580280137253128
    },
    {
        "question": " 51億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.765040127574289
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.53億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.598804349200378
    },
    {
        "question": " 790万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.675932492835912
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.9時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.552135247368732
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.79兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.959291297374901
    },
    {
        "question": " 2378万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.217779262084145
    },
    {
        "question": " 305万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.706364196514792
    },
    {
        "question": " 715万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.63265715601325
    },
    {
        "question": " 494分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.471819383313354
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.808740515008348
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.3万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4667833289356915
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6047024856233207
    },
    {
        "question": " 324億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.732620308978463
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.1472350704792795
    },
    {
        "question": " 281京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.949566847794701
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.1兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.655815283785216
    },
    {
        "question": " 680万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2761200549589682
    },
    {
        "question": " 26億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.636225397545333
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.85兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.454781194399875
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.240475060825124
    },
    {
        "question": " 30垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.97803212535289
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3066447827483352
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.37京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.415354106525628
    },
    {
        "question": " 1782兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.472761226327553
    },
    {
        "question": " 577億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.761369199162086
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.44万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.809084226091675
    },
    {
        "question": " 7331京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3663522443221616
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.8京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7611396547486518
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.66兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4286080627153799
    },
    {
        "question": " 908京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.180072223755655
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.42京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.733892509922166
    },
    {
        "question": " 134億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.127655946844139
    },
    {
        "question": " 6462万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.810386005756293
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6614728204929623
    },
    {
        "question": " 6606年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.762456398801779
    },
    {
        "question": " 21年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.82044781554413
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.8万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2938775934730637
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.96万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.281149700055209
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.213692960383921
    },
    {
        "question": " 86万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.992132650017594
    },
    {
        "question": " 2123億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.9468115252634
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.14時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.173156066425213
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.43兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.253915131038231
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.67億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.405984334929508
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.47億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.095050009161979
    },
    {
        "question": " 145分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9386206486443
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.987183579394035
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.03億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9828121700857195
    },
    {
        "question": " 9257億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.02996158271218
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.8億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.382074239903265
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6722586051426136
    },
    {
        "question": " 2733秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.436602973604058
    },
    {
        "question": " 3357億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0270888747779894
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.07京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.672870269566694
    },
    {
        "question": " 666兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.266974595385449
    },
    {
        "question": " 7151万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.076211612577757
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.29221653111188
    },
    {
        "question": " 1406msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.1479552585053785
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.09msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.490498279724795
    },
    {
        "question": " 128兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6072224919291669
    },
    {
        "question": " 740京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.932851921461959
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.4兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8237036076439717
    },
    {
        "question": " 139兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.364355196217647
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.1億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9596331078170754
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.039089987695566
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.9usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.690289508148208
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7983849998452497
    },
    {
        "question": " 46垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.726618401778649
    },
    {
        "question": " 9105京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.402957612197677
    },
    {
        "question": " 9032億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1776397902505786
    },
    {
        "question": " 2348億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3707338025876803
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.1兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.724900578608144
    },
    {
        "question": " 9428億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.974442012431972
    },
    {
        "question": " 362年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.501547323813196
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.93億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.905078849887936
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.581024587772424
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.23日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.017279792511493
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.49日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.811237418122039
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19050261105128308
    },
    {
        "question": " 4480万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.271119326442955
    },
    {
        "question": " 157時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9749898887681345
    },
    {
        "question": " 409万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8907887237915812
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0883300147896335
    },
    {
        "question": " 582万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.98670396714112
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.810753509651635
    },
    {
        "question": " 3911分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.370391466276123
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7476401724632118
    },
    {
        "question": " 121億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.147830938542053
    },
    {
        "question": " 6934秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2847063154348739
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.5億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.829472176875878
    },
    {
        "question": " 863秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.935809943271605
    },
    {
        "question": " 490兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.191411842059523
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.49億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8759246733935933
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4896385039805145
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.5兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.088103043699062
    },
    {
        "question": " 171万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2326560074662583
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.24msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.5108342549028615
    },
    {
        "question": " 173京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.740059134866654
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.42京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.797751899108846
    },
    {
        "question": " 320京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.948244965734432
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.1兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.079563367853334
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.325319746202117
    },
    {
        "question": " 532億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.725869508037279
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.2543981934499056
    },
    {
        "question": " 2472垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.894249913995615
    },
    {
        "question": " 5460兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8007086401953032
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.2兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8268982314695406
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.1兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1364225023546966
    },
    {
        "question": " 1524億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.182890258534581
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.52兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.65490902410705
    },
    {
        "question": " 4380万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.641426408476965
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.581686507303771
    },
    {
        "question": " 807年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.6274671712448
    },
    {
        "question": " 137年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.635626451675858
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.1万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.930067937536575
    },
    {
        "question": " 7974日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.281856133012619
    },
    {
        "question": " 7429日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.80740848051471
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.55兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.71506670936512
    },
    {
        "question": " 400億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.22213493696452
    },
    {
        "question": " 8771万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.721206616940512
    },
    {
        "question": " 146万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.720346539909531
    },
    {
        "question": " 189時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.832767775697846
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.7万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.175186145219014
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.92億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.435455483620304
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.350562031275185
    },
    {
        "question": " 6553万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.59461911047024
    },
    {
        "question": " 743分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.649367221736866
    },
    {
        "question": " 916兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.463051170688891
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09134271034709318
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.55737086251106
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.89億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.217044058686134
    },
    {
        "question": " 235秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.370308081281214
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.21秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.506866664231747
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.4兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7407259415937677
    },
    {
        "question": " 11京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.105651989141505
    },
    {
        "question": " 877兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.386565680958068
    },
    {
        "question": " 397億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.820869292221574
    },
    {
        "question": " 1245億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.09520870654904
    },
    {
        "question": " 248msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.3937984381368
    },
    {
        "question": " 21垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.823851965976418
    },
    {
        "question": " 4606兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.726841577646597
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.6兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4260975189825196
    },
    {
        "question": " 683億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0561560144666835
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.1兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.909247879049449
    },
    {
        "question": " 3962usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.5978612802965999
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.4垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.176735481541939
    },
    {
        "question": " 4959垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.758880152282066
    },
    {
        "question": " 6333京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.245323201238017
    },
    {
        "question": " 9039京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.177948703651959
    },
    {
        "question": " 4948億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.694448037723245
    },
    {
        "question": " 348兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.541697540141437
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.42億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.925543614431911
    },
    {
        "question": " 1069万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.591248147838343
    },
    {
        "question": " 862年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.656336317923168
    },
    {
        "question": " 2193日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7788182596926452
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.5日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6921312153128807
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.86日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.152009084870323
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.9兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.99139496780021
    },
    {
        "question": " 5697時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.375418189307219
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.87068929042184
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.61082644134483
    },
    {
        "question": " 718億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.135469460373772
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9213064012372785
    },
    {
        "question": " 1081分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.255753575225379
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.6分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6681338257725207
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.1京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.825819503193845
    },
    {
        "question": " 5245億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.78326273476713
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.2億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.290107922460103
    },
    {
        "question": " 362万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.781155566974293
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.0456648333347056
    },
    {
        "question": " 5341秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.727626366619281
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.01秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.845673137292783
    },
    {
        "question": " 113兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.553188888664618
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.119222448289322
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.9兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.742942255102399
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.575621867008375
    },
    {
        "question": " 5108億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.708248864549802
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.4万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.841571243764568
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.064716422894509
    },
    {
        "question": " 1703兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7323082827635239
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.356671629339427
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.8京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.317864703612853
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.92億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5062800569726056
    },
    {
        "question": " 104万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.01616383845035041
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.087711656402985
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.013188716668855
    },
    {
        "question": " 933垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.470963576204372
    },
    {
        "question": " 668垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.888515666717382
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6044287378390347
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.62垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.971405123875481
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.6京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.512887316751884
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.0077438179344917
    },
    {
        "question": " 8567万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.932853636099322
    },
    {
        "question": " 115年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.624049099067201
    },
    {
        "question": " 526年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.663171315780056
    },
    {
        "question": " 4785年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.40049024551042
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.53万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9850090845061275
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.5日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2524010504733303
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.27万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.451505699264969
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.158099201202221
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.82039843275911
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.991383631576475
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.95兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.277073423732352
    },
    {
        "question": " 2886億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.301972104366179
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.51万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0351236495348157
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.4分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4443751009376156
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.4分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.288999987909699
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.2分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.212600723165117
    },
    {
        "question": " 4695万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1727916399852114
    },
    {
        "question": " 2723万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.498622607470329
    },
    {
        "question": " 1471億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.61140865699176
    },
    {
        "question": " 142億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.373248728314877
    },
    {
        "question": " 4768秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.678321388403639
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.22秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.8587236268716145
    },
    {
        "question": " 5451兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.237637538492256
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.44億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9897090163083677
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.7兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.366645461343899
    },
    {
        "question": " 1995億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5217520302747625
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2193069810154067
    },
    {
        "question": " 158京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.700940067871025
    },
    {
        "question": " 119兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1379346516785365
    },
    {
        "question": " 263億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8637902785280782
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4490883036900428
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.52億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.655233930110853
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.4億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.853670454860705
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.373308100074871
    },
    {
        "question": " 625垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.297332150239766
    },
    {
        "question": " 505兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7668587386863901
    },
    {
        "question": " 191垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.72498610541836
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.46京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.032418362615831
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.34兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8657108094846935
    },
    {
        "question": " 2557万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.4077939628767133
    },
    {
        "question": " 2390nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.3783253764851935
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.301802629885235
    },
    {
        "question": " 281年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.169593624192293
    },
    {
        "question": " 3076日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9256516421507432
    },
    {
        "question": " 5501日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.120656752652373
    },
    {
        "question": " 4641日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.824947023255855
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.9兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.981125347033306
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.57億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.029267668180422
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9988027881383084
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.559936919885475
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.729790697562179
    },
    {
        "question": " 122万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9264084434896787
    },
    {
        "question": " 399分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8233637729453569
    },
    {
        "question": " 5699万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.533916596419314
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.893889346452022
    },
    {
        "question": " 1617兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7097848036981524
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.81兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.745879848627832
    },
    {
        "question": " 1617万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.652341921956266
    },
    {
        "question": " 134万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.349562894902235
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.3秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.794657097789594
    },
    {
        "question": " 138秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.138538280920635
    },
    {
        "question": " 3888億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.090931760348779
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4835552869339743
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.74229130527383
    },
    {
        "question": " 4669億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.891069499524844
    },
    {
        "question": " 137億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.136940720645937
    },
    {
        "question": " 426京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.130420874938863
    },
    {
        "question": " 8505京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.993181301870438
    },
    {
        "question": " 5863兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.211854683933764
    },
    {
        "question": " 2404億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6027558729091735
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.8兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4112112641127545
    },
    {
        "question": " 6108usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.7859325312017107
    },
    {
        "question": " 660usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.819709807249919
    },
    {
        "question": " 5786垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.263543042425942
    },
    {
        "question": " 8524兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9941449911501374
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.7兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0637204683563628
    },
    {
        "question": " 1088億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.25829261811774806
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.8京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.565590375248835
    },
    {
        "question": " 456兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.659421972722123
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.014960506925063
    },
    {
        "question": " 896年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.894808738915766
    },
    {
        "question": " 1244万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.532409253725245
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.403803056581149
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.124163698896016
    },
    {
        "question": " 7772万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.510354366538776
    },
    {
        "question": " 310万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.269927246801645
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.823032687279511
    },
    {
        "question": " 589兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.049106846245827
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.019616965675711
    },
    {
        "question": " 1867分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4929497322714202
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.3分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.273663790238268
    },
    {
        "question": " 8855兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.448374547550166
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.15兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.852598066774733
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.3億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.422694815126455
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.5万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8890840943748484
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.584458646803276
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.31兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.863520309583274
    },
    {
        "question": " 2407兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.825141567194315
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.779455222405236
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.446708203376556
    },
    {
        "question": " 259msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.413911447060492
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.4垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.107988217372162
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.09352940078225
    },
    {
        "question": " 304京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.926455824269881
    },
    {
        "question": " 9710兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.209081091536527
    },
    {
        "question": " 4503万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6535445099461354
    },
    {
        "question": " 135万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.131290850533348
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.5usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.658154603225749
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.3垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.869023028588392
    },
    {
        "question": " 2163京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3985899193040146
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.9垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.105303244494028
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3641548817343603
    },
    {
        "question": " 249億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3959433092013152
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.065569305876046
    },
    {
        "question": " 1782億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.250835907592654
    },
    {
        "question": " 1981万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.859205619607323
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.41年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.231915868403144
    },
    {
        "question": " 7603億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.318691920080928
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.2日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.717330623557468
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.89日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.833749713717157
    },
    {
        "question": " 105億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.077342692976538
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.56億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.028016521601322
    },
    {
        "question": " 179万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.030140620998775
    },
    {
        "question": " 183時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.818249789911862
    },
    {
        "question": " 252万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6804453266426214
    },
    {
        "question": " 1583分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04114547246581668
    },
    {
        "question": " 4997億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.920557091533345
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.1万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.511580854266461
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.44分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.513909391263686
    },
    {
        "question": " 154億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6892605729785792
    },
    {
        "question": " 110億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.104596879100648
    },
    {
        "question": " 1262億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.544632651062701
    },
    {
        "question": " 2584億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.6341696270249
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.2秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.30624525229438
    },
    {
        "question": " 1666京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.722822433455542
    },
    {
        "question": " 7683兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.949031057106137
    },
    {
        "question": " 445兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.092410012594422
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.8万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6653228051803783
    },
    {
        "question": " 53億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.724659263943224
    },
    {
        "question": " 5096兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2084080080778024
    },
    {
        "question": " 894億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.01499563982824803
    },
    {
        "question": " 347京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.98454548581957
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.488038423467584
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2987609697570655
    },
    {
        "question": " 113万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.053880300047229
    },
    {
        "question": " 129万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.111780415085416
    },
    {
        "question": " 156京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.694988866381354
    },
    {
        "question": " 109兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10080571169227559
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.94兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03900723603411427
    },
    {
        "question": " 9726億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2097866164949966
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.085893479455596
    },
    {
        "question": " 326兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.513030395093178
    },
    {
        "question": " 3308nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.5195362230335288
    },
    {
        "question": " 538万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.293146590166103
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.8年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.209842363002781
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.1万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1200314569196843
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.2万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.166910148018927
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.3日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.525888502839326
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.75万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.510606536105053
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.1万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7485416678569587
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.848980533415515
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.83万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.72392452024893
    },
    {
        "question": " 478億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.958487564157991
    },
    {
        "question": " 1034万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8559924338498917
    },
    {
        "question": " 1415万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.372482517109818
    },
    {
        "question": " 13万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.892124657972878
    },
    {
        "question": " 881分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.722894134574893
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.6分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.689660625075689
    },
    {
        "question": " 176億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.746097199745355
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.4万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0563247237100615
    },
    {
        "question": " 1347万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5729493703539505
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5572072564589887
    },
    {
        "question": " 672万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.827445984267966
    },
    {
        "question": " 2127秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.327773398605412
    },
    {
        "question": " 550京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.24146547369483
    },
    {
        "question": " 4693兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7349942376144245
    },
    {
        "question": " 862億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.379362331374085
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.58兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9688364339148325
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.02兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.603999195975213
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.00523792780981
    },
    {
        "question": " 4774msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.678889190729977
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.94京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.096449353343714
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.4兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.911065281598698
    },
    {
        "question": " 435京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.082549348151357
    },
    {
        "question": " 3173億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7233403397791545
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1182875483572303
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.94兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.841571575122327
    },
    {
        "question": " 841京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4258488483227425
    },
    {
        "question": " 793垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.962663787455796
    },
    {
        "question": " 240垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.82448372277968
    },
    {
        "question": " 222兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.567441106393421
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.5兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.562557258578833
    },
    {
        "question": " 8230兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.915426085055504
    },
    {
        "question": " 3418億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.53379101100071
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.573654522147203
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.9万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2221006318782077
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5546881747653565
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3535086428426286
    },
    {
        "question": " 1818億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.317134063893057
    },
    {
        "question": " 4991万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.317989211319134
    },
    {
        "question": " 744万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.649620314560513
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.6万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.131910811440576
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.580403021865604
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.2億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.813749052695595
    },
    {
        "question": " 4兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.443815897097851
    },
    {
        "question": " 175分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4651386304878202
    },
    {
        "question": " 2453万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.167770437237886
    },
    {
        "question": " 125分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.8756650117952836
    },
    {
        "question": " 30分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.25576144512798
    },
    {
        "question": " 3522万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04799470449909693
    },
    {
        "question": " 140万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.211151198562177
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.29兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.075868735699999
    },
    {
        "question": " 477万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.900346172326749
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.054856294368669
    },
    {
        "question": " 564億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2526303258453988
    },
    {
        "question": " 254億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4681636298067233
    },
    {
        "question": " 565兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.195988787775804
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.19億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.562319010087273
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.368830039143109
    },
    {
        "question": " 3222兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.009320994426135
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3522378546440703
    },
    {
        "question": " 4466億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.093623169386558
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.490605272453192
    },
    {
        "question": " 697億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.842963826715451
    },
    {
        "question": " 2435usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.3864767227102961
    },
    {
        "question": " 31usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.491054770954816
    },
    {
        "question": " 5603垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.249585488933906
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.55京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7216905259564173
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.5垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.303867218435867
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3512225456936366
    },
    {
        "question": " 809兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9081248157525685
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.2億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.8275473238126247
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.006175833043812
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.02年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.867121987092643
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.606450986262786
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.544752958910813
    },
    {
        "question": " 2635日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.800919227592743
    },
    {
        "question": " 4702日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.830602563484193
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.252244133315651
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.030658335646653
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.8億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.452402862680049
    },
    {
        "question": " 654億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.435142417009747
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8003483122481243
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.34時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.358520892829106
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.306410678436459
    },
    {
        "question": " 200億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.143647549114272
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.4億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.70525149579289
    },
    {
        "question": " 4015分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.381817420797948
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.841112775029147
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.7分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.30543683221638
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.98京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.403186154633609
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.4兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.59508261297648
    },
    {
        "question": " 692万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2838636365008345
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.321755851068721
    },
    {
        "question": " 923万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.965109921568787
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5533685735095712
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.72兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.634099548524916
    },
    {
        "question": " 4653万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1114659727493492
    },
    {
        "question": " 6812億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.055155257412159
    },
    {
        "question": " 604万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7812505188251455
    },
    {
        "question": " 779万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.89144525522891
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.6京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.925354289148517
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.8兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9869921267080324
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.73兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.014873279762126
    },
    {
        "question": " 1160兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.286360299212426
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0305821125736303
    },
    {
        "question": " 1420万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.152201207604649
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.02usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.7003322666178287
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.315e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.865815068510339
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.63京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.813628155429421
    },
    {
        "question": " 7376兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3115303487190797
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.78兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9011984091439227
    },
    {
        "question": " 449兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6520010030636065
    },
    {
        "question": " 170兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.230744968139799
    },
    {
        "question": " 130万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.113081152599727
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.69万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.23307979713522
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.214981726874978
    },
    {
        "question": " 119年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.796255756681214
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.09年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.818666176933685
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.52兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.838491404828456
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.68万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1345276421999255
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.330100033948372
    },
    {
        "question": " 170万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2886760244447215
    },
    {
        "question": " 384億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.204557456567926
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.8時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.602788165471935
    },
    {
        "question": " 3112兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.772387617862519
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.87万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4296319513797606
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.3万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9949066859392737
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.55分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6562257084335217
    },
    {
        "question": " 403兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.105999545140844
    },
    {
        "question": " 455万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7219701053528313
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.77億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.886298715441669
    },
    {
        "question": " 628秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0195240236164937
    },
    {
        "question": " 303万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.481564334852761
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7160148594737565
    },
    {
        "question": " 6億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8416309279281864
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.87億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.280736396996571
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.02万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06830494205302684
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.31万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.863748807635378
    },
    {
        "question": " 883msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.946138984144289
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.99msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.69767749649428
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7968587634672755
    },
    {
        "question": " 25京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.461738168614453
    },
    {
        "question": " 250億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8410831879471881
    },
    {
        "question": " 978兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.212333166234907
    },
    {
        "question": " 6223万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7939862767403503
    },
    {
        "question": " 98万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.991014112132606
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.4204653966928813
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6679794184974674
    },
    {
        "question": " 6670京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.88762580357886
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.47京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9837832064157244
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.55京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.879920620814813
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.090430320660051
    },
    {
        "question": " 277万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.4424641117917394
    },
    {
        "question": " 6214nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.7933899841509795
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.92万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.027634185188343
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.206052548339525
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.9年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.526165095539485
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.5年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.968804808011079
    },
    {
        "question": " 1934億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.724217614445761
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.19億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.7198595184417
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.208922495037424
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.1日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.866358810287757
    },
    {
        "question": " 4801億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.738791736130894
    },
    {
        "question": " 2339万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.988914439886095
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.31時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.190710704527529
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.4兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.267897709146792
    },
    {
        "question": " 152億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.022175838300449
    },
    {
        "question": " 1134万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.276637519367569
    },
    {
        "question": " 648分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.589567603882231
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.56億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.052221239991501
    },
    {
        "question": " 395億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.660040233888729
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.6万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9831582346583099
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.44億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.093441615553756
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.65万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.984597485858734
    },
    {
        "question": " 1333秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.124674559696661
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.572121961653211
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.15京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.682068685451714
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.68兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.382365347995598
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.4億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.782543190093801
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.246579597127225
    },
    {
        "question": " 563兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2518434794065658
    },
    {
        "question": " 8291京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.982119550990962
    },
    {
        "question": " 3691億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0108784878491215
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.28兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.083868007069315
    },
    {
        "question": " 306万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4850472381655968
    },
    {
        "question": " 176万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.244925769366737
    },
    {
        "question": " 401万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.603080661148862
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.798031855856735
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.266705230603872
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.6兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3959232816516043
    },
    {
        "question": " 1361億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3558050530538859
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.9億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2999019359110344
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.1億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.8520850181166555
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.468186730722852
    },
    {
        "question": " 705年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.410390117244114
    },
    {
        "question": " 9304年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.911181970885021
    },
    {
        "question": " 1072年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.750742971611453
    },
    {
        "question": " 296万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9094920685399126
    },
    {
        "question": " 3628万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.939910759486159
    },
    {
        "question": " 1736日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.17607540370953
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3262508206579038
    },
    {
        "question": " 496万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.315176641356913
    },
    {
        "question": " 3663万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.341952977017252
    },
    {
        "question": " 4749時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.232943570060328
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.853340851133318
    },
    {
        "question": " 538兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.009822805773803
    },
    {
        "question": " 2010万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.144928721538288
    },
    {
        "question": " 1777分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4715474863332234
    },
    {
        "question": " 256万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.186337016026755
    },
    {
        "question": " 4022分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.382603910164114
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.629430228185455
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4793233163517012
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.54億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.187173087569402
    },
    {
        "question": " 593秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9947228512199457
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.07秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.783468920311015
    },
    {
        "question": " 329京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.018557555444252
    },
    {
        "question": " 6048億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8450842417565556
    },
    {
        "question": " 1565兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.638244244131082
    },
    {
        "question": " 28億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.669283392994447
    },
    {
        "question": " 1034msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.014455411680991404
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.048038440674532
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.5427934958148
    },
    {
        "question": " 162垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.709803703179002
    },
    {
        "question": " 3552兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.613976728544461
    },
    {
        "question": " 2212京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.788526285703975
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.94億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5100500414825704
    },
    {
        "question": " 3278億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5156186234765805
    },
    {
        "question": " 2922万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.46574733426481
    },
    {
        "question": " 127usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.10532193324487
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.38垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3062633842278615
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.1京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4796354725862977
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.534853630804858
    },
    {
        "question": " 828兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.140036995221684
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.6兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.353608860948767
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.38兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.641214671188904
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.07億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.610041919702028
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.69676096079093
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.420995314942132
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.2年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.324538022266016
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.783989029757908
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.56億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.096416507208485
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.94日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.153961526483471
    },
    {
        "question": " 119日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.23570568074067
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.7日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.605904321427732
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.3万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.41887479759567525
    },
    {
        "question": " 1637万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.833759533374109
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.758495171218895
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.88時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.829990534341848
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.317223751859529
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.5万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.736504430215694
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.406461458668421
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.1分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.534924257724134
    },
    {
        "question": " 737億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3686922453698354
    },
    {
        "question": " 840兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.987763990463254
    },
    {
        "question": " 9004秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3981483351887005
    },
    {
        "question": " 969秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2079775343191124
    },
    {
        "question": " 292万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.465610624165365
    },
    {
        "question": " 6807秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.832972383853722
    },
    {
        "question": " 2891兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.962233123345879
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.19億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.566805352689892
    },
    {
        "question": " 7424億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.314333464711685
    },
    {
        "question": " 289兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.683496776928044
    },
    {
        "question": " 3006万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.477969723912874
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.14msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.910641416288531
    },
    {
        "question": " 301兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9796327783900272
    },
    {
        "question": " 6774億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8943625392121612
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.69京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.010168167396947
    },
    {
        "question": " 8115万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1311206688727229
    },
    {
        "question": " 650万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8127361378561582
    },
    {
        "question": " 279万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.445055616081827
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.178142438362636
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.441e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.888705141429305
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.04垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.765572500642688
    },
    {
        "question": " 846兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3711405496868276
    },
    {
        "question": " 7699兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.108301838074344
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.2京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.305531015271155
    },
    {
        "question": " 147兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.167552240978345
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.9億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.850645382809218
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.3万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.272779136845207
    },
    {
        "question": " 12年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.578088847296941
    },
    {
        "question": " 275万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.87641625051405
    },
    {
        "question": " 174万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.621976223696333
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3898954378143635
    },
    {
        "question": " 1694万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2864688836592473
    },
    {
        "question": " 344時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1561284455940934
    },
    {
        "question": " 118時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.850824118517975
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.8兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.76755653734976
    },
    {
        "question": " 6276万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.639299799371738
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.290667585988445
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.14分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.395539201328951
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.0606521488980425
    },
    {
        "question": " 177兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.748479113425757
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.15億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5620625163112143
    },
    {
        "question": " 2943万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.912495830089332
    },
    {
        "question": " 239万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.600106826117505
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.697247546440508
    },
    {
        "question": " 154秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.187604123608041
    },
    {
        "question": " 1549億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6913461308777591
    },
    {
        "question": " 161億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.270841848126884
    },
    {
        "question": " 8666万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3815133085883702
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.6万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1058477104975706
    },
    {
        "question": " 1745億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.241806335483584
    },
    {
        "question": " 102京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.511845091705435
    },
    {
        "question": " 43京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.697128285392717
    },
    {
        "question": " 1949京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.733417111283778
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.9兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.034373883405273
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1357142907919764
    },
    {
        "question": " 6701億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.826138945193406
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.3usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.386021574115553
    },
    {
        "question": " 112垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.550721550384653
    },
    {
        "question": " 6055兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8456452695138736
    },
    {
        "question": " 946京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.41950305469945
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.7兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.664707339110479
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.48兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.928342172728967
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.63兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.935910270591403
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.5万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.6527829140029549
    },
    {
        "question": " 9002年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.516632855606219
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.2億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.368331700221644
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.2万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.608915219239075
    },
    {
        "question": " 42日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.559915289942111
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.2兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.363514006866854
    },
    {
        "question": " 1522億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.802211524384619
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.9万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.191403206878881
    },
    {
        "question": " 160時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.7595769432769
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.1億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.229420253365533
    },
    {
        "question": " 334万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.364869529356622
    },
    {
        "question": " 1786分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4737830556805964
    },
    {
        "question": " 1017兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.508313003662406
    },
    {
        "question": " 7850億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.958387788948465
    },
    {
        "question": " 116億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.509227590629782
    },
    {
        "question": " 1060億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.246998456977922
    },
    {
        "question": " 1087秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.03626584236003
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8729759734154356
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.39454802673905
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.76億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8838525204744605
    },
    {
        "question": " 534兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.949135595769151
    },
    {
        "question": " 691万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.839373208647312
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.4msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.910881547057815
    },
    {
        "question": " 23京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.863634443308058
    },
    {
        "question": " 554京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.80666684418777
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.4兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.176149598092194
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.4兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.057116135931663
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.8兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.967531747547259
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.2万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.8275773783046656
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.1usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.881457691532429
    },
    {
        "question": " 293垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.968719153155325
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4342380390951166
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.1垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.842684418692041
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.374389893825049
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.5兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.889083321116903
    },
    {
        "question": " 1079兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.032839805028368
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.34万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.9212758703128152
    },
    {
        "question": " 158年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.761348589653215
    },
    {
        "question": " 1707年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.174777694753848
    },
    {
        "question": " 1057日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.46180731172712153
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.32万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.746211201554981
    },
    {
        "question": " 159万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.360897532247346
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.36日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.90769149092666
    },
    {
        "question": " 4534億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.714018684043332
    },
    {
        "question": " 441億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.264337519897403
    },
    {
        "question": " 1067万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.806259345936715
    },
    {
        "question": " 8348万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2009409389631864
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.43兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.712488074904794
    },
    {
        "question": " 2394億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.600927952936301
    },
    {
        "question": " 191万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.05978064253811
    },
    {
        "question": " 2131億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.829739283887148
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.63億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8848274468186847
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.87万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0311828856656724
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.6億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.871056619726931
    },
    {
        "question": " 4073秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.609873214210211
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.141744874567989
    },
    {
        "question": " 9080億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4592867208256821
    },
    {
        "question": " 57兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.819331138388634
    },
    {
        "question": " 3399兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.975039235002805
    },
    {
        "question": " 2692万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6519985394622427
    },
    {
        "question": " 103万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0122360816001637
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.89垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.091211425370082
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0919058897721032
    },
    {
        "question": " 2059億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7573698752065003
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.54兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.878607207412119
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0173346857346734
    },
    {
        "question": " 2164usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.3352035916870022
    },
    {
        "question": " 239垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.87941149683658
    },
    {
        "question": " 228兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4211879838791943
    },
    {
        "question": " 2271兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7998357361066537
    },
    {
        "question": " 5106兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.929936485134501
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.12京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.960111397636399
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.660658109218859
    },
    {
        "question": " 4655万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.667899641584724
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.13年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.057464330666239
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.41万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.324442959046326
    },
    {
        "question": " 633年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.5218814300152
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.96万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0349368249558255
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.99万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.634301787463324
    },
    {
        "question": " 21日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.258931473107989
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.2万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5084886573411183
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.7時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49320752601374473
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.075750514206682
    },
    {
        "question": " 199時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.854262264094416
    },
    {
        "question": " 732億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.143738297750049
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.158028429226739
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.9万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9770242508157794
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.204334613586515
    },
    {
        "question": " 168分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.002588946851241
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.9億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1818524109084625
    },
    {
        "question": " 5821万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8285329896652076
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.696697418963092
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.02万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.067991823986712
    },
    {
        "question": " 266秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.424873643874274
    },
    {
        "question": " 186秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.270044178784685
    },
    {
        "question": " 1886兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.776834765125643
    },
    {
        "question": " 303兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.544842010310273
    },
    {
        "question": " 1589万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6448691212503255
    },
    {
        "question": " 3125億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.716730335452533
    },
    {
        "question": " 57万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.755847395347767
    },
    {
        "question": " 512msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.708871474071572
    },
    {
        "question": " 2395垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.880503978503224
    },
    {
        "question": " 125兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1589993674301486
    },
    {
        "question": " 932兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.413144906049925
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.33兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.14269151826357
    },
    {
        "question": " 134万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12655673398048073
    },
    {
        "question": " 10億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.00142727645697
    },
    {
        "question": " 1236usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.091903257394352
    },
    {
        "question": " 2926垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.967494130496361
    },
    {
        "question": " 2082兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3820821251448878
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.8垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.248260735636086
    },
    {
        "question": " 9852京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.215380384704954
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.46京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.390081029602924
    },
    {
        "question": " 3971億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.598913674418835
    },
    {
        "question": " 3306nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.5193088851482786
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.808742670184899
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.5日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1549604575718773
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.45日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.968031593165887
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.002879468193523
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.352703112324324
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23635520441662283
    },
    {
        "question": " 1303時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7347591819323116
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.68時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4482776673771403
    },
    {
        "question": " 569時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.311209042165546
    },
    {
        "question": " 335時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.081301733062073
    },
    {
        "question": " 3023兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.75984923181466
    },
    {
        "question": " 3385分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3711770042066109
    },
    {
        "question": " 637分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0257599084216718
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.137134967143012
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.151778950166531
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.68億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9297181437281654
    },
    {
        "question": " 428兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.695173041431048
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.27億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.165556286396104
    },
    {
        "question": " 877億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.164772634169955
    },
    {
        "question": " 3193秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.504265108084434
    },
    {
        "question": " 199京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.800964361262065
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.4億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5161285711208161
    },
    {
        "question": " 3958億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.041176090351942
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.56万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10047362524391645
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2430029985685231
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.131422860064717
    },
    {
        "question": " 310msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.491489870559178
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6594369521121295
    },
    {
        "question": " 201兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.366586980438273
    },
    {
        "question": " 1500兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.61988814503399
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.30639568122703
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2866597416761367
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.8億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.670301673780586
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.71万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.756457631002781
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.838e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.765626693201494
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.8垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.062678591665918
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.95垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.138089970338529
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.490108027210062
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.5億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8483236185585918
    },
    {
        "question": " 167億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.221736083399427
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.204732896539564
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.564692531381891
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.6万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.332926063677743
    },
    {
        "question": " 117億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.507559890017609
    },
    {
        "question": " 395日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.755340300125629
    },
    {
        "question": " 452日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.591788813321964
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.7万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4679602857635188
    },
    {
        "question": " 146億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.783343847526178
    },
    {
        "question": " 1674時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.001798646101795
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.929365398517545
    },
    {
        "question": " 4908兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.970243121226366
    },
    {
        "question": " 5688万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5965805717663475
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.7分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07109520919636902
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.4万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.275075731761589
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.5分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.514276163608976
    },
    {
        "question": " 274億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.938757719325884
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.4兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.516537784399098
    },
    {
        "question": " 375万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0181188832806916
    },
    {
        "question": " 1537万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.408636393475961
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.4万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.86576429293861
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.695249535419649
    },
    {
        "question": " 204兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.372142642667342
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.09京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.934339865674195
    },
    {
        "question": " 373億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.793308917833721
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.06兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.906230455756829
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.2京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.124084992088311
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.187210182997946
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.6兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.253862579438672
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.4億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2102645008664465
    },
    {
        "question": " 142億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.152101372942835
    },
    {
        "question": " 1710万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.23289778339816
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.17usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.9623923215182764
    },
    {
        "question": " 2524垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.903277319140576
    },
    {
        "question": " 41京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6765946981603137
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.7垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.371763302719483
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.3京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.074814451705387
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.335060510149809
    },
    {
        "question": " 287億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.457506850914736
    },
    {
        "question": " 266万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.425651158922558
    },
    {
        "question": " 1092年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.600511595981269
    },
    {
        "question": " 536年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.671546839072987
    },
    {
        "question": " 4969年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.416887122064022
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.5万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.076502635126931
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6308075735638603
    },
    {
        "question": " 735日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.024348093216826
    },
    {
        "question": " 1936万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.344513205487911
    },
    {
        "question": " 5478万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.358449808679994
    },
    {
        "question": " 1453時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.940453388097621
    },
    {
        "question": " 101億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.284955771480358
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.849615230185625
    },
    {
        "question": " 165億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.439235423419541
    },
    {
        "question": " 1006分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.780740011387939
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.6分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.38717717102306
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.82兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.184264072077406
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19946351990201228
    },
    {
        "question": " 1億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4447676708352235
    },
    {
        "question": " 8462秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.149323349008939
    },
    {
        "question": " 172万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.236765188465416
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.04垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.80989173908138
    },
    {
        "question": " 2542億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4687519771318396
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.577966448345174
    },
    {
        "question": " 1081万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.255579841680201
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.65兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.56272757058173
    },
    {
        "question": " 8804京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.44587020768845
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.73京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.951584812272434
    },
    {
        "question": " 3142億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9409199058259685
    },
    {
        "question": " 478億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.901674288635813
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.24億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.351063746609828
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.59兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.933972612110633
    },
    {
        "question": " 930usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.968609728361988
    },
    {
        "question": " 973京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4891297726317108
    },
    {
        "question": " 543京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.798125548116026
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.594244982403232
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.38749596308988
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.96京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.952512523790062
    },
    {
        "question": " 15億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.1771740217639666
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.51億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.545043772066375
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.7万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.791975451939658
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.5万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7901406859457545
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.27万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.880155553123776
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.88万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3319185897696775
    },
    {
        "question": " 315時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.118325715335431
    },
    {
        "question": " 220万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.121354536764693
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.090018579397956
    },
    {
        "question": " 207兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.5949462913257
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.862382384269429
    },
    {
        "question": " 715万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.076146807924072
    },
    {
        "question": " 126万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.879589754403343
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.945547712916178
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.47兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.89366180967453
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.6兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.800447044683077
    },
    {
        "question": " 1997億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.743983614381614
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.32億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.947662989506378
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.28秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3577316504084473
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.2秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.505251350681274
    },
    {
        "question": " 2534億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9049220825158266
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.085792534733926
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.29億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0762142068154468
    },
    {
        "question": " 642万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.029131423447331
    },
    {
        "question": " 150万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1768680216237777
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.307162826168261
    },
    {
        "question": " 1779京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.751426252398502
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.6京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.860260842309489
    },
    {
        "question": " 5235兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.162590787145923
    },
    {
        "question": " 36兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.778378322951832
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.94兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.595024792515658
    },
    {
        "question": " 4146億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.61761143197337
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.09usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.70700492860868
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.74355237072308
    },
    {
        "question": " 964兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0475371545485113
    },
    {
        "question": " 5029兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.145183089086573
    },
    {
        "question": " 1038京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.237893346888775
    },
    {
        "question": " 6346億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.802480406069038
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.1億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7166414225202926
    },
    {
        "question": " 1073万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.030769877623797
    },
    {
        "question": " 266年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9877124228304615
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.4万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.645004320891438
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.6年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.055696459137986
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.884344539012233
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.4万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8527940462549053
    },
    {
        "question": " 147億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.786412708579952
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.031671562607987
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.60684685066191
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.774129385911696
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.423613855408587
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.42万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2247130126597616
    },
    {
        "question": " 4523億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.877260358084097
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.78分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.540294457446608
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.925959479340603
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.1京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.735328718704832
    },
    {
        "question": " 678万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8945903418741195
    },
    {
        "question": " 2604億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.859320310960422
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.8億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.801261617330701
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.5万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.728712311607008
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.48秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.542114936209656
    },
    {
        "question": " 6514億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3150150964771212
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.1億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.541482011681169
    },
    {
        "question": " 407兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.053579823071074
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.7万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1598046253426098
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.287841913975759
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.55393809848655
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.02兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5440871759531671
    },
    {
        "question": " 530京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.168284340569548
    },
    {
        "question": " 11京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.261609508937894
    },
    {
        "question": " 221億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3451521651811085
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.259780219490039
    },
    {
        "question": " 228usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.357047541117371
    },
    {
        "question": " 559垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.248693372445957
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.5京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.460796950103794
    },
    {
        "question": " 1354京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.575431597999865
    },
    {
        "question": " 4456億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8708148568529339
    },
    {
        "question": " 1723兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.236225153442586
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.65億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.423794027064826
    },
    {
        "question": " 7429億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.870940098916137
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.95万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.336832318553709
    },
    {
        "question": " 6013日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2168104675079827
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.7日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8946912123562774
    },
    {
        "question": " 298億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.53176030029682
    },
    {
        "question": " 1405億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.767552952911561
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.5万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.374859544020305
    },
    {
        "question": " 217万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6165821492689438
    },
    {
        "question": " 3000分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3187303842192779
    },
    {
        "question": " 260億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.636424599382169
    },
    {
        "question": " 39万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.368784040191207
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.817247778730889
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.5分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.374767237656727
    },
    {
        "question": " 5720兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.258607229412133
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.4兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.00505981168397
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.710509457137393
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.3万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4848823804994
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.6万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.618886113461533
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.36兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2303078389930464
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31227296391168835
    },
    {
        "question": " 4904億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.134258913465285
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.11億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.835881884512423
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1295507703615149
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.0971064541296105
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.745972392590834
    },
    {
        "question": " 5318億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7892843368392766
    },
    {
        "question": " 1486兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.615679304827324
    },
    {
        "question": " 14兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.366572722051412
    },
    {
        "question": " 1140億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.056902725432461
    },
    {
        "question": " 1499万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.175937962622766
    },
    {
        "question": " 1955垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.792255768686632
    },
    {
        "question": " 6018兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8429783651492038
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.2兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3425413339474135
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.8京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.665610861317873
    },
    {
        "question": " 123兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.089965867283302
    },
    {
        "question": " 234兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.369465760271236
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.98億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.9533466311604
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.5万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.54016603872675
    },
    {
        "question": " 5527年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.685014133698619
    },
    {
        "question": " 15万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.613329137062829
    },
    {
        "question": " 196日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.227749035041928
    },
    {
        "question": " 352億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.604130798651017
    },
    {
        "question": " 464億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.286549199566899
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.66万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.446297091642052
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.75時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.995221901650189
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.97時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.850668070570281
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.1兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.229305091777881
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.36兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.645187952230884
    },
    {
        "question": " 343分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7567309313693471
    },
    {
        "question": " 895万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.729861186344563
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.7分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.645353116225126
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.95京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.196059312018017
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.91兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.754321241933965
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.02億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.923588948200965
    },
    {
        "question": " 3204万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.727487073530943
    },
    {
        "question": " 490億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19174778103237755
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.1京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.480775991393768
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.96億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.138997329988256
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.406048021506356
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1273477093855044
    },
    {
        "question": " 260万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.414353895197028
    },
    {
        "question": " 4430msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.646413120286581
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.72京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3283566925865484
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.7兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0062795115710306
    },
    {
        "question": " 285億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8986981286473594
    },
    {
        "question": " 507億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9265107688215197
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0605491919570165
    },
    {
        "question": " 977万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.9896909693120843
    },
    {
        "question": " 266万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.425658685682198
    },
    {
        "question": " 3003京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.978813710737036
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.07垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.846970704975236
    },
    {
        "question": " 136垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.575969474541077
    },
    {
        "question": " 2970京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.694596195381937
    },
    {
        "question": " 643京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.808545680625393
    },
    {
        "question": " 42億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6234486555861145
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.435749507191913
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.64万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.384310254848878
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.138816341070328
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.681129152471858
    },
    {
        "question": " 2894日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.841709518798071
    },
    {
        "question": " 1457日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3217863782521295
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.103205764051707
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3021123017638949
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.2万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.265368287900405
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.6万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2197730746577715
    },
    {
        "question": " 1721時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.792182593899831
    },
    {
        "question": " 3761兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.854694481060694
    },
    {
        "question": " 1645分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05768552621577827
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.1万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8354578985161627
    },
    {
        "question": " 142分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9294128528974026
    },
    {
        "question": " 1991億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.800295721394258
    },
    {
        "question": " 125万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1598461870376064
    },
    {
        "question": " 141億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.591893790486215
    },
    {
        "question": " 127万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.325839065789637
    },
    {
        "question": " 2678億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9289693382984399
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.55京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.613536091326187
    },
    {
        "question": " 1935億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.730461462908249
    },
    {
        "question": " 7835万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.115881499989742
    },
    {
        "question": " 1455万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.162972380601907
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.4万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.869148712537547
    },
    {
        "question": " 1818msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.259705924240727
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.9京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.278467327797779
    },
    {
        "question": " 205京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.374260821171222
    },
    {
        "question": " 1258億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5433941759018632
    },
    {
        "question": " 211億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.546525769561044
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0849434217756877
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.1296437221098743
    },
    {
        "question": " 338usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.529098349827958
    },
    {
        "question": " 808垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.40874342212787
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.9京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.007455551629392
    },
    {
        "question": " 318兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9457713546917965
    },
    {
        "question": " 4956京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.916989284558566
    },
    {
        "question": " 202億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3058393800840007
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.182446388892629
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.15万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.9613948488135646
    },
    {
        "question": " 577万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.323293530781907
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.07万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.429601875363637
    },
    {
        "question": " 3725年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.291811550756442
    },
    {
        "question": " 4990億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.13576900350457
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.9日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.913210315642054
    },
    {
        "question": " 9102日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.895656309513257
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.137142525975227
    },
    {
        "question": " 3403万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.151695220193317
    },
    {
        "question": " 7505時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.653506599068844
    },
    {
        "question": " 988時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5509266094425564
    },
    {
        "question": " 54億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.011579507457419
    },
    {
        "question": " 2099分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16368593115946073
    },
    {
        "question": " 6199分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.01416318738867
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.3万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.586593964700324
    },
    {
        "question": " 914億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.461975355845511
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2041626488173636
    },
    {
        "question": " 649億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.255623553834614
    },
    {
        "question": " 1451万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.383558107417535
    },
    {
        "question": " 880秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.944353559670882
    },
    {
        "question": " 6001億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2794558083587315
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3265090722737751
    },
    {
        "question": " 1506万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6213885212079462
    },
    {
        "question": " 21万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5438008939662853
    },
    {
        "question": " 9611万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.982773702588821
    },
    {
        "question": " 308msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.48882966881729
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.591259226543885
    },
    {
        "question": " 14兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.210104520457458
    },
    {
        "question": " 582兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2087889966258425
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.51兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.097298263965304
    },
    {
        "question": " 9269兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.96705072165416
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.2075060083792177
    },
    {
        "question": " 243万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.385158706292891
    },
    {
        "question": " 658京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3197209453035628
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.7兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0490333465519599
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.786634658032126
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.4兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.031068706077341
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06543685396224519
    },
    {
        "question": " 674億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.828857756698902
    },
    {
        "question": " 1791万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.252992231938551
    },
    {
        "question": " 3077年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.050377717697617
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.9万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.403317544972783
    },
    {
        "question": " 370万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.005902222732071
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.55日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1382413320026625
    },
    {
        "question": " 1948億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.347084045235538
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.669259016017862
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.35時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1491897426788986
    },
    {
        "question": " 3565万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8313632029818083
    },
    {
        "question": " 129億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.952818800267644
    },
    {
        "question": " 105万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.24454927616167
    },
    {
        "question": " 294万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.24638180259248
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.4分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.4974437032399806
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.29兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.01799106231199
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.61億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.726944131052765
    },
    {
        "question": " 252億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.84566506341662
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.94億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.510385801086058
    },
    {
        "question": " 1180秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.071793866581849
    },
    {
        "question": " 350秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.54374062545481
    },
    {
        "question": " 6801億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3338015536042291
    },
    {
        "question": " 601兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.842564221360337
    },
    {
        "question": " 8842万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3902442626534106
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.5億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.611198211760476
    },
    {
        "question": " 291億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.46368132097645
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.9msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.578860853816634
    },
    {
        "question": " 308msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.489034687881523
    },
    {
        "question": " 1202兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5812125913545816
    },
    {
        "question": " 2468京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.455800230528238
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.547820328100584
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.326601875553329
    },
    {
        "question": " 129万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11159413949902164
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.97万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.4722377026417988
    },
    {
        "question": " 163京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7124892234797096
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0939141498449088
    },
    {
        "question": " 1170京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.511918040343627
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.7兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8311239649201303
    },
    {
        "question": " 2744兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.438370290646126
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.640978098203305
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.86兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.76785893890388
    },
    {
        "question": " 1143万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.620340486302164
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.06万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.791335809998692
    },
    {
        "question": " 748万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3113200568591425
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.19896284617842
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.52兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.988161329761876
    },
    {
        "question": " 4406時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2638080775782035
    },
    {
        "question": " 6772時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.608870342511302
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.4時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.275452894696263
    },
    {
        "question": " 155億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.468714900823479
    },
    {
        "question": " 1666億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.063341129317632
    },
    {
        "question": " 7001万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.067022203166575
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.1万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.285021916963313
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.33分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.145177525242528
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.894821393651583
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.79京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.263550475329753
    },
    {
        "question": " 163万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2760778505933423
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.882493279851799
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4822634402632024
    },
    {
        "question": " 881秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.944769176072931
    },
    {
        "question": " 300京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.978755175128879
    },
    {
        "question": " 334兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.587657583261596
    },
    {
        "question": " 224兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.794620536699646
    },
    {
        "question": " 981億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.21337982034818
    },
    {
        "question": " 234億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.368498020605083
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.85万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.895035466077292
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.646666672736018
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3406864373007588
    },
    {
        "question": " 3046億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9273862525235563
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.93億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0627433240151518
    },
    {
        "question": " 103兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.011994286295955
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.2345437925653555
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.81usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.8330023024409456
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.229e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.849323459650725
    },
    {
        "question": " 6626京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.88475150201841
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.6京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.239945287229613
    },
    {
        "question": " 142京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.374273028169589
    },
    {
        "question": " 1385億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.141303307544077
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.7億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.825908234390732
    },
    {
        "question": " 4011億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.603288992328537
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.49万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.436723176674013
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.358129722240262
    },
    {
        "question": " 366日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0017091726110662897
    },
    {
        "question": " 132万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.501759314960669
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.660215131692061
    },
    {
        "question": " 218億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.39615418640175
    },
    {
        "question": " 9599万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6020357467047575
    },
    {
        "question": " 6573万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.59592368548163
    },
    {
        "question": " 356時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1081443402041335
    },
    {
        "question": " 513万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9898512000642168
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.67万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5106758544268617
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.507822409010751
    },
    {
        "question": " 111分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8237828571236934
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.52分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.179827444678555
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.593250329909001
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.5兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4614402375048545
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.03万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3995447835361619
    },
    {
        "question": " 4402万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.865509205158606
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.572423404706225
    },
    {
        "question": " 412秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.614411762812823
    },
    {
        "question": " 114京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.559141888812507
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2371550896473071
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.3億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.320632035001645
    },
    {
        "question": " 792億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.120513295921545
    },
    {
        "question": " 236億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.372888097641993
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.5msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.694814538848384
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.7msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.609742158663502
    },
    {
        "question": " 778垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.391992129031035
    },
    {
        "question": " 4670京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.732835843291886
    },
    {
        "question": " 106京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.469086664945047
    },
    {
        "question": " 8755万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16411582945001335
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.4兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.910493913373139
    },
    {
        "question": " 2409万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.381868722118388
    },
    {
        "question": " 227usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.356554020829982
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8382169577367353
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.6垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.725898889740044
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.7垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.157393614310505
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.657615088290964
    },
    {
        "question": " 150兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.177315580162888
    },
    {
        "question": " 906億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.957057457119732
    },
    {
        "question": " 999万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.999362971807452
    },
    {
        "question": " 7046年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4102588758232715
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.7年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.73988146219781
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.94年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.094032053427696
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4824597510158677
    },
    {
        "question": " 535万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.108737722268621
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.305920726516809
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.125519243861422
    },
    {
        "question": " 127万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7233765656028845
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.943716807579856
    },
    {
        "question": " 128時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.663139036338619
    },
    {
        "question": " 2120万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6056358907824175
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.35億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.708093565427824
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.319965591189723
    },
    {
        "question": " 578分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.539750113068819
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.84175384732592
    },
    {
        "question": " 259億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.915005975412851
    },
    {
        "question": " 4020万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6676892676862973
    },
    {
        "question": " 723億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.30269835350588
    },
    {
        "question": " 12万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.302658376228319
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.79万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.680233613533898
    },
    {
        "question": " 883兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.44714738251606
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.165428386255253
    },
    {
        "question": " 243兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.829584130961163
    },
    {
        "question": " 3128万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.717072311153065
    },
    {
        "question": " 136億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.133500609206115
    },
    {
        "question": " 118万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.072554216309651
    },
    {
        "question": " 563垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.25160452206957
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.44兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.451461089613857
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.12兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.230462251765347
    },
    {
        "question": " 3123億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7163534289013955
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1679517016190566
    },
    {
        "question": " 902万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.9551070943957845
    },
    {
        "question": " 1320京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6217087806522157
    },
    {
        "question": " 592京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.836119044176862
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.93京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.136410886144596
    },
    {
        "question": " 8519兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.152228769024326
    },
    {
        "question": " 102兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.00814691840427
    },
    {
        "question": " 3209億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.506412088660621
    },
    {
        "question": " 4536万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.656685131423397
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.8年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.453100043420809
    },
    {
        "question": " 7346年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.808525877384264
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0688267137954455
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7968675035539194
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.9日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.991837453516343
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.20678692425338
    },
    {
        "question": " 84日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.86088380447655
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3613984097159484
    },
    {
        "question": " 1522億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.802265790022442
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.959692455079956
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.1万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.465019677451464
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.7億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8559448967825807
    },
    {
        "question": " 206万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.156439300226397
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.06億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.707241429917422
    },
    {
        "question": " 1946分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0673380476595185
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.62万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.337366270828454
    },
    {
        "question": " 1382億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.641691996041928
    },
    {
        "question": " 1215億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.147977636807475
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.3万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7057794642622304
    },
    {
        "question": " 724億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.081490784905151
    },
    {
        "question": " 356秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.551729081662211
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.57697851986443
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.2兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.864455109593299
    },
    {
        "question": " 269億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.872890830536544
    },
    {
        "question": " 209万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5415973322696641
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.32兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.364956577270812
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.100303781141605
    },
    {
        "question": " 320垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.006640842994525
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.11兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6770894967925065
    },
    {
        "question": " 8928兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.394461190921305
    },
    {
        "question": " 2160兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.556316579620973
    },
    {
        "question": " 9573兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.981035128885758
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.061125296657375
    },
    {
        "question": " 2413京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8836697652043264
    },
    {
        "question": " 1047垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.083560939732191
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.48垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.985851214172803
    },
    {
        "question": " 3509京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.767026714456435
    },
    {
        "question": " 288億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4599606511728858
    },
    {
        "question": " 418億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.621529475761582
    },
    {
        "question": " 8408nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.9246737072950828
    },
    {
        "question": " 4050年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.169760893751627
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.4年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.474432888353807
    },
    {
        "question": " 105年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.742481896103246
    },
    {
        "question": " 8061万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.344068122955971
    },
    {
        "question": " 355日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.930240723921111
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.3万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.653781219740083
    },
    {
        "question": " 105億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.07885682329912
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.2時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.36945544851316514
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.5時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0907831882096506
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.694034738584197
    },
    {
        "question": " 1585億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.47951420417367
    },
    {
        "question": " 669億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6673713217200925
    },
    {
        "question": " 1874分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4945391473627556
    },
    {
        "question": " 114万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.833600565836986
    },
    {
        "question": " 672分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.60560514755967
    },
    {
        "question": " 3175万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0029698242969478095
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.2兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.805271597908614
    },
    {
        "question": " 4885秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1325234591327007
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.507542240716277
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.289904162374434
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.7京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3123801197551055
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.113373696867254
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.48兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.094528167214996
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.2億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.195776327660507
    },
    {
        "question": " 360万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5566957930557153
    },
    {
        "question": " 1703msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.231305442218837
    },
    {
        "question": " 1549京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.691359448276122
    },
    {
        "question": " 821京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.977828092050939
    },
    {
        "question": " 768京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.328821292379764
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.2兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.768397097609563
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.65兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.562666763458025
    },
    {
        "question": " 1134万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.054731058691683
    },
    {
        "question": " 125万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.096921531199037
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.02垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.104987199969373
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.306681805735764
    },
    {
        "question": " 7435兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3149673376685684
    },
    {
        "question": " 233京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5892819223729155
    },
    {
        "question": " 1939兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.287583087020718
    },
    {
        "question": " 110万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.040507844600690124
    },
    {
        "question": " 111億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.044767182441815
    },
    {
        "question": " 178年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.811596830685135
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.23万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.569066820109231
    },
    {
        "question": " 878万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.381391157276177
    },
    {
        "question": " 549万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.119468600442536
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3556012064314333
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.42日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.582365562250056
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.246904584642134
    },
    {
        "question": " 2197万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.961669933795656
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.6万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.712849686191236
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.88時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.83080296180608
    },
    {
        "question": " 16兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.482474114973048
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.64兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.263997345770136
    },
    {
        "question": " 246万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.612438933447544
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9697052491665834
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.57万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.188454255632871
    },
    {
        "question": " 253億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9039296873522193
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.3億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3252531769234315
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.05億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.400120079815758
    },
    {
        "question": " 285万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.676868490725168
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.75万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.4400886874235
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.697365542783626
    },
    {
        "question": " 1063億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0901723608024554
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.87兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.280556569484959
    },
    {
        "question": " 138万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3619417620650542
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.25兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.352987694288
    },
    {
        "question": " 185万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.268333224786698
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.5兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3907512287952586
    },
    {
        "question": " 7297京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.926671383418116
    },
    {
        "question": " 562京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.193664885472543
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.2京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.58705664066476
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.228833864031527
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.2億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.75723366266094
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.3usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.765851669913978
    },
    {
        "question": " 5220垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.218878897031055
    },
    {
        "question": " 1281垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.171126047069137
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.54468074193526
    },
    {
        "question": " 126京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.320539537283482
    },
    {
        "question": " 141京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.150047973350041
    },
    {
        "question": " 161億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.2068543095906685
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.290573795696304
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.36年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4846034684207696
    },
    {
        "question": " 3134万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9337434095490815
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.470191112995032
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.16日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.436147505453856
    },
    {
        "question": " 106万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0833249528340714
    },
    {
        "question": " 826時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.53660749709012
    },
    {
        "question": " 142時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.708963477616049
    },
    {
        "question": " 662兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.099937492706582
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.1億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.626996440342632
    },
    {
        "question": " 2681分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.650184571527732
    },
    {
        "question": " 7660万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.662367867456712
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.3億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.295740534379852
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3591140517576408
    },
    {
        "question": " 111万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.490343907843803
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.2万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6872554939918487
    },
    {
        "question": " 8105秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.908737017092241
    },
    {
        "question": " 632億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3016998285340444
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.50309266520178
    },
    {
        "question": " 607万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2268737020948075
    },
    {
        "question": " 6788万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0536212103994353
    },
    {
        "question": " 1264msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1016821243043553
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.64万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.983904666003001
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.27msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.629929781788242
    },
    {
        "question": " 253兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9042109105229057
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.7京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.906831953009185
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.95兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.441362846865992
    },
    {
        "question": " 580兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.985080579115043
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.43兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.535615380142993
    },
    {
        "question": " 1854万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.268136539374943
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.3usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.604772966059512
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.027e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.51257961183945
    },
    {
        "question": " 656兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8805119475223255
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.5兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1803875728996416
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.67垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.78603796400493
    },
    {
        "question": " 805兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.905795262889302
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.0454596988778606
    },
    {
        "question": " 151万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.1795109770041643
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7277936393512086
    },
    {
        "question": " 1584年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.142193358628511
    },
    {
        "question": " 391年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.312627474118294
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.28兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.954126160594722
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.618881681899321
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.97万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9342030625537205
    },
    {
        "question": " 11日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.97868481516814
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.322087544293744
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.6兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.720115552659593
    },
    {
        "question": " 2586時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0324559928689077
    },
    {
        "question": " 2071万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.094371933877284
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.579893432180356
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.9億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0188123660709625
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.140110371920631
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3637293707351184
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.165979765496706
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.97分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.071523228529566
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.777366382259531
    },
    {
        "question": " 121兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.146436313075391
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.06兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.147505963513852
    },
    {
        "question": " 2731秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6581612169285276
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.7万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.861525173273776
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.86秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.586216960571623
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.583107338942753
    },
    {
        "question": " 8447兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.990220754848465
    },
    {
        "question": " 3851億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.029325402097557
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2296225234408116
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.55万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8163074291674552
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.272842933919068
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7655881857334075
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.5京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.469668680649474
    },
    {
        "question": " 797兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3450958167367
    },
    {
        "question": " 4762億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.899599746760148
    },
    {
        "question": " 1031億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.013283938001219
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.8万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.3582792768205083
    },
    {
        "question": " 324usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.510896670532644
    },
    {
        "question": " 207京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8168632621146297
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.25垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.783529571108887
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.2兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1699285618121968
    },
    {
        "question": " 79兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1195667413762953
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.2京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.852476333643047
    },
    {
        "question": " 2500兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.397877322198585
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.48兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.540998907161098
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.27年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.854885001722072
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.781063232000161
    },
    {
        "question": " 6795万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.212414644525538
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.6万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.87939105320595
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.013828709733307
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.089290899987562
    },
    {
        "question": " 347万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1604344151641515
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.863471451105723
    },
    {
        "question": " 647時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.366942687472601
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.771777400770308
    },
    {
        "question": " 1472兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.447309122793175
    },
    {
        "question": " 8億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7445739390711426
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.3万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.104173421482175
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.980681461089325
    },
    {
        "question": " 10兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.501656646864031
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.97万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06237720025008997
    },
    {
        "question": " 450億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.097022265668831
    },
    {
        "question": " 251億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.621771146793714
    },
    {
        "question": " 478万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.679246706506014
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.335186605893144
    },
    {
        "question": " 4138京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.11797609689467
    },
    {
        "question": " 7京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.908901341910125
    },
    {
        "question": " 5840億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.210090671896774
    },
    {
        "question": " 1305億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.337490073421907
    },
    {
        "question": " 251億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.400098549891379
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.88万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.688347704963999
    },
    {
        "question": " 7625兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3834580019104012
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.226397873199986
    },
    {
        "question": " 137億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.578841619946977
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.66億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2066389529549926
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.4億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.759016350829935
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.3434395320928845
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.078096786823886
    },
    {
        "question": " 701京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.347176703053191
    },
    {
        "question": " 627垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.860750188908757
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.709205795659663
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3248495431674756
    },
    {
        "question": " 449兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.652612524615824
    },
    {
        "question": " 493億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.692489479381296
    },
    {
        "question": " 401億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.603382865605882
    },
    {
        "question": " 1326年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.684711681194993
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.066504709355428
    },
    {
        "question": " 769日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3234512846130022
    },
    {
        "question": " 511日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.08873213709971
    },
    {
        "question": " 688日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.99606270478901
    },
    {
        "question": " 4333日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.573303383314483
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.41122657106233307
    },
    {
        "question": " 434万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.256886600084664
    },
    {
        "question": " 183時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.040741898037757
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.05万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.259561659911183
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.680508707769609
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.02兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8834943526866335
    },
    {
        "question": " 1286億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.950867700113109
    },
    {
        "question": " 259億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.634706952163512
    },
    {
        "question": " 5613万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.527380223718943
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.86兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.957166182090105
    },
    {
        "question": " 770万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.949942173311222
    },
    {
        "question": " 1925万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7282256871199335
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.1万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.835162261914327
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.32秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3656650489277142
    },
    {
        "question": " 195秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.291087050874404
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.03兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.106357401880442
    },
    {
        "question": " 979億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0543509271737257
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.4億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.911360674787762
    },
    {
        "question": " 890万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1710929327346973
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.24兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.915789593071374
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.251415541422023
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.2兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.543207759498137
    },
    {
        "question": " 109京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.481690049197418
    },
    {
        "question": " 11兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.263491858609221
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1936874273981815
    },
    {
        "question": " 3032億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.481695146813095
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.15垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.212920429318282
    },
    {
        "question": " 3135垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.559775375236146
    },
    {
        "question": " 321京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.949608670168759
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.05垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.829568206830025
    },
    {
        "question": " 1350億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.130292783658362
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.1兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.881575188226196
    },
    {
        "question": " 1541万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.187682462056699
    },
    {
        "question": " 351万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.10789128031531
    },
    {
        "question": " 379年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.520874950055251
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7847994016807505
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.11億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.346614145803483
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4616331182692566
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.25万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.669626979676948
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.100544634355202
    },
    {
        "question": " 424億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6851695419971024
    },
    {
        "question": " 1403時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7668770147672397
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.8万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.435978891081868
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.24兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.07445265673301
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.05万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4487297771706709
    },
    {
        "question": " 1261分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3224729747709596
    },
    {
        "question": " 514分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4888023465287645
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.5兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.039156674301446
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.7兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.824408984131582
    },
    {
        "question": " 4999万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.142603491228646
    },
    {
        "question": " 1113億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.268322868070015
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.72秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6740176346877917
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.6兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.81448594724142
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.6兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.866816279556301
    },
    {
        "question": " 5392兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.175452769845352
    },
    {
        "question": " 4978万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.918890674621073
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.5万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8950572638126895
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.4垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.425272232628679
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1311884998601975
    },
    {
        "question": " 5096億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.15088998736554
    },
    {
        "question": " 712兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.074439401351327
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2146653761718
    },
    {
        "question": " 1994億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.299709782385499
    },
    {
        "question": " 243usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.385793803157597
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.7垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.223370278729051
    },
    {
        "question": " 2635京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.484259488358573
    },
    {
        "question": " 3704京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.012315993921821
    },
    {
        "question": " 224京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.57295545447009
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.8京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.460042102996892
    },
    {
        "question": " 125万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.09521934640617236
    },
    {
        "question": " 3371億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.527808466039072
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6713172555455245
    },
    {
        "question": " 8457年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.869733704985413
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.45年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.371015626917886
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.68億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.003262367884173
    },
    {
        "question": " 197万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.673583889071674
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.46日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6978393242028416
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.9日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.793117990333685
    },
    {
        "question": " 6日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.71459046706891
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.26兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.778497603794266
    },
    {
        "question": " 421時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2445166663257012
    },
    {
        "question": " 197時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0730816832594225
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.853905269100146
    },
    {
        "question": " 2641万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.701066149199476
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.4万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3382326437828893
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4672291274892135
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.4分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.709637209483488
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.802520055170084
    },
    {
        "question": " 114兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.55968844014033
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.06億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6718822550309724
    },
    {
        "question": " 167億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.667484825376313
    },
    {
        "question": " 698万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.065912220286299
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.7兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.928148446204596
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.7京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.437905464387287
    },
    {
        "question": " 1766万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.690759913029998
    },
    {
        "question": " 161億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.427889042577841
    },
    {
        "question": " 4063億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.608834764224143
    },
    {
        "question": " 479msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.679901565721616
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.9msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.68068277803641
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.9垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.429962209476967
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.91京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.754432355273008
    },
    {
        "question": " 369兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.010667604051218
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.5億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.534461361472066
    },
    {
        "question": " 191兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.282060705780486
    },
    {
        "question": " 4645億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.666975773653217
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.4usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.647689604144251
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.002e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.502127280100531
    },
    {
        "question": " 8303垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.982736391155033
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.3垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.41220361903346
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.4京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.551387639149491
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.24兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.349339286254742
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.073261326871509
    },
    {
        "question": " 11億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.040533308628499
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.3万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.013926816774124
    },
    {
        "question": " 2433年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.106720506495249
    },
    {
        "question": " 2547万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.843663469789664
    },
    {
        "question": " 655日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.196270914990631
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.61万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.600243789882727
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.7万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9068174908604163
    },
    {
        "question": " 346時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1591043481402596
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.48万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.31945942210264
    },
    {
        "question": " 4817時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.239057114026023
    },
    {
        "question": " 4212億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.903872257796225
    },
    {
        "question": " 390万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.432905052363384
    },
    {
        "question": " 173分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4586503037972045
    },
    {
        "question": " 188万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.053243976478646
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.958911459263669
    },
    {
        "question": " 103億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.514325149997111
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.8兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.833141048796417
    },
    {
        "question": " 7192秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3005292709931362
    },
    {
        "question": " 6092秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.00663426344566
    },
    {
        "question": " 625秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.796085604165499
    },
    {
        "question": " 1242兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.595165828734994
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.179227509242344
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.4億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.004479954300078
    },
    {
        "question": " 948億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.198709785645477
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2508730719015493
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.3422021957871095
    },
    {
        "question": " 381msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.58145560834046
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.948198898048966
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.61垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.727014102456499
    },
    {
        "question": " 5709億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2002341370723313
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.535472642871422
    },
    {
        "question": " 2831万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4518770585528684
    },
    {
        "question": " 7764万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.890101800121727
    },
    {
        "question": " 5877usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.76917457924596
    },
    {
        "question": " 2278垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.858812818112908
    },
    {
        "question": " 960京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.04592337965736
    },
    {
        "question": " 917京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.40622339166812
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.51177868015711
    },
    {
        "question": " 169億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2267159470165245
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.267017775525085
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.1万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.84591220645516
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.88年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.336249128956053
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.96万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3385902593686616
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.5万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.196500668284931
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.30709061133678
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.324595847905154
    },
    {
        "question": " 124万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1523275692563724
    },
    {
        "question": " 190億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.89924450271469
    },
    {
        "question": " 1025万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.788913893684718
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.794005751217433
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.310534634223764
    },
    {
        "question": " 117億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.909569909026928
    },
    {
        "question": " 1962分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5146533143243646
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.863618117976817
    },
    {
        "question": " 19分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.056410116958323
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.41分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.703172013029555
    },
    {
        "question": " 150兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.678018178524937
    },
    {
        "question": " 455兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.721917123376652
    },
    {
        "question": " 4018億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.047660135663309
    },
    {
        "question": " 196万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.513118543016121
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.2万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.827151672690839
    },
    {
        "question": " 1350億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6314912469521083
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.3兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.623753120979723
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.612912845882077
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.91兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.913210955353202
    },
    {
        "question": " 8922万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.950467812737652
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.013280292225504
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7069503285854974
    },
    {
        "question": " 6150億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8524047353276509
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.94京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.730461797121475
    },
    {
        "question": " 113億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.273813770094005
    },
    {
        "question": " 135万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12935000589214707
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.050458472008447
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.606e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.706914762090815
    },
    {
        "question": " 836垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.985854386616841
    },
    {
        "question": " 2384京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.821085632166854
    },
    {
        "question": " 672億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.049444042649441355
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.164647251407693
    },
    {
        "question": " 5005億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.699398376370168
    },
    {
        "question": " 3474万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.540801178879584
    },
    {
        "question": " 7046年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7904198710525865
    },
    {
        "question": " 623億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.23237208139782
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.55日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.930644378751114
    },
    {
        "question": " 8576億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.990791505335652
    },
    {
        "question": " 239万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.998971828652788
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.935413954494459
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9528885652222323
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.714485232598829
    },
    {
        "question": " 295万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7490237609015526
    },
    {
        "question": " 2417億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.224964626502702
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.21万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1360245249443586
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0535680679152426
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.96分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.4734133846588815
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.3分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.126316450620733
    },
    {
        "question": " 1345億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.62987020626498
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.87億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8320061326154544
    },
    {
        "question": " 934万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4142037801477554
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.5億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.010708572335762
    },
    {
        "question": " 5942秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.773968147499987
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.662497320177601
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.65京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.000544163452867
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.25京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.796201691063741
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4734950088933032
    },
    {
        "question": " 742万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.870374164552196
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.0878322997582295
    },
    {
        "question": " 26垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.916953397610729
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.3兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.657776589302523
    },
    {
        "question": " 335兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9693237354243305
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3219205105905045
    },
    {
        "question": " 161億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.205922909109
    },
    {
        "question": " 1815億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.258820560016895
    },
    {
        "question": " 28usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.447625923132049
    },
    {
        "question": " 9556垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.481463359474599
    },
    {
        "question": " 1407垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.21166577557595
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.02京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.223407054441851
    },
    {
        "question": " 5888億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9918378030291286
    },
    {
        "question": " 158京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.197545003415897
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3069304213667072
    },
    {
        "question": " 8895億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.949126058747874
    },
    {
        "question": " 412年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.176726650921127
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.233438645249088
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.77年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.551260933953702
    },
    {
        "question": " 8758億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.380101161081075
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.56日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7883027674780139
    },
    {
        "question": " 617日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.948523400415537
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.475533948004815
    },
    {
        "question": " 59万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.390561339821085
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.6時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3646442248082598
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8976397840270005
    },
    {
        "question": " 3463万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.818851373017678
    },
    {
        "question": " 1678分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06633309548735644
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.330160150226507
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.095002275992782
    },
    {
        "question": " 136分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.910358598701539
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6492428355026167
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.66兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.947460054857335
    },
    {
        "question": " 428億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.075638352572426
    },
    {
        "question": " 139秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.36585265055012806
    },
    {
        "question": " 608秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.7842137215482605
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.674811611523931
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.72京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.820886825406724
    },
    {
        "question": " 165兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.661450066611937
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.64万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20598870775663247
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.120187706824296
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.3兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1275564993214029
    },
    {
        "question": " 560兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8119711957652234
    },
    {
        "question": " 989兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.438744949103783
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.9兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0134216288230125
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.110177976236171
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.04万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.7811973789455116
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.3京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4420755415224884
    },
    {
        "question": " 1872垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.335702878884025
    },
    {
        "question": " 950兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.421359135177157
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.407908620394283
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.9億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5300424079180177
    },
    {
        "question": " 193億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.2847952871710415
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.04兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.483340004423361
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.8年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.406458982302068
    },
    {
        "question": " 492年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.634637724152056
    },
    {
        "question": " 2793日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8837749603511924
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.08日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.425231865958013
    },
    {
        "question": " 949億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.03487869231936
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.4万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.087546253804116
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.9万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.741476146135088
    },
    {
        "question": " 176万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.80265799760393
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.931372800928743
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.634227505321638
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.969378994845528
    },
    {
        "question": " 24億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.601876275909838
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.52分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.178993281805413
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.610540182643234
    },
    {
        "question": " 111億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.108186627419569
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.97億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3453001680912156
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.4億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.972938501571153
    },
    {
        "question": " 50京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.199879424378397
    },
    {
        "question": " 1969億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3577015716542657
    },
    {
        "question": " 3460兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.982824744598142
    },
    {
        "question": " 21万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5441879439799413
    },
    {
        "question": " 5483msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7389806008097677
    },
    {
        "question": " 172万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.235230783252113
    },
    {
        "question": " 2855垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.95687970781572
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.7京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6313236172391345
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.3億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0263355484228045
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6611451684889678
    },
    {
        "question": " 185億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.266761763121406
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.143342721854006
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.1万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.864167666604107
    },
    {
        "question": " 775京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.390553508903314
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.278729748782199
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.35兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.171770492836667
    },
    {
        "question": " 389兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.812055443038178
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31597964207155327
    },
    {
        "question": " 4759万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6775076827270752
    },
    {
        "question": " 9109億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.959484393971554
    },
    {
        "question": " 1262日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.538865540585951
    },
    {
        "question": " 1066日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.40776203562968
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.296552788115255
    },
    {
        "question": " 6599億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.876976004743047
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.83980536476044
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.9時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5253756744064377
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6302771296699388
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.6億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8061619781988143
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.7億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.831728191565779
    },
    {
        "question": " 983分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2145919934776805
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.1万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.178228398625156
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.994050130072601
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.89億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3392492923219912
    },
    {
        "question": " 24万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.44452212548691583
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.5億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.380950395785849
    },
    {
        "question": " 1243億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.316494908915407
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.6秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.744983674232303
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.211931368558229
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.025679641792019
    },
    {
        "question": " 1174億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5708999308544083
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.191793217502919
    },
    {
        "question": " 5226兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.161906610479702
    },
    {
        "question": " 1528万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.406026978092836
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1623814463778057
    },
    {
        "question": " 525msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.720001612009193
    },
    {
        "question": " 720垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.358385616985364
    },
    {
        "question": " 2070億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3795567633231789
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.656557523939592
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.394020784411556
    },
    {
        "question": " 357万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5530629388182651
    },
    {
        "question": " 7311usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.8639793191597578
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.12万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.852769900426592
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.66垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.438792903829242
    },
    {
        "question": " 1156垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.126561649492443
    },
    {
        "question": " 3022兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.923973892285854
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.5京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.122387102933575
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.3兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.801166925924751
    },
    {
        "question": " 383億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.582816179007386
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.52兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.402217524821978
    },
    {
        "question": " 1429日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5927042821753881
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.7日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6530117659517227
    },
    {
        "question": " 26日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.572758866866241
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.28億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.573543955184904
    },
    {
        "question": " 5509万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.360894337014155
    },
    {
        "question": " 184時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.043375152560723
    },
    {
        "question": " 2523時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.958254922232187
    },
    {
        "question": " 223兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.627983280919835
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.9兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.43319564163568
    },
    {
        "question": " 2163万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.556987854806588
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.1万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.64805867891028
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.115452853224586
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.6兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.311296909553858
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.4万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6005384605630781
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.92276520645452
    },
    {
        "question": " 1582万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.421132238457387
    },
    {
        "question": " 300秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.477477962972509
    },
    {
        "question": " 1935億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7877985481945193
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.26745269236600033
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.22京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.789227070785032
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.1兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.971000904676128
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.9万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7471143137165077
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.234981253125881
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.194078407497845
    },
    {
        "question": " 10兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0652087715511422
    },
    {
        "question": " 1070京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.473116708780553
    },
    {
        "question": " 214兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.552566815175373
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.3億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9881578795572405
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.73兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.827910554856803
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.42万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.925308845990217
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.086e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.820442095680285
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.471371410469326
    },
    {
        "question": " 138垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.584460941385318
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3635492994817644
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2035409326602826
    },
    {
        "question": " 5269兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.72175076253015
    },
    {
        "question": " 2278nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.3575522778064866
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.9万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.553834991929014
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.8億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.795874575523177
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.499427954597953
    },
    {
        "question": " 404日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7647568073901025
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.71万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.369776205966142
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.2万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.993076516833504
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.9時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08013982566534406
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.8万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.568877262202854
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.662923214424914
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.613586209457507
    },
    {
        "question": " 467億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.511016097908146
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3765116410570384
    },
    {
        "question": " 6101万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.563538722571607
    },
    {
        "question": " 317分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.278988848544037
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.9分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.540863052518231
    },
    {
        "question": " 380億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0811225936051856
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.299798763321763
    },
    {
        "question": " 9196億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.407278780684829
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.7万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.208706268805943
    },
    {
        "question": " 205万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.312459421240831
    },
    {
        "question": " 972億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.48895980295654007
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.05億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8454222135583933
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.1兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.001655773557656
    },
    {
        "question": " 135億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.352846934635343
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.11兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.852101669450695
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.4京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.969236984440591
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.433260958069995
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.8億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3347204206104526
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.634204271749491
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.331578166979147
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.3万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.559729086567951
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.497e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.898699363555547
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.6兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0009173621397740028
    },
    {
        "question": " 328兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9592247428542864
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.251304241564306
    },
    {
        "question": " 105京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.022480542504601
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.339714647758991
    },
    {
        "question": " 237億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.375200806556239
    },
    {
        "question": " 453年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.218134604693844
    },
    {
        "question": " 1308年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0590690750702345
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.624416338994262
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.6億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.115345138296378
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.26万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.34691519536622
    },
    {
        "question": " 6399日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.964435934455377
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.17907014010496
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.53億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.362795355102767
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8091958676663173
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.7時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.123940388815586
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.818775985682146
    },
    {
        "question": " 403万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.446988165028715
    },
    {
        "question": " 119億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.29874344590132
    },
    {
        "question": " 4182万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.399543288230195
    },
    {
        "question": " 215兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.833952900765197
    },
    {
        "question": " 705億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.911913297432157
    },
    {
        "question": " 162億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.653234494992482
    },
    {
        "question": " 2120秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.548274838946253
    },
    {
        "question": " 39秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.59143814260341
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.686754909061725
    },
    {
        "question": " 1946億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.352647454540242
    },
    {
        "question": " 7939億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.343480696263679
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.8億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.998723315680948
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.64兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.421792130735627
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.1兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.287505974476997
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.7兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.650722841094302
    },
    {
        "question": " 867京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.381669917947097
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22977066102451094
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.178501221731313
    },
    {
        "question": " 656億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.816722041493497
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.124e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.551867695903884
    },
    {
        "question": " 169兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.29244119591551376
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.4垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.291324263333179
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.779390996309193
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3870944539830756
    },
    {
        "question": " 336万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.5263938400219748
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.53億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.403159393686298
    },
    {
        "question": " 1633年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7751565236842906
    },
    {
        "question": " 363年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.502595118765237
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.3年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.620000374125241
    },
    {
        "question": " 291万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9015882795704036
    },
    {
        "question": " 429日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.012878777909524
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.002003813405713
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.42日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.31955254073527
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.3兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.878935380678563
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.626640149031565
    },
    {
        "question": " 123万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.866921423856926
    },
    {
        "question": " 129万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.665894777258085
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.49時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.099251214262505
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.576673162732562
    },
    {
        "question": " 517億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.555185742062438
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6293945091688307
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.41万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.310276081794511
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.99兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.97729097606838
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.78億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8949505755477762
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.6万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.915626078730469
    },
    {
        "question": " 812億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.131384407449572
    },
    {
        "question": " 188秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.27336364560942
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7840416590056027
    },
    {
        "question": " 538兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.794661168408377
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.26億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0730439384972588
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.406142769308344
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.44兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.647199104609838
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.9msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.689217241568171
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.861677934283686
    },
    {
        "question": " 351兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.608333226530618
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.62兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.426862514623336
    },
    {
        "question": " 2939億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6900282890169986
    },
    {
        "question": " 231億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.363539315213483
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.290198105007726
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.373236103260196
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.1垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.093263693378477
    },
    {
        "question": " 236京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.437217393566954
    },
    {
        "question": " 2577兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8548817578353356
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.4京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.995797461740041
    },
    {
        "question": " 8483兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.928532030478307
    },
    {
        "question": " 2164兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.33517618574834
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.4兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.924280669864059
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.14万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.350301616237134
    },
    {
        "question": " 1719年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.177654583042817
    },
    {
        "question": " 886億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.384965195103087
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.02億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.860113813753397
    },
    {
        "question": " 768日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.043691309640482
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.9日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.598583750573037
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.952829024826537
    },
    {
        "question": " 20兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.359252826425632
    },
    {
        "question": " 7203時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.477330240517058
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.78億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7227906324038953
    },
    {
        "question": " 1572億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.038195697428238
    },
    {
        "question": " 1322分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3430688441550798
    },
    {
        "question": " 1103分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.820838180030469
    },
    {
        "question": " 9939分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.775483204902699
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.825555447735862
    },
    {
        "question": " 6695億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.326924988418001
    },
    {
        "question": " 1836億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.327436261540446
    },
    {
        "question": " 586万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2117840096239583
    },
    {
        "question": " 248秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6165751499592409
    },
    {
        "question": " 622万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.793704674724017
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.707605213941553
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.45京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.935943252561717
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.56億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.322405943832969
    },
    {
        "question": " 153兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.406279809434878
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.024712453044481
    },
    {
        "question": " 7751msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.889371678985407
    },
    {
        "question": " 132兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.620624854558598
    },
    {
        "question": " 3982億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6635749500821597
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9642893259558463
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.591384693282174
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.64兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.666461280214747
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.5万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.8893468067755013
    },
    {
        "question": " 836京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.423275312915637
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.109553777554268
    },
    {
        "question": " 1607兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.64973049834474
    },
    {
        "question": " 1319京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.341932166700506
    },
    {
        "question": " 2072兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.316290676527413
    },
    {
        "question": " 440兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.643090780380916
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.2万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.969461299727658
    },
    {
        "question": " 416万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.18095311832796
    },
    {
        "question": " 3181年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.445071178104145
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.977533522287698
    },
    {
        "question": " 568億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.192004983322798
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.31868671987801
    },
    {
        "question": " 154万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.245042610239042
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.08万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.937292162056415
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.7万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.318119735124124
    },
    {
        "question": " 691時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.395783479420331
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.704259995944809
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.864992655027404
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.525287718045119
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.931683963434168
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.508867703948043
    },
    {
        "question": " 804億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.968497278334097
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.93億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.03775368210817
    },
    {
        "question": " 647秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0326820371505507
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.688295537886775
    },
    {
        "question": " 1722兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.737110262460633
    },
    {
        "question": " 713億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.916802305327313
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.682792170423695
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.33兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.948480827482825
    },
    {
        "question": " 145億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.160481770053729
    },
    {
        "question": " 50万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.698689161888359
    },
    {
        "question": " 8917msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.95021463530929
    },
    {
        "question": " 320兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0065681188872155
    },
    {
        "question": " 7573兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.942793712941446
    },
    {
        "question": " 411兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.057895245389851
    },
    {
        "question": " 1340億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.348879004912252
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1547104073628507
    },
    {
        "question": " 218万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3375499466838843
    },
    {
        "question": " 3482usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.541799563049976
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.729947626267331
    },
    {
        "question": " 1552垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.254264332802192
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.91京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.283210181280782
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.88兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.059628036391985
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.7京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.567892836869737
    },
    {
        "question": " 761兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.88113918510015
    },
    {
        "question": " 470万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.672100175233023
    },
    {
        "question": " 327万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.076671515130567
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.38万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.865993048174568
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.33年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.021362389449893
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.7万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.00190549720727
    },
    {
        "question": " 348日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9216299674220245
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.5万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.069441309660121
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.29日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.660238208185832
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.3万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9045760013893054
    },
    {
        "question": " 185万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.886213593347697
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.47万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.317958019471478
    },
    {
        "question": " 236万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.929868268035174
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.679320052332105
    },
    {
        "question": " 622万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0733125842563507
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.9万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.34584419905714
    },
    {
        "question": " 185万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.488587040948636
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7877059787315135
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.662785503230368
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.8兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.840455863501578
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.670094427411563
    },
    {
        "question": " 1093億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.260414630473493
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.9秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.880020286684891
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.725209966643921
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.320553468916055
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6791529013106532
    },
    {
        "question": " 526兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.942682625245034
    },
    {
        "question": " 130億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.114407451192935
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.3垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.236206759172703
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3161775473781345
    },
    {
        "question": " 306兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.929793790314328
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.1京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.894531646381212
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.27192366870999
    },
    {
        "question": " 3438usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.5363060080425008
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.53垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.157474769432826
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3229614419229696
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.5兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3756731060292515
    },
    {
        "question": " 4248億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8500723150079426
    },
    {
        "question": " 238億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3764473889228912
    },
    {
        "question": " 106万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.02479910001579544
    },
    {
        "question": " 653億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.814843154362091
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.72年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.31970568551198
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.1万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.277275465488474
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.66億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.80467228518589
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.91日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.056360795051579
    },
    {
        "question": " 1207万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1392756060367324
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.983218727178301
    },
    {
        "question": " 546兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.01637526889049
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.04兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.325053556250541
    },
    {
        "question": " 954億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.201574245853681
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.11193651680568
    },
    {
        "question": " 512億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2104267777838547
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.95億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7581003396658517
    },
    {
        "question": " 1331万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5679712116279374
    },
    {
        "question": " 1922万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.505577994589762
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.24万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.719001523173267
    },
    {
        "question": " 54秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.7321763808341775
    },
    {
        "question": " 1320兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.621693762687171
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.09兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3830859729775185
    },
    {
        "question": " 5314万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1690883567666932
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.29億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.738866782104464
    },
    {
        "question": " 1043万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.018080285826837
    },
    {
        "question": " 503msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.701427033171884
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.09msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.320138452841921
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.4京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4741111334417285
    },
    {
        "question": " 3945億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6595865896028519
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.17兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.944475612850762
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.74兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.980987190666283
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.2兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.546428439849492
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.91万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.898431750639723
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.02万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.604714586417554
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.5京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9245306904786899
    },
    {
        "question": " 1291垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.174510578343076
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.1垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.013276887643878
    },
    {
        "question": " 7156億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0765138942946884
    },
    {
        "question": " 1897億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2781056458771287
    },
    {
        "question": " 1626億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.2111664392493875
    },
    {
        "question": " 347万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.5400385491302924
    },
    {
        "question": " 5327億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.164202296943579
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.465860361080532
    },
    {
        "question": " 7401日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.027665049751785
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.6兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.716193378297156
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.09億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.939339525034562
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.795072348242328
    },
    {
        "question": " 325時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.068241324400201
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.41時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.088581332784051
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6882458876747384
    },
    {
        "question": " 712億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.694324297342062
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.398359499201999
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.03分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2599081724242676
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.39億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3066022011807943
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.5万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30775516025946303
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0581935698322082
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.26億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.851395659383559
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.31秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.8002915779063215
    },
    {
        "question": " 5974億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2774623266029417
    },
    {
        "question": " 138兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.203931104144277
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.82945439644433
    },
    {
        "question": " 139億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.363453296034637
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.22兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.507879223250212
    },
    {
        "question": " 181万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.257334503248105
    },
    {
        "question": " 145垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.663123379271733
    },
    {
        "question": " 637兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.867708877108391
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.4京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.432396620579535
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.9兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.060343956960907
    },
    {
        "question": " 317兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.500473032520215
    },
    {
        "question": " 76億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.880885612307858
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.65京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16869593914386027
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.21206838026637
    },
    {
        "question": " 120京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.522493169776336
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.3兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.756921035278893
    },
    {
        "question": " 3400億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5314230018078074
    },
    {
        "question": " 594億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.773713372709924
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.37億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.867701666416086
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5703402856902544
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.83年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.934837142356044
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.768489556649804
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.194418076213069
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.99085507082886
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.97兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.05607563480798
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.83万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2030923745586968
    },
    {
        "question": " 3124万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.272920769893013
    },
    {
        "question": " 257時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.965486162582755
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.7億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.721861682185547
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.119782166984242
    },
    {
        "question": " 119分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2963923673337443
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.56分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.187156061923194
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.19京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.842543138660284
    },
    {
        "question": " 1552億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2544328244530565
    },
    {
        "question": " 15兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.62049776360414
    },
    {
        "question": " 223万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.569910414169821
    },
    {
        "question": " 319秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.504110401107484
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.29秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.968062527619841
    },
    {
        "question": " 303兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.982351696675497
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.48兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.605355988991735
    },
    {
        "question": " 404億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.050013187414968
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.671095040958556
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.003088237616499
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.1万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.281378654437919
    },
    {
        "question": " 1625垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.712019156713236
    },
    {
        "question": " 9520兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.042139948994322
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6074117542065745
    },
    {
        "question": " 717兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.07763747787588
    },
    {
        "question": " 3436万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5361001807053754
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.6億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.513735461044741
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.04万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.308644865904357
    },
    {
        "question": " 213垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.828784113394585
    },
    {
        "question": " 129兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1743630754680836
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.4京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.194842827399163
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.93垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.816371521094316
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.328903322620995
    },
    {
        "question": " 154万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.18884930761083996
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.63兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.935840412237912
    },
    {
        "question": " 2765年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.004071397753631
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.2万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.818465022390303
    },
    {
        "question": " 6035億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.218344881069779
    },
    {
        "question": " 7299日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.24346878684062
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.61日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.907067137146708
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.2日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.354291382177562
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.22449950128675
    },
    {
        "question": " 107時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6476063474648097
    },
    {
        "question": " 533時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.505062314561677
    },
    {
        "question": " 99万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.551923230043993
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.70416840152948
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.39億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.647104332477778
    },
    {
        "question": " 6662万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.045444180418071
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.9分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.583419578104665
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.194304392373428
    },
    {
        "question": " 4137億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.117844028101469
    },
    {
        "question": " 939億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.036141110393821
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.475463680685738
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.5億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.839503423536071
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.815683838454532
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.9億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3623091811811416
    },
    {
        "question": " 2574兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.854288132958374
    },
    {
        "question": " 131兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.337833484084335
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.84兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.685077843835186
    },
    {
        "question": " 2372兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8762254866083972
    },
    {
        "question": " 7980億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9655003873223023
    },
    {
        "question": " 4678兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.113740563190908
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.64億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7834589396098102
    },
    {
        "question": " 21兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.32191857925717
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.08万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.8500164498924065
    },
    {
        "question": " 418京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.122053918924659
    },
    {
        "question": " 6703兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8897517703237965
    },
    {
        "question": " 2338京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.812471913552613
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.11垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.546884098626478
    },
    {
        "question": " 1291億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1108907299716084
    },
    {
        "question": " 691万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.8395775397875394
    },
    {
        "question": " 113億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.053146548304863
    },
    {
        "question": " 193年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.848278560881053
    },
    {
        "question": " 6619年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.763265556310648
    },
    {
        "question": " 4530日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0937788581259766
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.1日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.207114740503716
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.216610202464767
    },
    {
        "question": " 145日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.098554799790016
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.5兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.979267860244098
    },
    {
        "question": " 488億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.308171631054998
    },
    {
        "question": " 3132万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.273989898769345
    },
    {
        "question": " 50万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.255641915442395
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.42億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.663280590780661
    },
    {
        "question": " 207億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.157241094528262
    },
    {
        "question": " 173分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.46008206830708165
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.92万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.47012502612621
    },
    {
        "question": " 433億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1378203456148537
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.33億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.700353901314748
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.452486310874937
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.3万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.606880416085414
    },
    {
        "question": " 1948京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.790796903333348
    },
    {
        "question": " 1637兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2776280707352905
    },
    {
        "question": " 5820億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.208608831458969
    },
    {
        "question": " 204万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5322605956972968
    },
    {
        "question": " 1346億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.129053130474826
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.89京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3395423034089298
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.9京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.971282879780878
    },
    {
        "question": " 466京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.112490544285452
    },
    {
        "question": " 2742億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.659925350132621
    },
    {
        "question": " 184万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.26439143625064054
    },
    {
        "question": " 4323億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.63576598231292
    },
    {
        "question": " 166万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.22104647025235
    },
    {
        "question": " 345垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.039285745378875
    },
    {
        "question": " 4817兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.746253091083907
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.11垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.057835818375825
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.706080220120912
    },
    {
        "question": " 285兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.454928457382319
    },
    {
        "question": " 8510兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.92995057963669
    },
    {
        "question": " 908万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.9579506135628706
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.5万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.457176606850972
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.1年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.434983624099502
    },
    {
        "question": " 578年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.482574331324578
    },
    {
        "question": " 136億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.572023889944326
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5025492265321472
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.289711155198769
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.49万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0349186237812358
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.3万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.529942119740843
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.11時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.737724754826536
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.68万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.984997463218592
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.513942806726267
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.5万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.08403117149051
    },
    {
        "question": " 3257億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.734664857467207
    },
    {
        "question": " 239分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.156843547488913
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.831179424653443
    },
    {
        "question": " 3374万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.02940597761888819
    },
    {
        "question": " 106兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.090046068299385
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.609259649975062
    },
    {
        "question": " 287万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.679234307258101
    },
    {
        "question": " 334秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.524115108973579
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.57秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.41031034458567
    },
    {
        "question": " 585京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.268412490280463
    },
    {
        "question": " 5414兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.796980381173651
    },
    {
        "question": " 815億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.354892921987002
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.92兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.172147468643526
    },
    {
        "question": " 3474万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.540812842511446
    },
    {
        "question": " 176msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.24469403391379
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.04945268570118
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.6垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.95727933382671
    },
    {
        "question": " 6543億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8792617363642863
    },
    {
        "question": " 737兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.311049626273193
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.351614603500916
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.1億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.492781340098514
    },
    {
        "question": " 5819万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.764884105108912
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.730643064002331
    },
    {
        "question": " 265京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4870202134886705
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.59垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.191329414335502
    },
    {
        "question": " 607京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.005370866637943
    },
    {
        "question": " 751京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.875549372479576
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.9億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.590096815492827
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.6億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.947426448862051
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.28年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.529822723919912
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.746934294519599
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.66万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8628933060791297
    },
    {
        "question": " 4765日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.05826326845543
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.231315059466636
    },
    {
        "question": " 761億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.500990558079776
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.7万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0251701577796455
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5950115952804804
    },
    {
        "question": " 93万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2477126591475287
    },
    {
        "question": " 212億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.168074112308437
    },
    {
        "question": " 423分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8485674025664414
    },
    {
        "question": " 5361万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2304084849305843
    },
    {
        "question": " 533兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.79027985029046
    },
    {
        "question": " 1595億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.646348747276751
    },
    {
        "question": " 104億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.238111511636758
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3474634624547903
    },
    {
        "question": " 766秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.88406691013307
    },
    {
        "question": " 2237億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8509392257539028
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.8億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.565684053651808
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.81249753448553
    },
    {
        "question": " 765万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1057662808103474
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.62兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.664461128672064
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.1兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3013611440861341
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.164145264876227
    },
    {
        "question": " 9404兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.417025667302232
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.345526365425641
    },
    {
        "question": " 7492万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.874578852799742
    },
    {
        "question": " 1兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.0021625652438
    },
    {
        "question": " 279usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.445739183365481
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.995e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8011125284027125
    },
    {
        "question": " 6211垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.856687594943056
    },
    {
        "question": " 1424京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.597231849363579
    },
    {
        "question": " 235京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5920354705616795
    },
    {
        "question": " 328京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.516488551618288
    },
    {
        "question": " 195兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.290729089652682
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.57万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.7460251332677024
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8352899794063733
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.161171366831551
    },
    {
        "question": " 6758年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.550458316527395
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.806401747675325
    },
    {
        "question": " 9178万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.400431997877084
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.320247474218693
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.169794566681626
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.8万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.038681296279944
    },
    {
        "question": " 217億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.95698530480185
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8700748347183582
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5710087695224124
    },
    {
        "question": " 2595万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.255870600067523
    },
    {
        "question": " 690万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.060843969654499
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9006610968863857
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.0208926509389915
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.9分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.540744919747105
    },
    {
        "question": " 239兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.879715794800738
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.9万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5086393344115381
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.9万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.341297077022856
    },
    {
        "question": " 173秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.45871113039710365
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.62秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.9354030840594545
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.296754715824405
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.209442538676955
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.5京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.290166658552495
    },
    {
        "question": " 12兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.143438440311442
    },
    {
        "question": " 462万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10858393137897493
    },
    {
        "question": " 568兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.976368575470643
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.55万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5498375702011347
    },
    {
        "question": " 269万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.429457294667197
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.708201783326107
    },
    {
        "question": " 4507億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7173919885381952
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.41兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1768681372287952
    },
    {
        "question": " 280兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.669258941230133
    },
    {
        "question": " 109兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.03784791409366
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.5億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.929654628303923
    },
    {
        "question": " 1058usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.02433317122192
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.918e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.784121796304351
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.7京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5779928169532313
    },
    {
        "question": " 886兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.390951800087188
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3746501410511636
    },
    {
        "question": " 1189億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.075125685771404
    },
    {
        "question": " 1248兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.096291112032747
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.56万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.4088831402364776
    },
    {
        "question": " 139万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.704686603482767
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.724831461429801
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5081341028939965
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.437914239366168
    },
    {
        "question": " 24万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.539278317621196
    },
    {
        "question": " 975億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.046547747190851
    },
    {
        "question": " 376時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1946318313300985
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.1万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.563692225561148
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.83939662879701
    },
    {
        "question": " 5718億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.036597141329263
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.1億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.122204273994973
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.633283310297162
    },
    {
        "question": " 4803万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.459641772559964
    },
    {
        "question": " 1509兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.679973463478609
    },
    {
        "question": " 180万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3181149519614677
    },
    {
        "question": " 6332秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2452197235233855
    },
    {
        "question": " 5299億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.946026329895297
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.88万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.896394831853401
    },
    {
        "question": " 380億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08085600801301607
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.93兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.904081977258393
    },
    {
        "question": " 218億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.782092615299998
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.54億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.879292637697518
    },
    {
        "question": " 1241msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09377594477097073
    },
    {
        "question": " 96msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.982065787353572
    },
    {
        "question": " 329垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.018589466722577
    },
    {
        "question": " 5837京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.829708496866912
    },
    {
        "question": " 89兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.393229043766713
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.8京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.649855005741271
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.8兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.541938793936467
    },
    {
        "question": " 1177万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.070840381294621
    },
    {
        "question": " 264usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.421059806992745
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.601e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.91628457547595
    },
    {
        "question": " 360京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.619994491370887
    },
    {
        "question": " 9216兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.408233603054238
    },
    {
        "question": " 2496京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.619173568882308
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.05兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.78177592773713
    },
    {
        "question": " 259億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.41326889211024
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.6億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.947471946560699
    },
    {
        "question": " 1699年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.172698625243562
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.904358939753612
    },
    {
        "question": " 297年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.972082240941234
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7866398662014804
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.9日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2246806702360873
    },
    {
        "question": " 2995日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.634806292630747
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.24億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.776570163542879
    },
    {
        "question": " 36億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.175889411615419
    },
    {
        "question": " 291時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.24228710716732
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5641230210184682
    },
    {
        "question": " 579億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.604590308060829
    },
    {
        "question": " 1269万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.325295393539458
    },
    {
        "question": " 22分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1202139474450616
    },
    {
        "question": " 3631分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.338205545277246
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.9分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.254106238244312
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.88億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.496175883152563
    },
    {
        "question": " 3608万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.620823344665065
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.663331266026813
    },
    {
        "question": " 1781万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.472437310987308
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.278567307024563
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.6秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.768086675790107
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.14秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.711089324762032
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.998602465253234
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.69兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.630777267160051
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.832355047162617
    },
    {
        "question": " 106兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.246364080695315
    },
    {
        "question": " 1562msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19360614725926317
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.53msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.930907715499443
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.2msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.366123393733318
    },
    {
        "question": " 8019兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.405339140945977
    },
    {
        "question": " 1519億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24497152981301618
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.456354891869505
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24444407857211026
    },
    {
        "question": " 127億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1035788614772
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.0700925745038259
    },
    {
        "question": " 314usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.497450435156891
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.241e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.851675076037633
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.53垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7193783160119445
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.52垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.099068277227152
    },
    {
        "question": " 6752兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0512706430623755
    },
    {
        "question": " 404億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6066090202707939
    },
    {
        "question": " 263兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.420763389195132
    },
    {
        "question": " 3292万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.517492841842364
    },
    {
        "question": " 61万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.347951453742965
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.86万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.399522094214273
    },
    {
        "question": " 252年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.122630938676473
    },
    {
        "question": " 8282万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.355848985050169
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5808308934053983
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.9日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.990101479734869
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.46日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.58591269211831
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.1万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.909042979274185
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.3億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.022350905164853
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.2時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.265754204860124
    },
    {
        "question": " 466兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.947871570209088
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.44億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.378437179906647
    },
    {
        "question": " 131億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.340346113647806
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.88分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.466604446798911
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.5兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.899345047083687
    },
    {
        "question": " 1121億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.112916355259053
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.682956492864658
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.9億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.696943896536164
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.17万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.713706228252676
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.58兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.381004278631279
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.096807807070887
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.51兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.185019038639661
    },
    {
        "question": " 172万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.458003756599272
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.5万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6854153367539113
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.272216117027628
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.623359937820297
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.098121495663565
    },
    {
        "question": " 5064億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.148233466679661
    },
    {
        "question": " 1993兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.521424494965445
    },
    {
        "question": " 1101万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0417504560592794
    },
    {
        "question": " 4887usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.689035155499943
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.03万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.480936927953648
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.2京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4563514398787725
    },
    {
        "question": " 118垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.134990872873693
    },
    {
        "question": " 299垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.919871606808318
    },
    {
        "question": " 2946京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.691092417745205
    },
    {
        "question": " 7223億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8587387215998117
    },
    {
        "question": " 1005兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.002030709069517
    },
    {
        "question": " 247億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.392841993758971
    },
    {
        "question": " 2126年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.270070670944744
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.8年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.558489978243267
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.2年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.47269044869838
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.08兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.92587578009366
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.2日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9948180411602463
    },
    {
        "question": " 181日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.194130085920376
    },
    {
        "question": " 8390万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9812810205642677
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.630333189516209
    },
    {
        "question": " 246万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.169713316661863
    },
    {
        "question": " 9861時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.550214409440573
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.793127748712497
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.876950714908792
    },
    {
        "question": " 512万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5509132635300835
    },
    {
        "question": " 796億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.122544748646021
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.49分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3204644289116882
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.918825180710238
    },
    {
        "question": " 6058億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.283518944758421
    },
    {
        "question": " 265兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.487354744555201
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.43兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.178420018972478
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.4億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.719306051984411
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.048271855560342
    },
    {
        "question": " 1430秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.155225883363386
    },
    {
        "question": " 593兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.274275760895724
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.86兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.958937185296092
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4521882682070615
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.25億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0178137266411
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0223867602219734
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.205505591584023
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.6msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.93445300293013
    },
    {
        "question": " 1179兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5728666648039136
    },
    {
        "question": " 247京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.457053852559227
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.636688049212772
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.307924274702369
    },
    {
        "question": " 8165兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.911974315622691
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.41兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.382813792373902
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.287e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.018054210391796
    },
    {
        "question": " 352京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.609697182742028
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.4京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.245611919547521
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.439282839493865
    },
    {
        "question": " 474兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.675933920466426
    },
    {
        "question": " 487万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.6879674069371688
    },
    {
        "question": " 1714万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.2341142704997345
    },
    {
        "question": " 520日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15361460293357831
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.84万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.37304476245906
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.59日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.092458346413769
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.71万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.36871179253292
    },
    {
        "question": " 12万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1369156410941372
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.1時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5743998962662822
    },
    {
        "question": " 16時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.982782518157814
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.360644889304132
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.4億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3390777683607915
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.248288759490886
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.77万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.721046086194703
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.63億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1665149547088283
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.2万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6103453650227297
    },
    {
        "question": " 497億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.139882389386375
    },
    {
        "question": " 65億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.034911563428143
    },
    {
        "question": " 478万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.679602960564456
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.2884516327028805
    },
    {
        "question": " 8003兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.404426558785916
    },
    {
        "question": " 655億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8798958193646786
    },
    {
        "question": " 1121兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.493240581340041
    },
    {
        "question": " 130万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.335445723618388
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.3億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.605512868621528
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.385394137968552
    },
    {
        "question": " 148京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.671286711747522
    },
    {
        "question": " 788京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.96017413125899
    },
    {
        "question": " 1346兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.572636999917809
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.4億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0173516905914877
    },
    {
        "question": " 211兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.32386061033898
    },
    {
        "question": " 2538usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.4044909068653424
    },
    {
        "question": " 111万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.045441104557755
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.936801786983666
    },
    {
        "question": " 5751兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8232205084012987
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.559960203458306
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.9京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.812890554337508
    },
    {
        "question": " 3942兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.595704105308102
    },
    {
        "question": " 5184万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.7146846362743262
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.04万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.6067288782319677
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.92年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.714599818743251
    },
    {
        "question": " 225年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.073259269839058
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.85万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.023160117848187
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.8日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.755872231571442
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.731022471561646
    },
    {
        "question": " 1745万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.299218424946896
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.8万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3260502942998365
    },
    {
        "question": " 1866時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.049010497453842
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.600150950746448
    },
    {
        "question": " 162兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.489636960948685
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.3万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8252050517723504
    },
    {
        "question": " 649万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.034096337751021
    },
    {
        "question": " 764万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.661022774959541
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.5分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.110064628771132
    },
    {
        "question": " 3031億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.982849140621787
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3286777250517146
    },
    {
        "question": " 4908億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.134639028298956
    },
    {
        "question": " 66万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.041360411600134
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.66秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7530745022082854
    },
    {
        "question": " 6243兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.296592728940258
    },
    {
        "question": " 197億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3569632901854565
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.524513412356643
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.03億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7035853005684816
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.29兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.798321925586201
    },
    {
        "question": " 2094msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.320932959540462
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.266843195077113
    },
    {
        "question": " 5776億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.825110289454658
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.86京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.339192519379783
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.88京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.91033323386941
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.53兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.742423557075128
    },
    {
        "question": " 1756万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.244641024300718
    },
    {
        "question": " 123京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5905108839762827
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.46垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.602265248817636
    },
    {
        "question": " 8986兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.397278778769377
    },
    {
        "question": " 3221億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7298557538053252
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.9京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.611702939218954
    },
    {
        "question": " 267万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.42636251746626885
    },
    {
        "question": " 346万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.53859970967225
    },
    {
        "question": " 926年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.909140267267895
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.619004806104818
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.58万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.260100018345975
    },
    {
        "question": " 2048日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.469760408683384
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.42日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.320664987286597
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.1億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.339375609581163
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7541591313320275
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0737668869936607
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8332173873737485
    },
    {
        "question": " 6127万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.066562559040006
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2103441335849452
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.84万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9881109044163146
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.3万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.424825684258681
    },
    {
        "question": " 8090万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.409171182358653
    },
    {
        "question": " 592兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.835765638392454
    },
    {
        "question": " 6593万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.262791175181033
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.18万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9363338014543383
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.9秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.83809607624133
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.630164641434373
    },
    {
        "question": " 16兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7059683288988134
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.32341737432481255
    },
    {
        "question": " 504万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14625161702378042
    },
    {
        "question": " 3591億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.777063828997697
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.45万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8723312938740377
    },
    {
        "question": " 254万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.405011068004683
    },
    {
        "question": " 39兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09201436913689243
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.9兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6187103556505518
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.1兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9502915071061215
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.255456212557654
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.1億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.464031124227378
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.149709688673708
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.72万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.570165517421787
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.188e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.841162032204795
    },
    {
        "question": " 21垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3867388320504554
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.51京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.184719486083752
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.43兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.757715807939274
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.306941049226145
    },
    {
        "question": " 9137万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.9607850734783172
    },
    {
        "question": " 2608万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.416325007859598
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.15年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1803951854084076
    },
    {
        "question": " 442年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.366470149128356
    },
    {
        "question": " 5520万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1796309913360385
    },
    {
        "question": " 545日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.116698187814341
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.2日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.541795531805053
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.49日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.865422418064252
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.22兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.68307922617874
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.676275587198832
    },
    {
        "question": " 233万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.1461528392688
    },
    {
        "question": " 252時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.957696891405119
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.64兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.101363467563486
    },
    {
        "question": " 904億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.797839089012497
    },
    {
        "question": " 37億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.789700201251721
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.11万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.737459149505206
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.47万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.706282587277798
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.4兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.881121561089788
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.37億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5907784125953923
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.7万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2199093271827888
    },
    {
        "question": " 275億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.66134346342942
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.1兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.90010048469874
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.19京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.56789214382023
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.75億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0172809175723048
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.433273823903998
    },
    {
        "question": " 1875万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.272904296083222
    },
    {
        "question": " 134万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.12830380031216
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.4京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.10711919376297
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.52兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4643147364429565
    },
    {
        "question": " 1503億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6206456823968662
    },
    {
        "question": " 4342億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.859571309974358
    },
    {
        "question": " 5542兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.743647367202566
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.96兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.775561942003081
    },
    {
        "question": " 4405垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.145129764657565
    },
    {
        "question": " 278京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.508015952726532
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.8兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1748258044917337
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.312134208600565
    },
    {
        "question": " 920億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9639556971353156
    },
    {
        "question": " 232万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.3660303808492482
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.1億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.793215388253974
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.38年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2038348765882385
    },
    {
        "question": " 4016億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.041458198652816
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.54万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.037621795127311
    },
    {
        "question": " 1573日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.355018726898923
    },
    {
        "question": " 7478日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.810262379227629
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.29日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.799171553469295
    },
    {
        "question": " 373億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.628931013974699
    },
    {
        "question": " 103時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6339915535768015
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.054917045305417
    },
    {
        "question": " 138億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.417723831764996
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.5億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.736690152037137
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.52万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6236827028473773
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.7分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.575171735535021
    },
    {
        "question": " 3843分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.362818999887992
    },
    {
        "question": " 472億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.174858864048915
    },
    {
        "question": " 6906万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.902723250388588
    },
    {
        "question": " 2969億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9162776432223305
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.393869816914376
    },
    {
        "question": " 12秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.080232134434571
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.250164403967755
    },
    {
        "question": " 5154京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.213306954356067
    },
    {
        "question": " 102億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.07307515940243
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.07兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.227010054560597
    },
    {
        "question": " 307兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.708491783987935
    },
    {
        "question": " 111万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0456258061052277
    },
    {
        "question": " 696msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.842739695552092
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.41京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.145202003497026
    },
    {
        "question": " 3996億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6651005694893575
    },
    {
        "question": " 342京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.977341774063634
    },
    {
        "question": " 525兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.942313294752593
    },
    {
        "question": " 2370億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.374786305089784
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.0537311042228588
    },
    {
        "question": " 629usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.798341085665668
    },
    {
        "question": " 1977京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7972841319408728
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1914200208657615
    },
    {
        "question": " 9290兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.411692593714777
    },
    {
        "question": " 1033京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.2359277375247
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.78兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.443319654774638
    },
    {
        "question": " 442兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.645339925921057
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.121214548504051
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.44年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.478767009602845
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.8年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.664117206387808
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.59年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.05375066460109
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.3万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3737399095865173
    },
    {
        "question": " 395万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.976545098848793
    },
    {
        "question": " 4098億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.670079153854052
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.3億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.256733871514086
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.929154400115427
    },
    {
        "question": " 3052分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.32617324148382365
    },
    {
        "question": " 5430億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.956610985466043
    },
    {
        "question": " 196分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.070398520150765
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.5兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.139509788833754
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.408138603663461
    },
    {
        "question": " 304億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9271206629119355
    },
    {
        "question": " 192秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5049398504442537
    },
    {
        "question": " 2462秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.39128119630247
    },
    {
        "question": " 144兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.658242506657042
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.9兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6644100040903815
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.01兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.398215547156401
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.3兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.923579389074561
    },
    {
        "question": " 6822億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.83389167171772
    },
    {
        "question": " 940msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.97306115701382
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.7垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.875770140143431
    },
    {
        "question": " 1569億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2592236593002828
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.2京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.308246588649311
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.3億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6423406134387153
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.45兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7360410523257155
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.41億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.382764850001632
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.598073875153187
    },
    {
        "question": " 389京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.653951653925369
    },
    {
        "question": " 501京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.143909052650534
    },
    {
        "question": " 1761兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.46768787326892
    },
    {
        "question": " 7935兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.899572023630194
    },
    {
        "question": " 1800万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.255271014037087
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.11億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.613710417054349
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.7年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.398852820391014
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.9年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.367653774071522
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.76億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.012941991277186
    },
    {
        "question": " 2173万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.717332298581551
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.09万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.116809813457843
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.143707221291377
    },
    {
        "question": " 409万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.668883562508819
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.8万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9773805585021993
    },
    {
        "question": " 926万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.744936402840489
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.8万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.388504409507904
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.4万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07420738380240488
    },
    {
        "question": " 1442億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.000699003070888
    },
    {
        "question": " 374分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7943988129880353
    },
    {
        "question": " 1975分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.07373735931224
    },
    {
        "question": " 7608分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.65940921127715
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.873779601568668
    },
    {
        "question": " 1044億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.082389227035465
    },
    {
        "question": " 526億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.16432632487329
    },
    {
        "question": " 3124万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.716498677369345
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.1797887642509055
    },
    {
        "question": " 122京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.58697125950647
    },
    {
        "question": " 5025億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7646336845750348
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4524195918532525
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.2万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.200295238028658
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.034383232066206
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.629947330242656
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.6京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.811994231368668
    },
    {
        "question": " 4665兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.112541899125229
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.4京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.915413712235114
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.7億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5652144426023535
    },
    {
        "question": " 271億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.433499235128455
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.2493124794617545
    },
    {
        "question": " 638京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.306225572999364
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.93垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.836576708252724
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6543850859808242
    },
    {
        "question": " 468京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8918656308368105
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.9京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.632401992312072
    },
    {
        "question": " 3611万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5575834280098733
    },
    {
        "question": " 2826億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.451111906935914
    },
    {
        "question": " 297年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.034824175025418
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.7年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.368481598247006
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.2億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.917701275924822
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.6万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.977351344346044
    },
    {
        "question": " 982日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.150395214961543
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.003053801306372
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.191239646402605
    },
    {
        "question": " 27万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.050397092758748
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.9万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.485230174048447
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.607045475229793
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.18兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.135333849000683
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.48万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.653045354947229
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.3億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.137156821276095
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9117851967800057
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.14分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.489417510432358
    },
    {
        "question": " 431兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.136159146355022
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.1兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8490461882934115
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.6億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.260517319485373
    },
    {
        "question": " 1353万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.35300619100639
    },
    {
        "question": " 159秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.201698019262317
    },
    {
        "question": " 121兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5855505819421927
    },
    {
        "question": " 3569億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6160767386115342
    },
    {
        "question": " 4709兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.116610571844948
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.4万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.849131020480024
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.7兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.567828661038268
    },
    {
        "question": " 9万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.954366298243145
    },
    {
        "question": " 2094msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.320959761261047
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.645724951733403
    },
    {
        "question": " 1445兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.223505676910035
    },
    {
        "question": " 8457億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.370912128665692
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.92兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.172310830110124
    },
    {
        "question": " 166億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.219702039598706
    },
    {
        "question": " 4864usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.6870377227472113
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.284986551250551
    },
    {
        "question": " 946垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.477048236365027
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2507381398096706
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.7垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.438109881088547
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.12京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.716379694955096
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.2億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7089746438658295
    },
    {
        "question": " 1067億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.028048177979178
    },
    {
        "question": " 1066万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.0277376133687195
    },
    {
        "question": " 14年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.087412671848175
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.473444770373693
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.39億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.816576320140236
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6075137225780343
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.94万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.531718366090805
    },
    {
        "question": " 1985億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.35533633181566
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7842171953578543
    },
    {
        "question": " 435時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.195026090863989
    },
    {
        "question": " 136時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.689690188425704
    },
    {
        "question": " 1236万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3713792812300285
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.8万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.754396005064251
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4073027207050735
    },
    {
        "question": " 3175分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.279908102187348
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.76億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0759261637743056
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.39億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7954530548116807
    },
    {
        "question": " 1060万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4688406433160504
    },
    {
        "question": " 2595億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.636018931324898
    },
    {
        "question": " 175秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.242415400248831
    },
    {
        "question": " 3809兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.081991120316972
    },
    {
        "question": " 107億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.09151026712897
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.449611090876001
    },
    {
        "question": " 2758万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6624159657230173
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.06万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.906585457770309
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.08垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.819674466054288
    },
    {
        "question": " 1122京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.113620817297361
    },
    {
        "question": " 272兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.878390068418076
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.87億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.809230372339732
    },
    {
        "question": " 964億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.983935852302449
    },
    {
        "question": " 331億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.5200038487803
    },
    {
        "question": " 301万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.47887633334953
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.4京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03318483468477962
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.437155766394129
    },
    {
        "question": " 195京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7344332053903475
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.494509080389842
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.067702604328279
    },
    {
        "question": " 267億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.427215984560815
    },
    {
        "question": " 319万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.503381191399133
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.7万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.843950916168831
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.483947463868668
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.03日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.063305069552998
    },
    {
        "question": " 610日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.721821791525002
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.5日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.543616883305823
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.9億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.95486227293691
    },
    {
        "question": " 103万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.632627479402188
    },
    {
        "question": " 2858時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.234144001962708
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.897848081257823
    },
    {
        "question": " 7478億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.15313692904155
    },
    {
        "question": " 513万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5516171032862975
    },
    {
        "question": " 5281分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9445847381585124
    },
    {
        "question": " 1227分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.867021860747803
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.85073535036537
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.6億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8926172802020047
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.97億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.535809412971509
    },
    {
        "question": " 142万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5953998104820784
    },
    {
        "question": " 214億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.552053288117886
    },
    {
        "question": " 7172秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.855617406777279
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.13秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.61601499411492
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.666117969750256
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.4億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8655313577384236
    },
    {
        "question": " 2606兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.85974336556884
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.7兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.648058923727787
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.08兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.488283207551834
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.55msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.81608594829944
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.8msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.714195756944463
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5826568982743145
    },
    {
        "question": " 5123兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.773062024844585
    },
    {
        "question": " 4084億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0547385294381915
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.6京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.997402751570531
    },
    {
        "question": " 1533万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1854345335716021
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.9万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.7916282194702777
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.7万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.957464414460986
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.9垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.272300078178141
    },
    {
        "question": " 711兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9156301078995566
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.4兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0604876398035334
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.42垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.867430052766345
    },
    {
        "question": " 508京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.705747638702512
    },
    {
        "question": " 176兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.245705127545175
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.220021294624169
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.33万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4274160567641605
    },
    {
        "question": " 2167年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.278396510625598
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.5年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.615418434311723
    },
    {
        "question": " 2814日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.886995821075649
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.56日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7887397790213921
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.88日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.106911918443315
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.208523776741088
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.6万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.430301904582114
    },
    {
        "question": " 1439時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.936278041835536
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.565157183301732
    },
    {
        "question": " 2304億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.641867059793374
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.3万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3635572691601414
    },
    {
        "question": " 1212億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.3054625164717
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.9万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.485156168478666
    },
    {
        "question": " 691分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.617818585777875
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.44億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2365250057553379
    },
    {
        "question": " 1918万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3462907065685923
    },
    {
        "question": " 1373万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5812880896237043
    },
    {
        "question": " 473億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.896991802769463
    },
    {
        "question": " 4926秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.692492727547257
    },
    {
        "question": " 773秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.888065363119006
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.275609841416296
    },
    {
        "question": " 2169兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.837441499925561
    },
    {
        "question": " 629兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.862264101915406
    },
    {
        "question": " 348億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9847042354888274
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.6兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.777700069948574
    },
    {
        "question": " 1269億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.103589735612474
    },
    {
        "question": " 126msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.101280225183162
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.523935286460043
    },
    {
        "question": " 4304兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.697353417533305
    },
    {
        "question": " 337京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.970798028530888
    },
    {
        "question": " 52京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.937977027218901
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.2億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9203839343336133
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.29兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.72384704417943
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.713061126649096
    },
    {
        "question": " 1402兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2102707505169585
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.31京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.078300561545342
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.49京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.199197455291633
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.89兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.838393494524437
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.4億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6934292479993394
    },
    {
        "question": " 9896億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.995449960142924
    },
    {
        "question": " 1260万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.662511397762554
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.61年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.606059103678122
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.74548642866078
    },
    {
        "question": " 12万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.515093852455408
    },
    {
        "question": " 17日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6119047066954693
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.262805931367636
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.061795006248238
    },
    {
        "question": " 3082時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1086001462672046
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.8時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.657971536776945
    },
    {
        "question": " 678時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.387782740989251
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.3時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.336743325326237
    },
    {
        "question": " 994兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.276847373409034
    },
    {
        "question": " 517億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.554725672839685
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.45万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.093776371598925
    },
    {
        "question": " 122億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5889335621362997
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.63億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8852889686795065
    },
    {
        "question": " 860万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3781434735893514
    },
    {
        "question": " 2580億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.633539971990244
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.3秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.7806044865353
    },
    {
        "question": " 1272秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.104587837402315
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.34秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.72745307028654
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7604107357823773
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.144126942040359
    },
    {
        "question": " 4195万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0664572842298914
    },
    {
        "question": " 8420億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.147151284600661
    },
    {
        "question": " 665億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.822755497581426
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.3兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15763319826212263
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.91兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.655837248702543
    },
    {
        "question": " 423兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0698570142861685
    },
    {
        "question": " 125億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3178050108043156
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.9兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.112194324104047
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.8億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.730498200587391
    },
    {
        "question": " 415usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.61758714333636
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.4京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3788405140732451
    },
    {
        "question": " 340垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.595395520387212
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5850579936961431
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.2京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.157336940466196
    },
    {
        "question": " 6911億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.839529146388653
    },
    {
        "question": " 153億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.184587872979531
    },
    {
        "question": " 9667億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.985298001877789
    },
    {
        "question": " 4117年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.176882458393664
    },
    {
        "question": " 166年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.719178491342067
    },
    {
        "question": " 1557日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6299494068767331
    },
    {
        "question": " 1165日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4466566057656385
    },
    {
        "question": " 651日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.971627704991391
    },
    {
        "question": " 229日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.295399049138805
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.1万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8436058166760005
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.8万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.894931028339925
    },
    {
        "question": " 2647時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.979116811039601
    },
    {
        "question": " 345億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.817706233333095
    },
    {
        "question": " 102万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.852062855451903
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.7億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.737000731401761
    },
    {
        "question": " 2782分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.222577482070684
    },
    {
        "question": " 129兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.610870330817166
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.5万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.45183299861768056
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.713834587881818
    },
    {
        "question": " 3543万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7711771243681635
    },
    {
        "question": " 851万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.929917650651577
    },
    {
        "question": " 886兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.448515886424319
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.55億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.721070491151653
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.8億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.064513539868817
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.321209169094003
    },
    {
        "question": " 128億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.10888493539627
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.6msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.440930122838522
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.937312836277638
    },
    {
        "question": " 1872兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.335739937198096
    },
    {
        "question": " 892兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3938581444379805
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.54京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.879107070983332
    },
    {
        "question": " 767億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.885030792161929
    },
    {
        "question": " 1935万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.286772531316462
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.56万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.745376798004372
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.89京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19020027448070187
    },
    {
        "question": " 395垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.659681664207394
    },
    {
        "question": " 146垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.607049581632246
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.7兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8310402648623043
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.4兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.404732168928657
    },
    {
        "question": " 154万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.18846777134638892
    },
    {
        "question": " 5276億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.722299690196072
    },
    {
        "question": " 1592万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.764114962779896
    },
    {
        "question": " 1941日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7257581537235924
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5897102644566108
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.2万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.950744210344823
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.096839343231979
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.08万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1079915500255515
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.9億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5991337381212807
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.25億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.194176068066705
    },
    {
        "question": " 2892分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6830022370579056
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.999571941101158
    },
    {
        "question": " 2227分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.125803976282258
    },
    {
        "question": " 34億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0331660413989283
    },
    {
        "question": " 470兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.73525000747451
    },
    {
        "question": " 3462万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9830675215694757
    },
    {
        "question": " 354億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.770259308817923
    },
    {
        "question": " 230秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.360960017315154
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.1京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.092938971799984
    },
    {
        "question": " 343兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.598298591733656
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.71億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.01313952202693
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.81兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.986392780553891
    },
    {
        "question": " 2136msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3296797962887954
    },
    {
        "question": " 21万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.322019511681216
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.64msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.883209276256065
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.71垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.174577735607466
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.077371516358841
    },
    {
        "question": " 4126億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0592430749424695
    },
    {
        "question": " 9811兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.213585006501171
    },
    {
        "question": " 4696兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.671736922193746
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.045417478835402
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.8京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2646011122309433
    },
    {
        "question": " 586垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.83135202459902
    },
    {
        "question": " 1557京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.635897329616302
    },
    {
        "question": " 208京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.540000625203387
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.2京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7927253315194145
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.1兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.806976839078641
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.2万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.4941537548589032
    },
    {
        "question": " 240万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.942361683903913
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.631292653214853
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.7万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8296432205863207
    },
    {
        "question": " 7552日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.258236851686663
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.06日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.785373718225659
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.56日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.916786568465099
    },
    {
        "question": " 3935億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.652415429530951
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.2万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.255270519687818
    },
    {
        "question": " 181時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.035494353643686
    },
    {
        "question": " 255万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.963682298771472
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.8兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.083901819363929
    },
    {
        "question": " 214万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.172075931039471
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.11万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1811783309836317
    },
    {
        "question": " 344分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.314986963510668
    },
    {
        "question": " 423億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1277653545628734
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5217030105159393
    },
    {
        "question": " 383万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.02693869598313
    },
    {
        "question": " 4915万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.91341358300361
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.1秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.545516238999055
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.84京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.267700278654287
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1605892208656121
    },
    {
        "question": " 2403億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.824457801261175
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.9万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6000308724942738
    },
    {
        "question": " 4795億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.680827030421051
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.068072230428989
    },
    {
        "question": " 235垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.872412888216695
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.183865438743954
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8566417569623495
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.02兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.527371752637691
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.010438240422931
    },
    {
        "question": " 1627万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.211293130700663
    },
    {
        "question": " 4369usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.6403674665680255
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.365e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8750997240228715
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.8京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7516624870598623
    },
    {
        "question": " 1326京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.566174190743083
    },
    {
        "question": " 3663兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.785708469602335
    },
    {
        "question": " 1741兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.240842894382381
    },
    {
        "question": " 9159億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.9618694557191185
    },
    {
        "question": " 114万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.0587483147308347
    },
    {
        "question": " 762年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.824273610077309
    },
    {
        "question": " 7406万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3072934776104645
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.463606890178638
    },
    {
        "question": " 2399万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4374437073595643
    },
    {
        "question": " 1031万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.632986597477859
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.67万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.494549886464464
    },
    {
        "question": " 1846時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.822476463215567
    },
    {
        "question": " 492億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9712495670296875
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.3億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.576385853414405
    },
    {
        "question": " 317億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.723317572460754
    },
    {
        "question": " 460兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.164059733499043
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.3万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5732139961260163
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.786614999310883
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3426198114680763
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.81兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.394004807228395
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.15140039584367
    },
    {
        "question": " 1603万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6485664240223588
    },
    {
        "question": " 9251万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.188033939287002
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.020168335459656
    },
    {
        "question": " 350京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.045852089475288
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.116969522255143
    },
    {
        "question": " 3476京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.984787254188097
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.87兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.809913476264688
    },
    {
        "question": " 9171億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.962430961001411
    },
    {
        "question": " 508億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.705975232182851
    },
    {
        "question": " 273usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.436905717547265
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.4垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2960831896609
    },
    {
        "question": " 571京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.820051113944736
    },
    {
        "question": " 5834兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2096845464492754
    },
    {
        "question": " 517京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9354353071479515
    },
    {
        "question": " 143兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.155232879548137
    },
    {
        "question": " 6442億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.808991701199574
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.084328310076682
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.66年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3857640712434103
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.92509699012621
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.7年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.451367681277823
    },
    {
        "question": " 4826億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.121289608640065
    },
    {
        "question": " 744万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.251915175492957
    },
    {
        "question": " 1526日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.1199404449467
    },
    {
        "question": " 200万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.358619787901697
    },
    {
        "question": " 2591万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.033189112855784
    },
    {
        "question": " 108万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.590521774964998
    },
    {
        "question": " 61億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.064879545241753
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.6万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.638413244496207
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.11万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1815962928174413
    },
    {
        "question": " 228万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.136187821207125
    },
    {
        "question": " 154兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.688379504790925
    },
    {
        "question": " 2260億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.417663123107785
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.76兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.204363657440974
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.97億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5171080727703234
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.193562854239104
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.15京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.999949402121399
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.69兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.629993014626718
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.1億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9346336877955372
    },
    {
        "question": " 1147億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.281300132037902
    },
    {
        "question": " 177億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2491222746474016
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.4msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.946452256243079
    },
    {
        "question": " 932京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.470793738871725
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.3兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.719231627483052
    },
    {
        "question": " 18兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6988182892386456
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.67191447999258
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.99億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7775957652904584
    },
    {
        "question": " 696億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.842352644609366
    },
    {
        "question": " 3037usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.482386502499649
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.684e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.171862757993768
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.474808436038958
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.15兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.35489819876074913
    },
    {
        "question": " 6854京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.057813751661284
    },
    {
        "question": " 266兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.425615387735996
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.6億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.8423847798407254
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.5億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.676545199310011
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.45年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.099714191612284
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.57万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.351840083795812
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.61年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.384444255180628
    },
    {
        "question": " 528万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.16001544456031
    },
    {
        "question": " 1086万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.416220261516054
    },
    {
        "question": " 4514日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.812926990168378
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.09642313838159
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.196975142515864
    },
    {
        "question": " 30兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.53412632494776
    },
    {
        "question": " 126時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7202280004412898
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.07万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.627646380490882
    },
    {
        "question": " 5048万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.982453946426015
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.6億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.758513149337947
    },
    {
        "question": " 5291分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9453870701606812
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.76547277666805
    },
    {
        "question": " 143万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2195083093219017
    },
    {
        "question": " 1781万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.694306691225815
    },
    {
        "question": " 9623万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.205171887489817
    },
    {
        "question": " 119万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.076252910972084
    },
    {
        "question": " 3859億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.08769521270916
    },
    {
        "question": " 2637億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.484685873503246
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.879352620344292
    },
    {
        "question": " 261兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.63777695095814
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.275682400442198
    },
    {
        "question": " 209万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.320582475780352
    },
    {
        "question": " 16msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.204974641326375
    },
    {
        "question": " 370京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.068860886296785
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2373164441737385
    },
    {
        "question": " 160京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.649098491096291
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5948788579432
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.7億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.768633752718644
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.162162784876357
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.674246189147777
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.169042381634859
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4711825152345728
    },
    {
        "question": " 5323京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.947999883404107
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.5億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4555421399589765
    },
    {
        "question": " 4205万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6237184372105007
    },
    {
        "question": " 1289nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.110107631147357
    },
    {
        "question": " 434年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.200262468890035
    },
    {
        "question": " 6615億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.258208952142146
    },
    {
        "question": " 24万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.76128594001621
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.51万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.812543653354532
    },
    {
        "question": " 121日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.019543562971764
    },
    {
        "question": " 84万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.981661837065769
    },
    {
        "question": " 1601時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8241110796699467
    },
    {
        "question": " 824時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.693819469190537
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.1兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.987318359589186
    },
    {
        "question": " 1711分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0749419614340896
    },
    {
        "question": " 558分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9682440222683164
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.38分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.646430609211075
    },
    {
        "question": " 512兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.210268949811647
    },
    {
        "question": " 1278億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.170012233854826
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.63億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.003969267383358
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.399614310392777
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.23秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.8589268453687255
    },
    {
        "question": " 189兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7766365162360516
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.91億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5268626588656178
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.7兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.316760606075188
    },
    {
        "question": " 1301億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.336067002323703
    },
    {
        "question": " 105億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.022634968778069
    },
    {
        "question": " 6002msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.778276765568695
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.76msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.677282583785871
    },
    {
        "question": " 269垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.931608673691173
    },
    {
        "question": " 324兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.573551257267218
    },
    {
        "question": " 279億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8892113548208536
    },
    {
        "question": " 110兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.264992725755899
    },
    {
        "question": " 4680兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.670268823595357
    },
    {
        "question": " 266万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.425396419531328
    },
    {
        "question": " 13万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.115479715578227
    },
    {
        "question": " 2875京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.959859783281844
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.4京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9327237923725735
    },
    {
        "question": " 17垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.673151670001879
    },
    {
        "question": " 4507億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8757367273356964
    },
    {
        "question": " 2775兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.443263911421394
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.01億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.9036429842880382
    },
    {
        "question": " 2292nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.36028361543833487
    },
    {
        "question": " 2102年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.884830858796992
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.4年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.357829571925657
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.7万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2930386320692495
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.2日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1941891997268392
    },
    {
        "question": " 4610日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.822086481069048
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.04万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.543180326101691
    },
    {
        "question": " 715億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.911542817382252
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.8億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.57316963736282
    },
    {
        "question": " 158万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.755677382296463
    },
    {
        "question": " 4452万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9279180775466531
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.7億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.461670658199365
    },
    {
        "question": " 480万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.902806594224387
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.878688062908516
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.26分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.574704708012053
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.673068760061629
    },
    {
        "question": " 7620万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.945444296763271
    },
    {
        "question": " 9956秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4417907759206541
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.31億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.741177554393646
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.57754863246112
    },
    {
        "question": " 450秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.65300617018998
    },
    {
        "question": " 2029億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8084607837573066
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5844049727304643
    },
    {
        "question": " 502億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.144111179983289
    },
    {
        "question": " 829万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1403115931516323
    },
    {
        "question": " 1886msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.27561946790803704
    },
    {
        "question": " 105京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.522626874395565
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3789832450671176
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.6億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.007277420490041653
    },
    {
        "question": " 1558億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.414475561926219
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.83兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.683593556162607
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.23兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.859151972042486
    },
    {
        "question": " 3961usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.597784191868149
    },
    {
        "question": " 1888垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.777190171006261
    },
    {
        "question": " 243京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4490204768054
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.750600671060458
    },
    {
        "question": " 2249兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.573822144037823
    },
    {
        "question": " 437京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.640386548745854
    },
    {
        "question": " 1051億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.02140940885597
    },
    {
        "question": " 1422nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.1529162878490231
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.9年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.152526837776488
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.982556901957108
    },
    {
        "question": " 2697億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.868655881355297
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.9日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8974738009140264
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.414441852180484
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.360714943916493
    },
    {
        "question": " 365時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1822807307991312
    },
    {
        "question": " 1691万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.006316758858746
    },
    {
        "question": " 2847時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.010711674649306
    },
    {
        "question": " 2423万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6636848571665719
    },
    {
        "question": " 130万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.954156354791132
    },
    {
        "question": " 1318億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.341703516166145
    },
    {
        "question": " 421万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.40209254579041
    },
    {
        "question": " 2643分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.200280343250203
    },
    {
        "question": " 401億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.104422037727834
    },
    {
        "question": " 6038億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.844416721124182
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.680359452717745
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.1万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.754763295947706
    },
    {
        "question": " 653万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.815195541364343
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.6秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.485102545545682
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.7京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.325520721659262
    },
    {
        "question": " 494億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.757341864238608
    },
    {
        "question": " 307兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.930992015280459
    },
    {
        "question": " 19兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.499600075740224
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.09億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.611916085771389
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.1008130853346696
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.91京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.340938623599844
    },
    {
        "question": " 905億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.02009577698954823
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.1億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.34723936942597344
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.238157857820912
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.29304852476642
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.121129968720629
    },
    {
        "question": " 192万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.282518908514705
    },
    {
        "question": " 1375京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.639578500912658
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2552799524267018
    },
    {
        "question": " 3125京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.938607693346919
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.345604545306273
    },
    {
        "question": " 236京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.37342129965336
    },
    {
        "question": " 97億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.98671113445931
    },
    {
        "question": " 4693nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.6714799546043249
    },
    {
        "question": " 249年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.958732546821285
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.979302407299068
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.908559077920272
    },
    {
        "question": " 120億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.516005243258494
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.6日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9892073505026504
    },
    {
        "question": " 2930億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.52437285929626
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.8万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.476075242398297
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.113756943251874
    },
    {
        "question": " 496時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.252069814642472
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.888004360162695
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.33億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.80148316586603
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.71億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.668511362038369
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3448712679448325
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9683420331077917
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.82兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.184149839187047
    },
    {
        "question": " 21万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.385858798543951
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.05兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.292178280674415
    },
    {
        "question": " 282万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.671559538877439
    },
    {
        "question": " 36秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.55679138231018
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.936344030881738
    },
    {
        "question": " 174億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.303694105118421
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.38億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9726726967963115
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2582303165101263
    },
    {
        "question": " 1027万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0113956236786965
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.33万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.366848849641561
    },
    {
        "question": " 656兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3180005605465483
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.7兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.906580493766673
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.6兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8848039785019095
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.437964451271041
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2838606757637736
    },
    {
        "question": " 10万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.0008049932685203
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.6usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.551491741959621
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.754607042036695
    },
    {
        "question": " 1393垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.207405657913803
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.96京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.34469857737715
    },
    {
        "question": " 3527京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.769307363549327
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.9億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8913247609715724
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.0803370154047873
    },
    {
        "question": " 873億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.94088515312308
    },
    {
        "question": " 697年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.405396136998743
    },
    {
        "question": " 3431年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.256100558644475
    },
    {
        "question": " 2008日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7404012232109136
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.1万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.813142037342663
    },
    {
        "question": " 781日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.829011534259063
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.3万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.580151214435187
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.1万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.982865020601994
    },
    {
        "question": " 1640時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.993088556733261
    },
    {
        "question": " 8632億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.21548320425632
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.7億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3557532925927465
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.5万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.840247788338301
    },
    {
        "question": " 2126分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.105657416365187
    },
    {
        "question": " 38分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.357441089372293
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.11分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.563849458517417
    },
    {
        "question": " 135億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.632806697801322
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1534622667712355
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6117353598803563
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.357622031856991
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.6秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.803590153526368
    },
    {
        "question": " 5798秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.76331212952147
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.8兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.976103752884589
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.36666214829321
    },
    {
        "question": " 1089兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.480631326018564
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3622242986586799
    },
    {
        "question": " 8027万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.904574062529827
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.315649210299668
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.16msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.6192908974155795
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6782948129703685
    },
    {
        "question": " 1839兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.328110698875893
    },
    {
        "question": " 147兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6105333606168735
    },
    {
        "question": " 128億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.329587957351822
    },
    {
        "question": " 97億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9867598149637407
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.1億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.8695824633251945
    },
    {
        "question": " 275京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9409040882711348
    },
    {
        "question": " 5461兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8007390129974854
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.89076198385756
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.7兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6536096396310718
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.9兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.723090673473299
    },
    {
        "question": " 9109億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.9594940406388694
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.5万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.483777731518252
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.1万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.521137833770003
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.448738451725932
    },
    {
        "question": " 2889億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.89842565975317
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4394893509581852
    },
    {
        "question": " 20日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.236817005563823
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.2兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.713068221562386
    },
    {
        "question": " 3971時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.218674790203452
    },
    {
        "question": " 4463万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.42780610330518
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.86兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.273151005137686
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.38兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.217587980000571
    },
    {
        "question": " 165万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4398523296749115
    },
    {
        "question": " 7540分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.655513572072602
    },
    {
        "question": " 886分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.725579830377214
    },
    {
        "question": " 148兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.670399066431908
    },
    {
        "question": " 641億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.870238842221558
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.84兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.12845486538949
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.16万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.183672633969379
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.8京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.081271049895546
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.56兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7228180268426145
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.7兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.197131588977417
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.230757673476898
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.3億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.988299380156125
    },
    {
        "question": " 101msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.005959662288822
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.99垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1992260281505835
    },
    {
        "question": " 819兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9769007825843627
    },
    {
        "question": " 2603億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8592465787279278
    },
    {
        "question": " 6473万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03294816480213569
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.18兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9629275906474986
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.176607840008108
    },
    {
        "question": " 4456垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.150181337902284
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.7京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.030747648310802
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.6垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.75804095440816
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.43兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1478070392919846
    },
    {
        "question": " 9583兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.981513816774259
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.29兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.51656702721594
    },
    {
        "question": " 1012億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.005178869261314
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.9万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.400635621109608
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.788621771531479
    },
    {
        "question": " 5945日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2118834738949447
    },
    {
        "question": " 528日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.10305728818089
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.98日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.934864846638757
    },
    {
        "question": " 712日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.78889218832823
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10761858141807745
    },
    {
        "question": " 1967万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.913548325181955
    },
    {
        "question": " 24万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.157661499873614
    },
    {
        "question": " 222時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.903036769010725
    },
    {
        "question": " 3431兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.814723262695269
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.3億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2932390878853575
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.3万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.940529196469029
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.4分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.26109421112341
    },
    {
        "question": " 529億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.224595545008376
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.88兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.058462281990224
    },
    {
        "question": " 3032億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.925406647525416
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.88万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6813585721982713
    },
    {
        "question": " 5786秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.762405111504538
    },
    {
        "question": " 475秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.676881493413548
    },
    {
        "question": " 5215億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.218456206122196
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.53京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.042585676361078
    },
    {
        "question": " 203億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7503450525870043
    },
    {
        "question": " 11兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.262737536856092
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.1億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.281713071702441
    },
    {
        "question": " 19万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.27942187921628
    },
    {
        "question": " 1002京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.502167083791067
    },
    {
        "question": " 149兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2377394063525666
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.22兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.068558052392887
    },
    {
        "question": " 8845億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.16852740609872
    },
    {
        "question": " 283万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.45215765671631103
    },
    {
        "question": " 2331万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.367505165383596
    },
    {
        "question": " 473usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.675228002821812
    },
    {
        "question": " 404京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1079383150100597
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.102474004660679
    },
    {
        "question": " 6973兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.287100133128922
    },
    {
        "question": " 8391京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.145642753107799
    },
    {
        "question": " 5486億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.739228713585631
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.4兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.405419089485732
    },
    {
        "question": " 479万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.6799982563005362
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.97億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.213773109250969
    },
    {
        "question": " 973日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.368488217623591
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4714646572077665
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.43日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.807490392587882
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.5万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3683755490333105
    },
    {
        "question": " 1875万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.892843280572406
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.781232643016741
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.47時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.294064528656203
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.900130828085459
    },
    {
        "question": " 290万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7414620294438068
    },
    {
        "question": " 1037億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.857341420526277
    },
    {
        "question": " 799万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.124509878035788
    },
    {
        "question": " 960分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.760458824952311
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.11分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.564250949043082
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.26分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.407365016859316
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.593534958795525
    },
    {
        "question": " 112兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.112182906324689
    },
    {
        "question": " 1304万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.558975872346093
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.52億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.876943914531104
    },
    {
        "question": " 320京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.0062879250352
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.8兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.652162409831353
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.97億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9161737712383942
    },
    {
        "question": " 461億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.885440600210794
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.89万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6897471467494263
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.545808533913903
    },
    {
        "question": " 443京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.710035877843192
    },
    {
        "question": " 2775兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.886979382997982
    },
    {
        "question": " 340億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.753203951760864
    },
    {
        "question": " 189万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2765633643617438
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.69兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.755480116171507
    },
    {
        "question": " 3449usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.537650776644604
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.17e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.002202693973647
    },
    {
        "question": " 545兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7996555712163123
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.7京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.031332804899468
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.1京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.130805787601528
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.1京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.51995685150155
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.1387571880917786
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.6億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.77536030460632
    },
    {
        "question": " 2877年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0211732833059965
    },
    {
        "question": " 1059年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.967527519545419
    },
    {
        "question": " 1161億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.502583310016085
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.9日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1716040810593427
    },
    {
        "question": " 18万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.41275375674527
    },
    {
        "question": " 3753万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6319001706818432
    },
    {
        "question": " 247万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.012403276940444
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.23万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.572292922696468
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.4万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.1627916060016
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2996360513227265
    },
    {
        "question": " 1992分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14097512485246155
    },
    {
        "question": " 2047億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.532907784085596
    },
    {
        "question": " 356万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.330112310747214
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.1分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.103116239861851
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.7億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8939194284487582
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.9兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.38321792600817
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.38万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8206864462916164
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.08億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.179835325920867
    },
    {
        "question": " 1123京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.551554052984457
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.88億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.058394098688965
    },
    {
        "question": " 550万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18408376617173428
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.39億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.027454615091093
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.5万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.561976825793808
    },
    {
        "question": " 8619msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.935437120763245
    },
    {
        "question": " 429垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.133626801371223
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.117968322650251
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.490890867812044
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.258937013614496
    },
    {
        "question": " 3062億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.48605958814835
    },
    {
        "question": " 1019usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.008281270433272425
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.8usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.885099632111723
    },
    {
        "question": " 8542京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4327659245366893
    },
    {
        "question": " 2214兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.408719835760378
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.3京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0272135471929555
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.04京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.069614607436313
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.036875749984372
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.48兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.3950029043968435
    },
    {
        "question": " 220億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.342711457334186
    },
    {
        "question": " 1548万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.75196943862689
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.9年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.681741082281428
    },
    {
        "question": " 1283年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.828845798161181
    },
    {
        "question": " 388万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.026138527624755
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.2万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.372209062336995
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.027441385968576
    },
    {
        "question": " 163億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2691788925644545
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.5万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.090038046281615
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.93億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.052201103521769
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.95兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.793582283525256
    },
    {
        "question": " 152分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4037135723078755
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.77分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.539487164434856
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.53京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.377822494476655
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.97兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5355981239742515
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.529003289078944
    },
    {
        "question": " 1267万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.324514527111216
    },
    {
        "question": " 667万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.823938137704115
    },
    {
        "question": " 287秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.457275576048728
    },
    {
        "question": " 1694兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.730100648471408
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.8兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.802330460912098
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.46兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.834080333132573
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.513535558449489
    },
    {
        "question": " 227億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.356205035140784
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.1msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.399914198723687
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.04垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.811067880967922
    },
    {
        "question": " 297兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.535913828562709
    },
    {
        "question": " 4236兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.070611617761015
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.6兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.215594176864735
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.14億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.616485368926049
    },
    {
        "question": " 580万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7632861321863054
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.76usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.9423786251385717
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.67垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.065835072390431
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.2垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.916013398480991
    },
    {
        "question": " 744兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3150412539690937
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.91京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.993762303122788
    },
    {
        "question": " 461京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.663705502327693
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.4兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.482544712299961
    },
    {
        "question": " 8935nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.9511002614518282
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.3万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.805845437318768
    },
    {
        "question": " 1450億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.599193254388187
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.626002776038861
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.221529465176319
    },
    {
        "question": " 2204時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9629567414235027
    },
    {
        "question": " 1344万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.906584558192119
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.47時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9490309044074845
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.05時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.163463955104553
    },
    {
        "question": " 607億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.062567802464918
    },
    {
        "question": " 237億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.217300480834527
    },
    {
        "question": " 5703億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.977948171475644
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9069561375988084
    },
    {
        "question": " 160分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.982524104426998
    },
    {
        "question": " 133億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6241247257848563
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.131669999427048
    },
    {
        "question": " 57億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.199735443360196
    },
    {
        "question": " 1060億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.247175560569275
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.8兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.492622975126203
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.9兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.715721524574003
    },
    {
        "question": " 239兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.822534974636506
    },
    {
        "question": " 6241億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.017084982621709
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.38億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.641618863815918
    },
    {
        "question": " 161万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.208082355393692
    },
    {
        "question": " 144京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.658453390625615
    },
    {
        "question": " 2364兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4370952478211585
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.22京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3019445103828815
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.5兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.720574304445253
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.92兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.464855678648995
    },
    {
        "question": " 715億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.854108225353639
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.055972084637084
    },
    {
        "question": " 7278垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.363225433015618
    },
    {
        "question": " 8705京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.003284076408512
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.3京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.015262541723704
    },
    {
        "question": " 304兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7046645390116995
    },
    {
        "question": " 4192億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6224192052678683
    },
    {
        "question": " 833億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.92073988461112
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.1883473386582433
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.3年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.178252501081623
    },
    {
        "question": " 205億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.74867256383202
    },
    {
        "question": " 223日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7280056764662985
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.5日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.613185827917726
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.280489970843424
    },
    {
        "question": " 1042万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0755273726599865
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.3万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.50788458652373
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.5時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.644266797779241
    },
    {
        "question": " 582時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.32119570007547
    },
    {
        "question": " 2690兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.70907172888589
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9033535750483321
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.5億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.85000446431098
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7984106765884995
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.782102448073647
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.8京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.929071832883773
    },
    {
        "question": " 166兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.28276728961211
    },
    {
        "question": " 203億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.751723744627912
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.43万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.956381374814728
    },
    {
        "question": " 1502秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.176704466597886
    },
    {
        "question": " 280秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.447177553010674
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.723589956211048
    },
    {
        "question": " 8650兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.000536217493595
    },
    {
        "question": " 767万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3282135762222238
    },
    {
        "question": " 5660万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.974643953049311
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3453129390297336
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.8msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.87376931192277
    },
    {
        "question": " 1407msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.148277439167426
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.3兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.010229466967758283
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.279481553335383
    },
    {
        "question": " 226京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.797590126134079
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.6593529910081
    },
    {
        "question": " 471億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.672806955993566
    },
    {
        "question": " 1855億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.268390418104868
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.4usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.309760656350814
    },
    {
        "question": " 8568京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4340958530822476
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.7京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.735571690837543
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.4京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.155079383718071
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.5兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9073446385842425
    },
    {
        "question": " 314兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.496927164753814
    },
    {
        "question": " 243兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.386144069975362
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.1698271872849686
    },
    {
        "question": " 169万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.789600090811106
    },
    {
        "question": " 1686年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.947605141228305
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.86億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.894226152825421
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.3万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.072861739674339
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.49815922181808
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.8万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.617295712721699
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.10143347448482
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8723467235157765
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.8時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.378155010914532
    },
    {
        "question": " 9163時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.518333117787074
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.5兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.70208382675839
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.102772770334929
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.81万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.166792505802661
    },
    {
        "question": " 335分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.303367851123086
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.9億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.113034168277733
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6207601049951643
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7577470817485665
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.4億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.121442379556417
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.89万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.995391800431706
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.04兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9841970619822535
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.22兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.781286841744846
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.67兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0079678643337
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.65兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8893349978970875
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.22万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7180480145813382
    },
    {
        "question": " 111万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.045644741480366
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8415089014221913
    },
    {
        "question": " 322兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.571562666192932
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.4京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.10056752079014
    },
    {
        "question": " 363億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7817405560145856
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.13兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.960292470747323
    },
    {
        "question": " 8878usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.9482948433495719
    },
    {
        "question": " 181京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7585909454086057
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.1垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8488814872422346
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.5兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09727549404205948
    },
    {
        "question": " 470兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.893841383854475
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.95兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.774497248124933
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.84兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.766307880205437
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.38万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.3773227692542167
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.7年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.267600928679373
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.3億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.985532114071715
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.8日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7565402194994437
    },
    {
        "question": " 292日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.62340770403557
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1012448724119395
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.2日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.8668420215417
    },
    {
        "question": " 57億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.813022172788752
    },
    {
        "question": " 196万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.911989067334112
    },
    {
        "question": " 9792時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.547160148307601
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.946044456752945
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.71億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.266541849093043
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.1万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.387448508827471
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.492262043105816
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.5分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5524735282820217
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.946836903087373
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.28分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.640480689342956
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.84兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.186489924672749
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.1万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7629903856060649
    },
    {
        "question": " 5062秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14802813300739515
    },
    {
        "question": " 383秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.804653398630254
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.153815147268103
    },
    {
        "question": " 3529京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.048801625218195
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.56京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.941800213328023
    },
    {
        "question": " 2508万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8430587859107475
    },
    {
        "question": " 341万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.755084997929477
    },
    {
        "question": " 574億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.758609980187638
    },
    {
        "question": " 8782msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.943615607006946
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.09msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.611671737215751
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.9兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1996477077749126
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.286469133122367
    },
    {
        "question": " 135兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.575601667577471
    },
    {
        "question": " 1兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.223602774609229
    },
    {
        "question": " 745兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.871892649511011
    },
    {
        "question": " 5945usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.7741474030717299
    },
    {
        "question": " 661垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.321299643130707
    },
    {
        "question": " 121京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.145722626524582
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.2京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.117538562638097
    },
    {
        "question": " 528京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.944193921945769
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.9京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.110877280705445
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.254120416918237
    },
    {
        "question": " 8518nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.9303549607334438
    },
    {
        "question": " 696年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.405000334039317
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.28万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.573735044580022
    },
    {
        "question": " 15年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.897649475476397
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.561438696923044
    },
    {
        "question": " 1463万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.602936407302969
    },
    {
        "question": " 949日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.357640531928256
    },
    {
        "question": " 359万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.713374507754278
    },
    {
        "question": " 2512日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.336599523736375
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.41万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7909609885313595
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.88838987415046
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.2万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.213396106535282
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.9万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.875749158455788
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.1兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.035854785571667
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.1万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.165836698851289
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2333385251879365
    },
    {
        "question": " 2547万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.18425755571614
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.52億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2430099549203621
    },
    {
        "question": " 1699億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.293591376046418
    },
    {
        "question": " 482万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.126494491374283
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.580891469527864
    },
    {
        "question": " 231秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.363439101871338
    },
    {
        "question": " 4秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.601899321653235
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.27兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0154776646121286
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.324195503040528
    },
    {
        "question": " 3032億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.925433008631473
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5966128174116974
    },
    {
        "question": " 6735万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8283634564353095
    },
    {
        "question": " 116万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.065437736470574
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6286377644751022
    },
    {
        "question": " 4679兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.733678924164667
    },
    {
        "question": " 2434兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.829958410808641
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.3億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.03666580197684
    },
    {
        "question": " 118億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.070927094864114
    },
    {
        "question": " 979万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.9907273989449275
    },
    {
        "question": " 5022usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.700837546678789
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7016939907994602
    },
    {
        "question": " 2065兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3783575105435797
    },
    {
        "question": " 42兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0672607162889092
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.1兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1469009059410222
    },
    {
        "question": " 105京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.022309135889575
    },
    {
        "question": " 8850兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.946955100656785
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.471027564342182
    },
    {
        "question": " 100年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.944601519365522
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.4年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.126201806574473
    },
    {
        "question": " 3074日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9253671232381022
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4572732169476375
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.7兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.304961442982716
    },
    {
        "question": " 1496時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7947075039544536
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.3時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2598038536657636
    },
    {
        "question": " 1121時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.605795461033081
    },
    {
        "question": " 473万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9540531072737934
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.32兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.477058777481757
    },
    {
        "question": " 188億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.496539505488471
    },
    {
        "question": " 1万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.779277527935346
    },
    {
        "question": " 788分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.674576151028259
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.7兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.222880263178973
    },
    {
        "question": " 630兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.86317314488518
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.48917957930563194
    },
    {
        "question": " 456億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.880338943953852
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5892279177919884
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.3兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.412579837668455
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.5億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8665985711268425
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.6兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.613370979510067
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.086424160350052
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5897752515182613
    },
    {
        "question": " 1583京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.26291017975464
    },
    {
        "question": " 1279兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.550499753705294
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.9兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.961693529959067
    },
    {
        "question": " 3318兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.520879297262013
    },
    {
        "question": " 7699億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.886411497377514
    },
    {
        "question": " 2599京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.916023732671614
    },
    {
        "question": " 424兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6910523152683745
    },
    {
        "question": " 138京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5823004623027614
    },
    {
        "question": " 885億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16882912643395587
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30272122585246586
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.334424639497049
    },
    {
        "question": " 902万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.9551677377218386
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.83万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.014741987877009
    },
    {
        "question": " 1415日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5885332327204706
    },
    {
        "question": " 102日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3871507254252786
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.5日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.947205329563595
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.23日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.795767368188916
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.8兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.937123915508439
    },
    {
        "question": " 606時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4024196081929763
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.08万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.096375656077779
    },
    {
        "question": " 717時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.411869742125332
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.818823220336604
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.1万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.722975517547257
    },
    {
        "question": " 251万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.621827572659329
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.68分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.20560430048892
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.894843232287649
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5147804931548805
    },
    {
        "question": " 921億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.027984997764079
    },
    {
        "question": " 23兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.804687382279957
    },
    {
        "question": " 2376万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.597759398271384
    },
    {
        "question": " 1949秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.289825155156137
    },
    {
        "question": " 468億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17150727762500706
    },
    {
        "question": " 1583億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2629321350135507
    },
    {
        "question": " 135億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5748947284466794
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.441801306524043
    },
    {
        "question": " 254億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.404744306217028
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.4垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.228423071775916
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.099376173771823
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.3京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.21662140787828
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.59億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7766795327464437
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.2億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.715901283769754
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.029751260608972
    },
    {
        "question": " 2123垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.828092696499742
    },
    {
        "question": " 3898垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.654287343947953
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.517599449635112
    },
    {
        "question": " 6926兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.062336302016002
    },
    {
        "question": " 190兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.278222446718339
    },
    {
        "question": " 229万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.3603196112710716
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.7万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.9397579537190945
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.114988555031317
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.564655662827748
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.650463656462423
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.56万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.566237661720968
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.56日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.487550370618008
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.104334035669547
    },
    {
        "question": " 200時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9217263437041912
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.9万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.548387579577004
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.16時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.468010395153584
    },
    {
        "question": " 435億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.917634325019194
    },
    {
        "question": " 3903億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.433097876515024
    },
    {
        "question": " 3861分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8085173750824435
    },
    {
        "question": " 387万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.36535338662799
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.1兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4699340276926955
    },
    {
        "question": " 185万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3315920748391585
    },
    {
        "question": " 7658万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.327834113416219
    },
    {
        "question": " 7928万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.121026573334346
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.2秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.973968815122218
    },
    {
        "question": " 185京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.769349346138316
    },
    {
        "question": " 2981億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5378981612986484
    },
    {
        "question": " 1808億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.700875731447295
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.2573754418526
    },
    {
        "question": " 8078msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9073057169366039
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.679378986392219
    },
    {
        "question": " 110京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.10444645546601
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.784057274048725
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.1億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9859055317670848
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.8兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.776823624691901
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.93兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.773271638427389
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.653428695343656
    },
    {
        "question": " 7139京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.917125041372346
    },
    {
        "question": " 1100京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.485007637085712
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.33043017077653
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.93兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6929205517170436
    },
    {
        "question": " 5010万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6998433139824576
    },
    {
        "question": " 113万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.051477223416353
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.56万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.440569940296207
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.99972821548079
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.1年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.48140159808153
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.67万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.002495855110935
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.952688164630516
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.2万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.966204612693115
    },
    {
        "question": " 2584万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.469826525697264
    },
    {
        "question": " 2112億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.94449102822946
    },
    {
        "question": " 2739時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.993846383689773
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.78億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8565093774031936
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.19万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.633621215229517
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.98万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.99826209483274
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.3万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.606124230618776
    },
    {
        "question": " 16京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.705361682242748
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2424044586344387
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.65兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.111136615416694
    },
    {
        "question": " 506秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9259392292240587
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.13秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7874170625439896
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.4兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.425686790275136
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.194214628963801
    },
    {
        "question": " 192億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7279002574658184
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.565221140644395
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2026100617076074
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.629342639495272
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.2兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0466407879998902
    },
    {
        "question": " 136億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5768484701247389
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.229856632113339
    },
    {
        "question": " 2120億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.326409512098275
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.6億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.91153762780201
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.0558556345527332
    },
    {
        "question": " 530垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2254050578435915
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.129686157222056
    },
    {
        "question": " 412兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.058691697102246
    },
    {
        "question": " 1223京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.309326073429833
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.87京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.768711106462344
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.4億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7358242624799374
    },
    {
        "question": " 4531万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.656227513150571
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.58万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.543757865032061
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.29万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.574485328772205
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.667305497983959
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.4万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.168253480781051
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.5万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.967771252484042
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.8日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.53618866248067
    },
    {
        "question": " 730万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9205905197292745
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.933640637619795
    },
    {
        "question": " 109時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.594523923027046
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.12億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8943776505953056
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9453750068361397
    },
    {
        "question": " 112億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.271552906240846
    },
    {
        "question": " 8829分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.724078779990368
    },
    {
        "question": " 919億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4644745653946307
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.109386885960684
    },
    {
        "question": " 8664万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.381425186724714
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.97億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.516500017523156
    },
    {
        "question": " 4412秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.644645290512759
    },
    {
        "question": " 1629京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.713184569472462
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.91京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.835184454567006
    },
    {
        "question": " 267億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8708707600158734
    },
    {
        "question": " 637万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.025792884224158
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.52億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.814133744913428
    },
    {
        "question": " 1052msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.021983632842752
    },
    {
        "question": " 174兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7419228364238528
    },
    {
        "question": " 1453億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22591285320497811
    },
    {
        "question": " 1116京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.49130453749693
    },
    {
        "question": " 6715万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04889289593029478
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0272001763652767
    },
    {
        "question": " 30万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.4764831243291887
    },
    {
        "question": " 147万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.167529671405877
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9281447394134252
    },
    {
        "question": " 195京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.352550707303145
    },
    {
        "question": " 3046京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.92746250216076
    },
    {
        "question": " 394京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.816900710289431
    },
    {
        "question": " 631京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.800240399289573
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.45兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.871946179162012
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.57万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.6598275492418335
    },
    {
        "question": " 2188年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.282572305556972
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.6年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.06222631153299
    },
    {
        "question": " 1159万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.501831770208595
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.3日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3061373450219866
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.2日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.665867380908303
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.6日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.598799579054924
    },
    {
        "question": " 921万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.021629666945641
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7490764996787975
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.784747118504156
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.8万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.26064374380863065
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2110903482887356
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.89億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.682422744254641
    },
    {
        "question": " 8744分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.719867106118137
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.74万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.351346703322143
    },
    {
        "question": " 5171万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.21480091929460765
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.262408921412989
    },
    {
        "question": " 7127億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.296586753957866
    },
    {
        "question": " 1718万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.45693341499541
    },
    {
        "question": " 203秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.3079873252483765
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8557096406157336
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.5億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4695111670480832
    },
    {
        "question": " 5792万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2065019984971947
    },
    {
        "question": " 2652億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.64538454362593
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.084230287190218
    },
    {
        "question": " 8441msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.926407524791411
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.27888650350561
    },
    {
        "question": " 2686垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.930262243628935
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.02京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.369766322013021
    },
    {
        "question": " 1506兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.621609719431185
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.8億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.193885389986354
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.92億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7723387550045064
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.4兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.380984967001405
    },
    {
        "question": " 2047usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.3111527167836625
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.065e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.816155293717465
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.1垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.849817929695565
    },
    {
        "question": " 450兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0970664835479944
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.13兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.837735118879632
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1848881473368973
    },
    {
        "question": " 9731万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.9881614452399232
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.13兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.85285734984082
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7297160903404745
    },
    {
        "question": " 856年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.652876990296898
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.535623609156249
    },
    {
        "question": " 1597万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.583508410934837
    },
    {
        "question": " 196日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4508884317351844
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.965240108679376
    },
    {
        "question": " 394億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.652751408904561
    },
    {
        "question": " 1343万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.747822575087377
    },
    {
        "question": " 307時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.04395037059616
    },
    {
        "question": " 107万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3080727590116017
    },
    {
        "question": " 954万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.821165092380733
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.71万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.109036311566087
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.15分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.5667333939056
    },
    {
        "question": " 770億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3875038926426893
    },
    {
        "question": " 242万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4476524363497234
    },
    {
        "question": " 4264万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.073511785169853
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.5万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.765347646098957
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.410698391816176
    },
    {
        "question": " 1378億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.640480481457808
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.307887180966562
    },
    {
        "question": " 2882万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9033478169284459
    },
    {
        "question": " 1717万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.456563393955291
    },
    {
        "question": " 1229億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.08959769763446
    },
    {
        "question": " 275兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9408089507890438
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.48垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.60447688530884
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7890460777643553
    },
    {
        "question": " 179兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.475004716426319
    },
    {
        "question": " 351億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.545122829155676
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.6万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.9114785797526146
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.7垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.089468306646
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.280260351605425
    },
    {
        "question": " 326兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.957166191631332
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.3兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0926748057248377
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16740696138170197
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.012613831231138
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.3万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.633007204969792
    },
    {
        "question": " 178年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.812411298316082
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.8万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2754801760386387
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.53万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.78389898873591
    },
    {
        "question": " 23日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.52063405185276
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.5日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.33516098111032
    },
    {
        "question": " 236万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4299417130184975
    },
    {
        "question": " 182億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.879424726503292
    },
    {
        "question": " 6803万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.610852671352308
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.807296990067405
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.832460025815937
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.48638666720277
    },
    {
        "question": " 3302万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.360460102751369
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.19億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.013311445333646
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.870943009977838
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.76兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.638830342431956
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.22億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.161250442057143
    },
    {
        "question": " 1345億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.350490459599817
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.2万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.749573406809818
    },
    {
        "question": " 6283兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.299345816927849
    },
    {
        "question": " 2276億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4206187049448133
    },
    {
        "question": " 1835万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7072497363204022
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.39億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.090436803606341
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.64兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.560990104455797
    },
    {
        "question": " 713msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.853059046939599
    },
    {
        "question": " 6575msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.817922329037156
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.56634498057841
    },
    {
        "question": " 759兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.943827851159213
    },
    {
        "question": " 140兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.591092927584585
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.466824324613184
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.57億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6597702312324802
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.08兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.487871693597098
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.57京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16121497929661444
    },
    {
        "question": " 373垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.634926673425191
    },
    {
        "question": " 2459兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.834385046260366
    },
    {
        "question": " 6278億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0196421978804893
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.88兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.769126020430169
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.3689927062308525
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.72億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.82758675090031
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.88万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.531618226084136
    },
    {
        "question": " 731年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.584584686249574
    },
    {
        "question": " 1094日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4768453267421935
    },
    {
        "question": " 1501万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.55668325170307
    },
    {
        "question": " 4834日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.842627091800014
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.024237664917378
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.48億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.59961958984385
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.5万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.216720206739436
    },
    {
        "question": " 5338時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.505531572887268
    },
    {
        "question": " 2029時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.863575740055436
    },
    {
        "question": " 2484時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.951521132737316
    },
    {
        "question": " 8136億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.189738448719295
    },
    {
        "question": " 3366分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3687347491325066
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4670366187139754
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.32万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.747690553168804
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.07万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.483430652613213
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.526204612355139
    },
    {
        "question": " 1304万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.178614483750594
    },
    {
        "question": " 2094億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.764691476981367
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.9秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1990465812115938
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.26448737830458
    },
    {
        "question": " 402億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1052624080980269
    },
    {
        "question": " 71億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.914676419267668
    },
    {
        "question": " 630万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24276177588740122
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.234115599593897
    },
    {
        "question": " 14億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.145433623200591
    },
    {
        "question": " 1659msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.219948559558679
    },
    {
        "question": " 2447msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.388584265480004
    },
    {
        "question": " 5194兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.216697660884206
    },
    {
        "question": " 174兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.302903751999098
    },
    {
        "question": " 3409兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.976298913363239
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.251194381819122
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.207449414631436
    },
    {
        "question": " 4459万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.6491946784647915
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.295e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.613418843350306
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.222188520487345
    },
    {
        "question": " 97垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.430492732932695
    },
    {
        "question": " 115兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2823372019767874
    },
    {
        "question": " 255京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.406340565616887
    },
    {
        "question": " 7472兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.87342553764541
    },
    {
        "question": " 2019万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.305208385062757
    },
    {
        "question": " 4906年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.633211427171199
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.8年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.119688633554379
    },
    {
        "question": " 261万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8547559492786423
    },
    {
        "question": " 2091万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.700472477139922
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.13万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.068534959960825
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.940113857047731
    },
    {
        "question": " 1582億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.256655637370809
    },
    {
        "question": " 1973時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9148741723778373
    },
    {
        "question": " 147万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.946098966329238
    },
    {
        "question": " 285万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.734069645952915
    },
    {
        "question": " 193万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.127182777617045
    },
    {
        "question": " 1180億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.293715727317398
    },
    {
        "question": " 519分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4934439956747685
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.2億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1368636558420784
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.25億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.575323031316157
    },
    {
        "question": " 3191万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9476430662028985
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.6万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.841159625212618
    },
    {
        "question": " 221万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.34373483149912
    },
    {
        "question": " 856億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43363020846822753
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.44兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.93486326908733
    },
    {
        "question": " 1932万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7298172248871293
    },
    {
        "question": " 5604億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.970367051292098
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0361788086347756
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.135198663345257
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.471743507960445
    },
    {
        "question": " 185兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7690415016288255
    },
    {
        "question": " 7450兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.935632607057007
    },
    {
        "question": " 989億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4390016337393619
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.2億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2182218765846153
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.5兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5736867202073626
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.1億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.624673449700671
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.4万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.675900787657474
    },
    {
        "question": " 388垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.089623990494049
    },
    {
        "question": " 174垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.304783930911148
    },
    {
        "question": " 54京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.176144534854856
    },
    {
        "question": " 5187京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.93680268924465
    },
    {
        "question": " 12兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.077539358215011
    },
    {
        "question": " 605兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.781534605606485
    },
    {
        "question": " 972億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.98748248547538
    },
    {
        "question": " 3233年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.452158778189015
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.06年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3292977988882555
    },
    {
        "question": " 2572万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8480121068154105
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.3万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.963562317508103
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.250763035739707
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.5日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6042719057743255
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.476232759710934
    },
    {
        "question": " 2861万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.076288321429538
    },
    {
        "question": " 4718億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.953117213596599
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8885687130638606
    },
    {
        "question": " 3221万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.729796096615644
    },
    {
        "question": " 133万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.900472656725546
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.7分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.31839123349829
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.52億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0472481645235054
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.7億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7932209040073035
    },
    {
        "question": " 263億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.863097092608811
    },
    {
        "question": " 295万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.691226558136793
    },
    {
        "question": " 51万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.707898187536735
    },
    {
        "question": " 1841億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7662134739489079
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.1京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.736960627546573
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.76兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.386227241718546
    },
    {
        "question": " 3080万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7103689226560688
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.6万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.872960779691882
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.32万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.96964471892829
    },
    {
        "question": " 1369兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6376774705648989
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.95垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.532680149799207
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6152509624618334
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.461442788171789
    },
    {
        "question": " 3848万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5852010343766132
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.78万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.9434622100536925
    },
    {
        "question": " 204usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.309967723924657
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.641e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.43774974835837
    },
    {
        "question": " 220京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.405299819983542
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.2垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.808924331549392
    },
    {
        "question": " 3940京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.817347493890422
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.297884932442663
    },
    {
        "question": " 1171万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.0685010845184495
    },
    {
        "question": " 1504万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.1773344130565295
    },
    {
        "question": " 7469年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.435550439349836
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.800531841087047
    },
    {
        "question": " 1215億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.52211279294934
    },
    {
        "question": " 581万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.144569735404685
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.5日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1518998965201135
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.12日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.789146059719923
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.08兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.545696026205961
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.5万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.971794723675833
    },
    {
        "question": " 220万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.120837717487532
    },
    {
        "question": " 633時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.357421478966568
    },
    {
        "question": " 216万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.614029514430946
    },
    {
        "question": " 677億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.672009267281624
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.471919595751975
    },
    {
        "question": " 4956分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.473308110998216
    },
    {
        "question": " 1544兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.689766402715398
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.76億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.823797440006146
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.488370544298512
    },
    {
        "question": " 236億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.595141086793767
    },
    {
        "question": " 9089秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.958516419188024
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.168666647694657
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.568936475587791
    },
    {
        "question": " 7040兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.911080585632665
    },
    {
        "question": " 4686億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.114525205011641
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.6億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0829732559434335
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.084727829133828
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.43万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.64677045306001
    },
    {
        "question": " 104京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.517158209117504
    },
    {
        "question": " 8140京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.974148681662687
    },
    {
        "question": " 524京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.163213596339736
    },
    {
        "question": " 1497兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3970100495987365
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.07兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.782861445925512
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.8億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.96747645065373
    },
    {
        "question": " 106京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5273920429649623
    },
    {
        "question": " 15垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.240231341365549
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.9垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.242446748825204
    },
    {
        "question": " 3186京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.725092055657877
    },
    {
        "question": " 381億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5806949115293722
    },
    {
        "question": " 2865億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.457143747294182
    },
    {
        "question": " 3224億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.50841158991505
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.4万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.323385441513022
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.003362868968507
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.81年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.079909040380679
    },
    {
        "question": " 3194日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9419700660004671
    },
    {
        "question": " 798万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.282183590499711
    },
    {
        "question": " 459万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.820357035929652
    },
    {
        "question": " 1051万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0790402106059522
    },
    {
        "question": " 418時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2408157141522191
    },
    {
        "question": " 159時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9795561092344
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.5時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4568035113970295
    },
    {
        "question": " 44兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.922972643231441
    },
    {
        "question": " 2589万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.254732295262343
    },
    {
        "question": " 337分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7498478651991203
    },
    {
        "question": " 15万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.953337936612922
    },
    {
        "question": " 9694億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.487681818706813
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.7兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.494357776693517
    },
    {
        "question": " 9108億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.403141060717367
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.53811577281272
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.891166017495687
    },
    {
        "question": " 3121京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.995459753269168
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.433868800383689
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.6兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.156676234357676
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3616031592066937
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.92億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.465171205615312
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.57msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.41047428376657
    },
    {
        "question": " 371京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.070317012278229
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4796191321514451
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.466740851300623
    },
    {
        "question": " 1557億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.414166407508974
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.292709034519222
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.149080486811962
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.053875071122524
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.624e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.920199861120246
    },
    {
        "question": " 516兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7763994493224102
    },
    {
        "question": " 3501京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.98787656724628
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.7兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2161015245013047
    },
    {
        "question": " 4630億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6655916404551103
    },
    {
        "question": " 1379万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.1394901023721637
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.2765389035794685
    },
    {
        "question": " 6947年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4041184637164985
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4502849575957795
    },
    {
        "question": " 2714日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.813754092271585
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.2万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.716535922209705
    },
    {
        "question": " 116日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.001038680207437
    },
    {
        "question": " 173万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2963307020131984
    },
    {
        "question": " 6351時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4226218699703406
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.9万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.475948232482982
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.22時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.35035778154191
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.809482521961597
    },
    {
        "question": " 885兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.226070772330825
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.15億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.340589574703114
    },
    {
        "question": " 4530億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.877958289977153
    },
    {
        "question": " 804分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.683266759094233
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5617901846817352
    },
    {
        "question": " 208億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.381223737672915
    },
    {
        "question": " 8018億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.34774773794169
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.4億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.551279541739433
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.028387830195715
    },
    {
        "question": " 617億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2913125017243956
    },
    {
        "question": " 2614兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.480726515219779
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.83兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.209054549743353
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.3万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2097467413079843
    },
    {
        "question": " 861万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9352093784663067
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.349147775909418
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.890705834814048
    },
    {
        "question": " 132京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.183758774001696
    },
    {
        "question": " 3002兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.92109842859633
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.4京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.915374420445445
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.4億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.583976469968354
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.189033046151652
    },
    {
        "question": " 1389京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6439641448608797
    },
    {
        "question": " 107垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.091822481333464
    },
    {
        "question": " 741京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.313478710145005
    },
    {
        "question": " 158京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.420322265378459
    },
    {
        "question": " 439京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.642663891800648
    },
    {
        "question": " 137万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.136112874364277
    },
    {
        "question": " 279億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.445347233962666
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6892050253549735
    },
    {
        "question": " 8460年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.869855886393528
    },
    {
        "question": " 8065年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.62724271325467
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.69年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.48527916611832
    },
    {
        "question": " 1410日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5868683526744245
    },
    {
        "question": " 193万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.665046384340516
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.985493801414163
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.1億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.035783832950813
    },
    {
        "question": " 94万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.592876206352241
    },
    {
        "question": " 357時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3307155066014555
    },
    {
        "question": " 621時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.349248185238622
    },
    {
        "question": " 166兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.499975470359372
    },
    {
        "question": " 93億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.810008984502694
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4121645226565205
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.88兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.449549313168398
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.42兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.597931475920041
    },
    {
        "question": " 381万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.025169532782659
    },
    {
        "question": " 109秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2612537121016667
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5435245655722851
    },
    {
        "question": " 1126兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1149705347072985
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.3億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.895081434689973
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.3万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9720042900810189
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.01億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.700055094527999
    },
    {
        "question": " 6949京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.343149065862182
    },
    {
        "question": " 3584億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6178533390568852
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.3億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07993568759645298
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.09京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.711896110589779
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.276630634383972
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.1663184850371064
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.2垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.06001982632429
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2052138142944875
    },
    {
        "question": " 321兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9500802503320402
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.6京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.78562542292277
    },
    {
        "question": " 345億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.538097032989939
    },
    {
        "question": " 2081億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.318205460536878
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.496254476839814
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.17年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4745227412902944
    },
    {
        "question": " 139年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.085768291143862
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.740613504657659
    },
    {
        "question": " 410億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.050518765790684
    },
    {
        "question": " 5763万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.140883333128128
    },
    {
        "question": " 1478日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.327931863305146
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.388515694228946
    },
    {
        "question": " 518万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.333789975742995
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.76時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.219609431532862
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.1時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.305060519550857
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.337578564160224
    },
    {
        "question": " 6830万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.676049606293825
    },
    {
        "question": " 761万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.103351399599589
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.857892624053685
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.22京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.465992266011064
    },
    {
        "question": " 27億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.495619171199489
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.647073658269113
    },
    {
        "question": " 1734万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.460890656888161
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.31秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6341611941693728
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.97垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.974657064906673
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.01兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6664581550573105
    },
    {
        "question": " 8201兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.357569560936254
    },
    {
        "question": " 108兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.25446005986279
    },
    {
        "question": " 7713万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.887224414359044
    },
    {
        "question": " 2649msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.423138174652206
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.18099382932729
    },
    {
        "question": " 5706兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2575518140822926
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.4兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.932855801938067
    },
    {
        "question": " 3438京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.980009897814856
    },
    {
        "question": " 92億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1858527374987338
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.4億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4688859908416605
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.9万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.9442287774544615
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.9usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.4627956970429508
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.901149991070323
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.129480807589681
    },
    {
        "question": " 4720京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.117618949123285
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.8兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.810622085244491
    },
    {
        "question": " 225億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3521406820227244
    },
    {
        "question": " 323万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.5094927079808542
    },
    {
        "question": " 2558億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.407913603726985
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.69876861581802
    },
    {
        "question": " 3224億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.946156477490671
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.2日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.814678405837662
    },
    {
        "question": " 313万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.6541761018679
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.6日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.842764513031919
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.1日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.618938639543561
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5358738198788826
    },
    {
        "question": " 1492億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.793445346697418
    },
    {
        "question": " 3527万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.325577791202361
    },
    {
        "question": " 202時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.861623253423952
    },
    {
        "question": " 214兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.608818843502362
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2280513762993
    },
    {
        "question": " 810分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.130576983029804
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.08193066216479
    },
    {
        "question": " 184分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.042852060421312
    },
    {
        "question": " 365兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0631263073876696
    },
    {
        "question": " 892万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.013806243328342
    },
    {
        "question": " 224億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.794758256138957
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.07億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.071261469450166
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.7万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.957668179268742
    },
    {
        "question": " 6656兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.324411954397691
    },
    {
        "question": " 1306兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.179406933258379
    },
    {
        "question": " 603兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.224092135861486
    },
    {
        "question": " 20兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.52395630721878
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1454242653043345
    },
    {
        "question": " 714msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.853569415344257
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.08msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.8501397300757745
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.59368168498606
    },
    {
        "question": " 6933京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.904393962273225
    },
    {
        "question": " 122億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5292006119558135
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.313053360301149
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.060223645475899
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.67万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.8240453629536535
    },
    {
        "question": " 622usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.794105310226717
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.747e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.940002405151317
    },
    {
        "question": " 6542京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.879192283786836
    },
    {
        "question": " 4328兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.07999001951773
    },
    {
        "question": " 189兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4993511169667335
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4466287632472103
    },
    {
        "question": " 478兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.679106243415172
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.04兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.482887324541057
    },
    {
        "question": " 15年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.739748451200564
    },
    {
        "question": " 5731日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1958965750745476
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4003990487241313
    },
    {
        "question": " 6801日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.990898090763737
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.042635502951967
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.028214610466186
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.24万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9736762991542725
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.6億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.557231144953008
    },
    {
        "question": " 1666時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.999890554981682
    },
    {
        "question": " 145時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.718050473432453
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.427862202383074
    },
    {
        "question": " 1265億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.943772596713016
    },
    {
        "question": " 1842億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.487211471243732
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.091242144777715
    },
    {
        "question": " 2010分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.081361661540658
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.78京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.078420558146183
    },
    {
        "question": " 1466万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2295683050982573
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.603454263900389
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.2億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.687119412350429
    },
    {
        "question": " 276秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.440425982272204
    },
    {
        "question": " 93秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.968344973954729
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.716716752232427
    },
    {
        "question": " 4030億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.668834899326007
    },
    {
        "question": " 1722万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6796108268283807
    },
    {
        "question": " 2490億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.618000754356345
    },
    {
        "question": " 167万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2214968015515844
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.25msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.352649373529096
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.3垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.920333244517371
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.48京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.604558607087247
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.1兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.151820910506599
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.558372449033714
    },
    {
        "question": " 42兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.623457653982112
    },
    {
        "question": " 154億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.18701128519397
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.4万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.405468336142313
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.686e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.72809944110942
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.36京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.985721824089552
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.2京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.126433093035949
    },
    {
        "question": " 34兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7531516336626383
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.7億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6197427314917547
    },
    {
        "question": " 298万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.4736045016866619
    },
    {
        "question": " 1602nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.2047841897333702
    },
    {
        "question": " 181年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.820907342863624
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.02330562389021
    },
    {
        "question": " 2547億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.843713543342718
    },
    {
        "question": " 367万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.944698941574697
    },
    {
        "question": " 112日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.207739163563829
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.091620056146688
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.258723902578263
    },
    {
        "question": " 1076万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.651646279370181
    },
    {
        "question": " 161万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9851544404249895
    },
    {
        "question": " 2945時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.02539765457743
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.807841952729125
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.236427590554564
    },
    {
        "question": " 1123万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8921008945086513
    },
    {
        "question": " 1053分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.244189608751457
    },
    {
        "question": " 4817分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.460920569558522
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.6兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.368270416601215
    },
    {
        "question": " 100兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.063417009234666
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.347874200505249
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.404337061894248
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.2万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.793794923471234
    },
    {
        "question": " 126京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.600019474995545
    },
    {
        "question": " 6948億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9053673278204792
    },
    {
        "question": " 135兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.573705912190335
    },
    {
        "question": " 193億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.507941546767773
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.5万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6184601146321596
    },
    {
        "question": " 445万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.648675519683179
    },
    {
        "question": " 745msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.8721210960983
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.05垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.283113022099358
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.8兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.537680992778263
    },
    {
        "question": " 805京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.349703859122227
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.3億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.887338167128041
    },
    {
        "question": " 271兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.432380390770115
    },
    {
        "question": " 9551万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.980045138109528
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.42万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.870618080301693
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.948326882990878
    },
    {
        "question": " 2952垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.533620205563041
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.2垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.769022296262298
    },
    {
        "question": " 5644兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.973408137297746
    },
    {
        "question": " 3237兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.51009303452314
    },
    {
        "question": " 1345万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.1285737652256367
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.12万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.4941540820400978
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.700976397131408
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.2年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.226038908425943
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.071083959508252
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.60465355416281
    },
    {
        "question": " 3884万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.969498488448306
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.49日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.032681067110192
    },
    {
        "question": " 442万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.703057826011225
    },
    {
        "question": " 561時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3690868347342366
    },
    {
        "question": " 7954時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.678737101413381
    },
    {
        "question": " 165時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7741639279765415
    },
    {
        "question": " 94億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.252483145424993
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.28億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.357673004640492
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.4億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.626989835248716
    },
    {
        "question": " 1765分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.024881628419645
    },
    {
        "question": " 11京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.542061092306527
    },
    {
        "question": " 820万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9773100003774768
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.98兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.287609491204178
    },
    {
        "question": " 2300万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.583524619120017
    },
    {
        "question": " 407秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.610106108827484
    },
    {
        "question": " 3023億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9816643448803319
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.7兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.768226276335383
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.87億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3917647043354986
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.34億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7450512395229243
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4260523673238605
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.68msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.8851493652991955
    },
    {
        "question": " 6900msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.838874199912
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.1兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10429525753407498
    },
    {
        "question": " 3388兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.593444243515288
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.9億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.28832780954110904
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.1兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.929306684749074
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.97兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.696646585018823
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.143724356234165
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.284776215660527
    },
    {
        "question": " 1058垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.525814682716375
    },
    {
        "question": " 6974垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.906969317048873
    },
    {
        "question": " 904京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.399640173995533
    },
    {
        "question": " 413京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.837781517064073
    },
    {
        "question": " 216京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.3338120651444
    },
    {
        "question": " 1835億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.263740911270859
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.35兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.866359112181186
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.71万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.132208737188393
    },
    {
        "question": " 1010年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.94684822362444
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.4年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.230897051701183
    },
    {
        "question": " 2374日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8132263242349924
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.504805369487315
    },
    {
        "question": " 137日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.295546482609655
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.4日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.603112682695342
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.61512326242146
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.1億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.111854404729875
    },
    {
        "question": " 1486万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.950032075644348
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.583609222501428
    },
    {
        "question": " 2003万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.581047596415499
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.96607939150065
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.382972950569926
    },
    {
        "question": " 1346分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.907162643639177
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.16万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.277814509431954
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.75兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.260527064227278
    },
    {
        "question": " 1259億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.163679395696715
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.32万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9649994872232082
    },
    {
        "question": " 523万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.94027176638853
    },
    {
        "question": " 889秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.948760931567476
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.1兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.460774832803102
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.56京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.614990760377793
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.91兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.393470923549941
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.670091859430726
    },
    {
        "question": " 4709msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6729516196646679
    },
    {
        "question": " 224万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.350900355967266
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.4msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.822172170903793
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.1垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.020552879878737
    },
    {
        "question": " 3361億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5899830643830795
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.4兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.004440555108455
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5342382708444826
    },
    {
        "question": " 8428万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9257332071206545
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.2万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.8760309469687586
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.837009668502212
    },
    {
        "question": " 3263兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5771544134987459
    },
    {
        "question": " 9250京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.409831337679109
    },
    {
        "question": " 5019兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.922480101431671
    },
    {
        "question": " 427京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.63080510244165
    },
    {
        "question": " 112兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.048426418428999
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.177277179714553
    },
    {
        "question": " 2161万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.897003606410298
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.634499107613553
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.730655666206776
    },
    {
        "question": " 2235日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.729513905221304
    },
    {
        "question": " 6311日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.736572867406196
    },
    {
        "question": " 473億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.732094521070331
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.776820638731861
    },
    {
        "question": " 676時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.607790476992571
    },
    {
        "question": " 1892時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.833173146935708
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.325142948091357
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.00043424821168
    },
    {
        "question": " 163億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.435102874663663
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9750182452788367
    },
    {
        "question": " 1847分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.044732582375605
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.3分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.164387103280749
    },
    {
        "question": " 623億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.295476108313303
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.283954108433294
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.88兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.213357018887969
    },
    {
        "question": " 2022万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.527529539361602
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.17595024642355
    },
    {
        "question": " 8413兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4261599619592396
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20417649500813928
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4465356152838758
    },
    {
        "question": " 242兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.606147303687136
    },
    {
        "question": " 462万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6643730892436777
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.6万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.917068355031063
    },
    {
        "question": " 476京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1790372782689245
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.18京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.777489580710547
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.8兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8882201287140985
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.5億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.627989994966933
    },
    {
        "question": " 3074兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.487773931433175
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.74万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5727516669314001
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.18e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.292210215825463
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.11垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.915551696533914
    },
    {
        "question": " 183垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.70560549454957
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.06垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.925630424916273
    },
    {
        "question": " 150億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1753905502025963
    },
    {
        "question": " 131兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.118237009786906
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.206135980186368
    }
]